<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 17.12 - December 2017</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 17.12.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-304 Add support of exporting RVM (AVEVA PDMS) New feature THREEDNET-312 Add shorthand way to scale geometries Improvement THREEDNET-314 Add support of exporting custom property/ID to nodes in GLTF format Improvement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 17.11 - November 2017</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 17.11.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-303 Add support of importing RVM-binary (AVEVA PDMS) New feature THREEDNET-305 Add support of merging meshes New feature THREEDNET-306 FBX to GLTF - incorrect material opacity in GLTF Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 17.10 - October 2017</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 17.10.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-292 Add support of importing 3MF New feature THREEDNET-302 OBJ to GLTF - incomplete rendering of 3D model Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 17.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 17.9.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-286 Add support to uniquely identify Meshes from FBX New feature THREEDNET-288 Add support to render scene in fully customized shaders New feature THREEDNET-284 Improve the memory consumption when writing a large FBX file Enhancement THREEDNET-293 Incorrect export OBJ with texture to GLTF and GLB Bug THREEDNET-290 Animate properties rotation (Euler) and scale for FBX format Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 17.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 17.8.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-279 Render scene into a cube map with 6 faces. New feature THREEDNET-280 Add post-processing of equirectangular projection. New feature THREEDNET-281 Render cube map to fisheye. New feature THREEDNET-276 Incorrect conversion of OBJ to GLTF and GLB. Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 17.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 17.7.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-265 Add support of exporting 3D scene to PLY format. New feature THREEDNET-271 Simplify the creation of transform matrix. New feature THREEDNET-270 Allow generate mesh from gray-scale image as a height map. New feature THREEDNET-272 The FBX file generated cannot be edited by 3ds max.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 17.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 17.6.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-257 Export 3D scene into GLTF 2.0 ASCII files New feature THREEDNET-258 Export 3D scene into GLTF 2.0 Binary files New feature THREEDNET-264 Models has tangent but has no bi-normal will not render correctly Bug THREEDNET-267 Materials in Collada files may not be loaded correctly.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 17.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 17.5.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-244 New PBR material to support physically based rendering New feature THREEDNET-250 Allow Aspose.3D API to import GLTF 2.0 ASCII files New feature THREEDNET-253 Allow Aspose.3D API to import GLTF 2.0 Binary files New feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 17.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 17.4.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-235 Add support of exporting 3D models to Google Draco (.drc) format. New feature THREEDNET-237 Improve camera movement in orthographic projection mode. Enhancement THREEDNET-238 Add support to zoom out Camera Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 17.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 17.3.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-233 Add support of importing Google Draco (.drc) files. New feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 17.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 17.2.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-230 Add support of importing the X (binary and ASCII) files. New feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 17.01 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-01-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-3d-for-net-17-01-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 17.1.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-227 Add support of importing the PLY models. New feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>