<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.12
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the December release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
We have optimized SVG files received with our image vectorization API, which now results in a reduction of SVG file size by 7-12% by removing redundant and useless information and reducing the size of SVG path elements through vector graphics optimization.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.11
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the November release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
We have halved the load time of large svg documents and reduced memory consumption by 40%. Several new optimization options have been added to the SVG Document Optimization API.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.10
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the October release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
We have added a new SVGOptimizer tool to optimize SVG documents, which provides functionality to remove redundant and useless information and reduce the size of SVG path elements through vector graphics optimization.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.9
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the September release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
We have
improved the algorithms of the Image Vectorization by adding a new approach to fitting Bezier curves, and also added a new feature for &amp;ldquo;stenciling&amp;rdquo; vectorized images;</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.8
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the August release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
we improved and expanded the interface for working with CSS color models described in the W3C specifications: https://www.w3.org/TR/css-color-4/ and https://www.w3.org/TR/css-color-5/ we optimized the CSS processing code to run faster.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.7
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the July release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
The &amp;lsquo;%userprofile%\AppData\Local\Microsoft\Windows\Fonts&amp;rsquo; folder was added to the default fonts lookup folders. This enhancement should fix the issue SVGNET-97.
We have reduced the size of svg files produced by text vectorization by about 2 times by using quadratic beziers instead of cubic beziers and replacing relative path commands with absolute ones.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.6
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the June release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
it was added support for rendering SVG textpath elements;
improved calculation accuracy of SVGGeometryElement.getPointAtLength() method;
it was added support for converting colors according to specifications: https://www.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.5
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the May release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
it was fixed the issue that caused pagination to hang on SVG documents with elements that had an infinite or very large height;
improved performance of CSS style parsing algorithm.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.4
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the April release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
several improvements were added to the code working with TTF substitution tables; new approximation algorithms for the processing of Gaussian Blur and Morphological filters were implemented, which made it possible to avoid the problem of exponential growth of the execution time depending on the size of the kernel.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.3
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the March release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
this release contains improvements to the text vectorization and rendering algorithms for Indian and Arabic scryps. Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category SVGNET-20 Vectorizing text is not working for certain languages Bug SVGNET-23 Vectorized right-to-left Arabic text coming out as left-to-right Bug SVGNET-24 SVG to PNG/JPG - there are odd characters and spacing problems Bug Public API changes: No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.2
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the February release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
this release contains significant improvements in text processing algorithms, namely in matching code units to glyphs, it is now possible to work with complex matching scenarios are common in non-Latin scripts.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-svg-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 22.1
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the January release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
we added support for matching fonts to individual runs of text, which provides for each character in the run a font family is chosen and a particular font face is selected containing a glyph for that character;</description></item></channel></rss>