<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 20.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 20.12.
Major Features There are 116 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved Arabic fonts rendering using Harfbuzz plugin. Added an ability to allow embedding of PostScript Fonts upon save documents. Implemented condition evaluation extension point. Provided an option to import styles from a dynamically inserted document for LINQ Reporting Engine. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-16895 Add feature to insert style separator using DOM New Feature WORDSNET-20552 LINQ Reporting Engine - Provide a way to import styles from a dynamically inserted document New Feature WORDSNET-18827 Add option to perform memory optimization while loading document New Feature WORDSNET-21432 Check Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 20.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 20.11.
Major Features There are 87 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Regular OSGI compatibility check&amp;amp;update is performed. JAI + non-Oracle JRE incompatibility is fixed. Document.SpellingChecked and Document.GrammarChecked properties were exposed publicly. Charts data points API was extended. Implemented basic support for rendering fonts with legacy Arabic encodings. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10130 Implement table row wrapping around floaters as MS Word 2013 does New Feature WORDSNET-16527 Incorrect RTL table row wrapping around a floater in 2013 mode New Feature WORDSNET-18416 DOCX to PDF conversion issue with table position Enhancement WORDSNET-20148 Table row does not break across pages Enhancement WORDSNET-20626 Converting DOC/DOCX to PDF - Page break issue Enhancement WORDSNET-21179 Saving requires a seekable stream Enhancement WORDSNET-14311 Font type is changed after converting Word to PDF Enhancement WORDSJAVA-2386 Different scales of the image watermark.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 20.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 20.10.
Major Features There are 101 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Tamil text can be rendered using the HarfBuzz plugin. Added support for loading CHM documents. Document.ExtractPages() feature was introduced. Implemented a new API for exporting specific pages to fixed page formats. Released the first version of SmartArt Cold Rendering. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-3110 Allow export of non-sequential pages to rendered formats New Feature WORDSNET-17788 Consider supporting the CHM format New Feature WORDSNET-11143 DOCX to HTML issue with smartArt rendering New Feature WORDSNET-19983 Improve text effects rendering in .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 20.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 20.9.
Major Features There are 86 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Culture/Locale tables are synchronized with Windows/.NET now. So, now we can read/write Windows-generated documents with &amp;ldquo;strange&amp;rdquo; Cultures: Pseudo, Invariant, de-De with Phone sort, Chinese with Bopomofo sort, etc. VbaReferenceCollection and related types are exposed publicly. Implemented support of footnotes upon loading PDF documents.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 20.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 20.8.
Major Features There are 93 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Multi-page TIFF rendering improved. Json engine improvements. Implemented Markdown ‘Inline Images’ feature. Added new font substitution rule for font name processing. Added flag indicating whether images must be skipped while loading PDF document. Implemented support for SVG images embedded using data URLs upon HTML import.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 20.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 20.7.
Major Features There are 97 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Explicitly set encoding Charset and BOM via TxtSaveOptions.setEncoding(Charset) Added new nodes to handle multi-section structured document tags. Added a new public property MailMerge.RetainFirstSectionStart. RevisionOptions class is extended with new properties. Improved performance of SmartArt cold rendering. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-2327 User option to explicitly set encoding Charset and BOM via TxtSaveOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 20.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 20.6.
Major Features Font.EmphasisMark is exposed to the public. Added a new public property ImportFormatOptions.IgnoreHeaderFooter. MarkdownSaveOptions class is introduced. Provided options to control JSON simple values’ recognition for LINQ Reporting Engine. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release WORDSNET-13983 Add feature to support &amp;lsquo;Emphasis Mark&amp;rsquo; font setting New Feature WORDSNET-19976 Font embedding works fine but the symbol is saved to PDF incorrectly New Feature WORDSNET-20513 Check how Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 20.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 20.5.
Major Features Provided ability to show/hide Grammatical and Spelling errors. New helper class to work with watermark inside document was introduced. Added feature to set the compression level for OOXML documents. Added resilience for the conversion of semi-broken MHTML files to PDF. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10403 Add feature to &amp;lsquo;Hide spelling errors in this document only&amp;rsquo; New Feature WORDSNET-4879 Add a helper method to insert a watermark into the header New Feature WORDSNET-10404 Add feature to &amp;lsquo;Hide grammar errors in this document only&amp;rsquo; New Feature WORDSNET-20094 Add an option to remove duplicate styles to Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 20.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 20.4.
Major Features OpenGL Rendering (using the external library) is supported on the Java platform now. The logging system is updated and improved. Sonarqube tests passed. Provided ability to change Asian paragraph spacing and indents. Added image interpolation option for PDF rendering (new public property PdfSaveOptions.InterpolateImages). Added a new mode 3D shapes rendering. Extended API of chart data labels and series.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 20.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 20.3.
Major Features FindReplaceOptions class is extended with new properties. Implemented the correct rendering of the &amp;ldquo;Letterlike&amp;rdquo; symbols. Supported dynamic stretching of an image within textbox bounds preserving the ratio of the image for the LINQ Reporting Engine. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-18362 LINQ Reporting Engine - Provide option to fit the image within textbox bounds while maintaining ratio New Feature WORDSNET-19568 Provide ability to set different attributes of Shape inside IFieldMergingCallback.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 20.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 20.2.
Major Features Performance and memory improvements due to NodeCollectionEnumerator algorithm optimization and loading of Blank Document optimization. IFieldUpdateCultureProvider is accessible from public API now. FieldOptions.setPreProcessCulture() is accessible from public API now. Added support of additional Java Charsets (Charsets that not exist in .NET). Background shape texture image is now rendered the same way as in print layout of MS Word with a 100% scale.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 20.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-java-20-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 20.1.
Major Features Implemented support of paragraph rules in footnotes. API to get/set the position of the floating table is exposed. Implemented an ability to check if VbaProject is signed. Added feature to insert IconCaption while using InsertOleObject. Supported dynamic bookmark insertion for LINQ Reporting Engine. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-2248 Investigate loading documents from PostgreSQL BlobInputStream.</description></item></channel></rss>