<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.12</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.12.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-48381 Extract and remove text based on subtype/form Feature PDFNET-55265 Implement PDF to Markdown conversion Feature PDFNET-55404 Implement OFD to PDF conversion Feature PDFNET-55323 Add &amp;ldquo;ChatGPT&amp;rdquo; plugin Feature PDFNET-56041 Add &amp;ldquo;Merger&amp;rdquo; plugin Feature PDFNET-50206 Positioning single-page documents side by side Enhancement PDFNET-52637 Font applying for text when Arabic and English are mixed Enhancement PDFNET-55868 Add the ability to convert PDF to TIF with a color depth of 24 bits per pixel (3 components, one byte each).</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.11</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-38031 Remove hidden text from PDF file Feature PDFNET-47791 Support for thread interruption Feature PDFNET-48151 Page Tree is flat after merging the files Feature PDFNET-44725 Reducing output file size after PDF to PDF/A conversion Enhancement PDFNET-49059 Grouping Checkboxes with the same name, but different Export Values Enhancement PDFNET-53159 Ignore or detect the hidden text in the PDF file Enhancement PDFNET-55890 PDF to ODS: Reducing output file size Enhancement PDFNET-44600 PDF to PDFA - Output file does pass compliance test Bug PDFNET-52215 Convert to PDF/A 3-b - the signature fields are removed Bug PDFNET-51876 Convert to PDF/A 3-b - the signature fields are removed Bug PDFNET-55675 Conversion of a particular PDF to PDFA-2A produces a non-compliant result Bug PDFNET-54007 ResizeContents method raises &amp;ldquo;Wrong format of page&amp;rsquo;s content&amp;rdquo; Bug PDFNET-47004 PDF to PDFA1A: Text cannot be mapped to Unicode Bug PDFNET-44161 Getting information on how much memory will be occupied when the document is converted Bug PDFNET-43487 Error &amp;ldquo;Page does not have Resources dictionary&amp;rdquo; in PDF/A conversion Bug PDFNET-55696 Incorrect page number for field after copying Bug PDFNET-55690 CheckBoxField.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.10</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.10.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-43784 Adding Type 7(Tensor) Shadings support Feature PDFNET-45292 Adding flatten transparency function Feature PDFNET-46395 Remove tags from tagged PDF Feature PDFNET-52882 Provide APIs to measure the character height Feature PDFNET-54566 Sign a PDF using a signed HASH Feature PDFNET-55017 Print Dialog Presets Page Scaling Feature PDFNET-52289 PDF to PDFA: Avoid Exception &amp;ldquo;Cannot access a disposed object&amp;rdquo; Enhancement PDFNET-53440 Improving conversion speed from PDF to HTML Enhancement PDFNET-55525 Update PdfViewer public API: replace System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.9</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.9.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-55157 Adding image with ImageFilterType.Flate does not preserve transparency Feature PDFNET-55270 Provide a way to remove a child annotation from a fillable field Feature PDFNET-44218 PDF/A-1b Conversion: Improve performance on some files Enhancement PDFNET-55385 Enhance CheckBoxField.AddOption method behavior Enhancement PDFNET-55343 Reduced file size after copying fillable fields from another document Enhancement PDFNET-45377 Enhance the behavior of Annotation.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.8</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.8.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-54615 Add Incremental Updates detection Feature PDFNET-55034 Provide a way to work with nested checkbox fields Feature PDFNET-52395 Add Aspose.PdfOrganizer Optimize API Feature PDFNET-51913 Extract Drawn Shapes from PDF document Enhancement PDFNET-53955 ResizeContents raises InvalidCastException Enhancement PDFNET-47472 Removing specific images from PDF using operators Enhancement PDFNET-48653 APS-to-PDF conversion and saving consume less and take less time Enhancement PDFNET-52641 Change XFA button conversion Enhancement PDFNET-52457 Difference between Page.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.7</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.7.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-51464 Copy OutputIntents from input PDF to destination PDF Feature PDFNET-46298 Add the shape extraction support Feature PDFNET-53628 Detect Overflow when adding text Feature PDFNET-45863 Saving to APS takes less time Enhancement PDFNET-49893 Memory consumption decreased while adding image to PDF Enhancement PDFNET-54323 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.6</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.6.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-54559 Aspose PdfConverter Html to PDF Feature PDFNET-52405 Aspose PdfOrganizer Resize API Feature PDFNET-52407 Aspose PdfOrganizer Compress API Feature PDFNET-54708 Aspose.PdfForm add feature &amp;lsquo;Export &amp;lsquo;Value&amp;rsquo;s from fields in document to CSV file&amp;rsquo; Feature PDFNET-54499 Aspose.PdfForm Add the ability to set properties for a separate fields Feature PDFNET-53357 Add the ability to set the title of the HTML, Epub page Feature PDFNET-39373 Removing Combobox options Enhancement PDFNET-53491 Provide an API for positioning vector graphics Enhancement PDFNET-51919 Bates stamps mismatch in the merged pdf file when using &amp;ldquo;LinkDuplcateStreams = true&amp;rdquo; Bug PDFNET-47174 Absorber.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.5</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.5.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-47704 Add RedactionAnnotation FontSize option Feature PDFNET-53220 Add support for Factur-X format for electronic Invoices Feature PDFNET-48527 Detect vector graphics inside PDF Feature PDFNET-49311 Extract table as single object if it is spanned over multiple pages Feature PDFNET-53209 Report generation crashes with ?</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.4</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.4.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-53492 Aspose.PDF for .NET 7 Feature PDFNET-49440 Aspose.Pdf 21.2: merged XPS file size decreased Enhancement PDFNET-37871 Setting Form field value improved Enhancement PDFNET-54025 Wrong symbols are extracted via TextFragmentAbsorber Bug PDFNET-53858 TextStamp isn&amp;rsquo;t added to landscape page in hr-HR locale Bug PDFNET-53764 Page.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.3.1</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-3-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-3-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.3.1
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-54012 Release plugins Aspose.PdfForm, Aspose.PdfConverter PDF to HTML, Aspose.PdfConverter PDF to XLSX, Aspose.PdfOrganizer Rotate, Aspose.PdfExtrator for Images Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Added APIs Type:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.ComboBoxFieldCreateOptions Method:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.ComboBoxFieldCreateOptions.#ctor(System.Int32,Aspose.Pdf.Rectangle) System.Void Property:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.ComboBoxFieldCreateOptions.Editable System.Nullable`1[[System.Boolean, mscorlib, Version=4.0.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=b77a5c561934e089]] Property:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.ComboBoxFieldCreateOptions.Options System.Collections.Generic.List`1[[System.String, mscorlib, Version=4.0.0.0, Culture=neutral, PublicKeyToken=b77a5c561934e089]] Property:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.3</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.3.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-34836 Get structure of TOC from PDF file Feature PDFNET-51871 Add resolution to image Feature PDFNET-49799 Aspose.PDF Flatten all the layers in resultant PDF Enhancement PDFNET-51851 PDF to PDFA: Image improved quality Enhancement PDFNET-53348 Merging PDF/UA results in non PDF/UA Bug PDFNET-52734 Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.2</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.2.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-53172 RAM consumption decreased while processing PDF Enhancement PDFNET-47808 Empty PNG image generated from PDF Bug PDFNET-53194 Text isn&amp;rsquo;t properly extracted from PDF by IPdfTypeExtractor Bug PDFNET-53165 PDF to JPEG: Paragraphs and images not rendered Bug PDFNET-43453 System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.1.1</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-1-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-1-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.1.1
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-52395 Add Aspose.PdfOrganizer plugin Feature PDFNET-52395 Add Aspose.PdfExtractor plugin Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Added APIs Method:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.PdfExtractorOptions.AddDataSource(Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.IDataSource) Type:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.DataType Field:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.DataType.File Field:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.DataType.Stream Type:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.FileDataSource Method:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.FileDataSource.#ctor(System.String) Property:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.FileDataSource.DataType Property:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.FileDataSource.Path Type:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.FileResult Property:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.FileResult.IsFile Property:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.FileResult.IsStream Property:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.FileResult.IsString Property:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.FileResult.Data Method:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.FileResult.ToFile Method:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.FileResult.ToStream Type:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.IDataSource Property:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.IDataSource.DataType Type:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.IOperationResult Property:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.IOperationResult.IsFile Property:Aspose.Pdf.Plugins.IOperationResult.IsStream Property:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.1</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-pdf-for-net-23-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 23.1.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-39205 Create PrinterMark annotation Feature PDFNET-48852 Detect if PDF file contains vector graphics Feature PDFNET-36137 Support Vector images extraction Feature PDFNET-53150 PDF to Excel conversion issue with number format Enhancement PDFNET-52604 HTML to PDF conversion throws System.</description></item></channel></rss>