<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 16.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-16-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-16-12-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 16.12 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODEJAVA-149 Reading problem of DataMatrix barcode Enhancement BARCODENET-36365 Improve recognition speed for Aztec Enhancement BARCODENET-36383 Improve recognition speed for Aztec by reducing the number of passes Enhancement BARCODENET-36380 Include CodablockF and Coupons in Silverlight control Enhancement BARCODENET-36387 Incorrect recognition of CodabloackF with AllSupportedTypes Enhancement BARCODENET-36398 Reading Barcode from a BMP image is generating exception Enhancement BARCODENET-36381 Remove line offset for CodablockF (GraphicsUnit.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 16.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-16-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-16-11-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 16.11 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36304 Add support of the new BarCode type: Codablock F New Feature BARCODENET-36340 Add support GS1 for CodablockF New Feature BARCODENET-36356 Add support of AI 8012 New Feature BARCODENET-36357 Add support of the classification of the encode types (symbologies) New Feature BARCODENET-36349 Add support of more than 64 types to the encoder API New Feature BARCODENET-36239 Implement saving to CMYK format New Feature BARCODENET-36240 Add support to read barcode in CMYK New Feature BARCODENET-33878 Slow recognition speed when reading QR codes from multi-page Tiff Enhancement BARCODENET-33909 Can&amp;rsquo;t recognize QR codes through free QR scanner apps available on the app store Enhancement BARCODENET-36344 Correct the bits in datamatrix recognition Enhancement BARCODENET-36234 Exception while trying to generate PDF417 barcode Enhancement BARCODENET-36348 PDF417 coded Barcode recognition is not working Enhancement BARCODENET-36347 Improve recognition rotated MicroQr barcodes Enhancement Usage examples: BARCODENET-36349 Add support of more than 64 Symbologies to the Encoder API</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 16.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-16-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-16-10-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 16.10 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36287 Support for GS1-128 AI 8102 Coupon Extended Barcode New Feature BARCODENET-36324 Support for UPCA &amp;amp; GS1 Databar coupon New Feature BARCODENET-36332 Set Wide Narrow Ratio for barcode symbology : Code128 New Feature BARCODENET-33941 Can&amp;rsquo;t recognize PDF417 code using the Motorola DS4208 scanner Enhancement BARCODENET-36336 Barcode generated using Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 8.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-8-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-8-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 8.1.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36297 Support to generate Code128C coded barcode New Feature BARCODENET-36259 Add new BarCode type: Aztec Runes New Feature BARCODENET-36262 Implement Aztec Runes generator New Feature BARCODENET-36288 Add checksum validation for OneCode and AustraliaPost New Feature BARCODENET-36266 Implement Aztec Runes decoder New Feature BARCODENET-36300 Dynabic.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 8.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-8-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-8-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 8.1.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-34430 Implement new algorithm for recognizing 3D-distorted Aztec codes New Feature BARCODENET-36252 Fake recognition of 2D barcodes with many errors Enhancement BARCODENET-36248 Improve recognition speed for Aztec Enhancement BARCODENET-36232 Databar Expanded barcode is generated incorrectly for the big lenght (21 or 22 symbols) Enhancement BARCODENET-36231 Add error correction for Mode Message in Aztec code Enhancement BARCODENET-36230 Correction of moot symbols in a DatabarExpanded barcode Enhancement BARCODENET-36229 Recognize a datamtrix with black dots around Enhancement BARCODENET-36228 Fix order of recognition results for Aztec Enhancement BARCODENET-36223 Unable to recognize the barcode from PDF Enhancement BARCODENET-36211 Recognize data matrix with a lot of errors because of low scanner resolution Enhancement BARCODENET-36195 Program hangs on Aztec code Enhancement BARCODENET-34304 QREncodeMode Enumeration is missing Binary enum Enhancement BARCODENET-34430 Implement new algorithm for recognizing 3D-distorted Aztec codes Code sample: BarCodeReader reader = new BarCodeReader(&amp;#34;AaBbCc_3D_2.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 8.0.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-8-0-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-8-0-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 8.0.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-34365 Add new BarCode type: DutchKix New Feature BARCODENET-34361 Add new BarCode type: DotCode New Feature BARCODENET-36213 Barcode not reconginzed if image is not rotated Enhancement BARCODENET-36212 Unable to Read the barcode from a PNG image having 100 multiple barcodes in it Enhancement BARCODENET-36210 BarCodeReader not detecting the barcodes with default settings Enhancement BARCODENET-36208 Support recognition of invasion in the quiet zone for data matrix Enhancement BARCODENET-36205 Incorrect 3D-distorted Aztec code recognition Enhancement BARCODENET-36201 Incorrect recognition of the Aztec code Enhancement BARCODENET-36196 Recognize poor quality code128 with histogram method Enhancement BARCODENET-36195 Program hangs on Aztec code Enhancement BARCODENET-36188 Can&amp;rsquo;t recognize 3D-distorted Aztec code from the JPG image Enhancement BARCODENET-36186 Several consecutive recognitions give different results Enhancement BARCODENET-34361 Add new BarCode type: DotCode Encoder code sample BarCodeBuilder builder = new BarCodeBuilder(@&amp;#34;!</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 7.9.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-7-9-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-7-9-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 7.9.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-34430 Implement new algorithm to recognize 3D-distorted Aztec codes New Feature BARCODENET-34421 Generate data matrix barcode with text on its right side New Feature BARCODENET-34433 Not able to recognize rectangular Aztec codes Enhancement BARCODENET-34422 Verify APTCACheck for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 7.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-7-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-7-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 7.8.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-34363 Add new BarCode type: Code32 New Feature BARCODENET-34368 Add new BarCode type: MICR (only reader) New Feature BARCODENET-34364 Add new BarCode type: Datalogic2of5 New Feature BARCODENET-34399 Add a manual hint &amp;ldquo;SkipRotatedBarcodes&amp;rdquo; New Feature BARCODENET-34415 Unable to recognize PDF417 barcode Enhancement BARCODENET-34411 System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 7.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-7-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-7-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 7.7.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-3426 Add MaxiCode implementation New Feature BARCODENET-34359 Can&amp;rsquo;t recognize Aztec code Enhancement BARCODENET-34352 Recognize 1d barcodes with a heterogeneous brightness Enhancement BARCODENET-34324 Unable to read barcode from image containing graphic in it, unless the graphic is removed from the file Enhancement BARCODENET-34223 Incorrect code and type returned by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 7.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-7-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-7-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>New Features
Key Summary Category BARCODENET-34345 Recognize datamatrix with decorated modules New Features BARCODENET-34315 Implement recognition of dot peen datamatrix (rotated) New Features BARCODENET-13003 Export / Import BarCode property to / from xml - file New Features BARCODENET-34337 Add generatorBase parameter to the ReedSolomon encoder/decoder. Enhancements BARCODENET-34332 Fake recognition of MicroPdf417 in picture with Code128 Enhancements BARCODENET-34328 Unable to recognize QR barcode from Pdf file .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 7.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-7-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-barcode-for-java-7-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 7.5.0 and we are pleased to announce it.
New Features BARCODENET-34310 Implement GS1 QR decoding Enhancements BARCODJAVA-33592 Implement getting readable type name from BarcodeReadType BARCODJAVA-33507 Can&amp;rsquo;t recognize Aztec code from the JPG image BARCODJAVA-33506 Can&amp;rsquo;t recognize Aztec code from the JPG image BARCODENET-34309 Reorganize the logic of recognition in manual hint mode to speed up the detection BARCODENET-33812 Add support to encode GS1QR code BARCODENET-34319 DataBarStackedOmniDirectional encoding, BarCodeBuilder.</description></item></channel></rss>