<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2013 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2013 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 13.12.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-12-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-12-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 13.12.0
Aspose.Words for Java has been updated to version 13.12.0 and we are pleased to announce this release brings the addition of 109 new useful improvements.
Using Aspose.Words for Java you can work with DOC, OOXML, RTF, HTML, OpenDocument, PDF, XPS, EPUB and other formats in your applications. You can also view, generate, modify, convert, render and print documents all without using Microsoft Word.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 13.10.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-10-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-10-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 13.10.0
Aspose.Words for Java 13.10 Release Notes What&amp;rsquo;s New There are 177 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:  Finally implemented a much richer support of CSS cascading and inheritance in HTML and MHTML imports Added support of table styles in HTML and MHTML imports Quirks and Standards modes are supported now in HTML import Improved import of CSS margins for paragraphs, lists and tables Base PDF/A-1b compliance level is implemented in rendering to PDF Improved floating shape positioning in complex scenarios Implemented vertical section alignment All Fixes Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-782 Specifying PdfImageCompression.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 13.9.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-9-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-9-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 13.9.0
Aspose.Words for Java 13.9 Release Notes What&amp;rsquo;s New There are 115 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:  Further features and improvements in DrawingML Charts rendering Textboxes rendering improvements &amp;ldquo;Zero-weight&amp;rdquo; files are now supported Various improvements in handling of MS Word formats All Fixes Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-742 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 13.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 13.8.0
Aspose.Words for Java 13.8 Release Notes What&amp;rsquo;s New There are 159 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:  Rendering to PostScript 3.0 is now supported Metafile rendering performance significantly improved EditableRange API introduced German ordinal/cardinal list label generation supported Improved tab width computation in marginal scenarios Improved table border rendering with conflicting or missing attributes For a list of changes to the public API in this release refer to the in the documentation.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 13.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 13.7.0
Aspose.Words for Java 13.7 Release Notes What&amp;rsquo;s New There are 142 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:  Rendering of table diagonal borders Document structure output into PDF/A-1a compliance Export of SDT controls as editable PDF form fields Improved text wrapping logic for section breaks EQ (mathematical) fields rendering implemented Added options for setting image resolution while rendering to PDF Fixed problem with incorrect font rendering for Korean language Supported theme overrides (OOXML) Improved format revision support (including styles) Several improvements in OLE support area For a list of changes to the public API in this release refer to the in the documentation.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 13.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 13.6.0
What&amp;rsquo;s New There are 142 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved algorithm of content width calculation inside table cells. More support for compatibility options in layout. Layout performance improvements. Decrease document size with Document.RemoveUnusedResources(). Theme fonts are used in calculation of Run.Font font names. Many HTML and MHTML import improvements. Material when rendering VML objects with 3D effects.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 13.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 13.5.0
Aspose.Words for Java 13.5 Release Notes What&amp;rsquo;s New There are 138 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Update of the INDEX field is supported by the field update engine. The HTML parser inside Aspose.Words now conforms to the HTML 5 Specification. New public Paragraph.GetEffectiveTabs() method now allows to get fully resolved tabstops.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 13.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 13.4.0
Aspose.Words for Java 13.4 Release Notes What&amp;rsquo;s New Printing to multitray printers improved Printing documents that contain pages with different orientation Improved memory performance for large documents (now code uses ~20% less memory for 1Gb+ documents) DOC and DOCX document can be signed with digital signatures, also signatures can be removed; 3D color for VML extrusion effect is supported Improved performance of PDF rendering of documents with Jpeg images DML Charts enhancements: surface charts rendering, moving average trend lines rendering and more Supported rendering of revisions Improved pagination of footnotes Implemented character paragraph indents Fixed positioning of a table broken across pages when it has repeated header rows Improved table row wrapping around floaters Fixed issue with Arabic-Indic numerals inside SDT Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 13.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 13.3.0
Aspose.Words for Java 13.3 Release Notes What&amp;rsquo;s New There are 110 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improvements in style handing in Tables, Format Revisions Improvements and resiliency code for ODT, RTF and DOCX DrawingML Charts 3D mode rendering implemented VML perspective shadows rendering implemented Outline rendering to PDF and XPS improved Multi-level bookmark rendering supported PDF rendering performance improved for documents with images Improved clipping of text boxes Fixed issue with missing footnotes in complex page layout For a list of changes to the public API in this release refer to the following article in the documentation.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 13.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 13.2.0
Aspose.Words for Java 13.2 Release Notes What&amp;rsquo;s New 3D effects are rendered for VML shapes. Shadows are rendered for VML shapes. PDF rendering performance is improved for documents with large JPEG images. DrawingML Charts rendering new features added. DIV elements in HTML are supported. Non-binary OLE objects are supported in ODT. Floating table breaking and positioning improved. Layout of RTL tables and paragraphs improved.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 13.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2013/aspose-words-for-java-13-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 13.1.0
Aspose.Words for .Java 13.1 Release Notes What&amp;rsquo;s New There are 120 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Extended public API for working with fields in the document. Added public API to find on which page a particular document element is laid out. Layout performance improved by at least 10%. Improvements to layout of nested objects and tables.</description></item></channel></rss>