<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.12.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50016 Add support to duplicate / clone a shape Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50677 Provide the single API to convert a Visio shape to PDF Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50678 Provide the single API to convert a Visio shape to HTML Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50762 The parsing error of the long attributes value occurred while generating a VDX diagram Bug DIAGRAMNET-51401 Output VSDX - the controls in Shapes do not work Bug DIAGRAMNET-51402 VSDX to image - an OLE object is not preserved Bug DIAGRAMNET-51406 VSD to image - the additional characters appear Bug DIAGRAMNET-51410 VSD to PDF - the page number remains 4 in all pages Bug DIAGRAMNET-51411 VSD to image - the page number remains 4 in all pages Bug DIAGRAMNET-51414 VSDX to PDF - missing the content of shapes Bug DIAGRAMNET-51415 VSDX to PDF - incorrect background color of the shapes Bug DIAGRAMNET-51416 VSDX to HTML - incorrect background color of the shapes Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-51386 VSDM to SVG - incorrect shading on bottom shapes Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51387 VSDM to SVG - shadow on shapes is being lost Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50762 The parsing error of the long attribute&amp;rsquo;s value occurred while generating a VDX diagram Bug DIAGRAMNET-50919 VSDX to PDF export - Shadows of Shapes are not being preserved properly Bug DIAGRAMNET-51370 VSD to VSDX - misplaced text items at the bottom Bug DIAGRAMNET-51376 VSDM to SVG - incorrect shading on header bar Bug DIAGRAMNET-51377 VSDM to SVG - incorrect shading on header bar Bug DIAGRAMNET-51378 VSDM to SVG - the background image is small and compressed Bug DIAGRAMNET-51379 VSDM to SVG - the background image is small and compressed Bug DIAGRAMNET-51381 VSD to PDF - formatting errors in the output PDF Bug DIAGRAMNET-51382 VSD to HTML - the header is missing in the output HTML Bug DIAGRAMNET-51383 A null reference error occurred on loading VSDX drawing Bug DIAGRAMNET-51384 Open and save routine of VSDX does not preserve a container text Bug DIAGRAMNET-51385 Open and save routine of VSDX removes tab property object Bug DIAGRAMNET-51391 VSD to PDF - cannot skip background pages Bug DIAGRAMNET-51392 VSD to image - cannot skip background pages Bug DIAGRAMNET-51394 VSDX to PNG - an argument exception occurred Bug DIAGRAMNET-51397 VSD to image - incorrect display of the shape Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.10.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-51349 Add support of converting a drawing to image same the area as a PDF Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51352 Accessing embedded files Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51085 The formulas are lost under the controls tab of Shapesheet on saving in VSDX Bug DIAGRAMNET-51094 Preserve default settings under the control tab on placing a Trapezoid shape Bug DIAGRAMNET-51355 VSDX to PDF - the text items are misplaced Bug DIAGRAMNET-51356 VSDX to HTML - the text items are misplaced Bug DIAGRAMNET-51357 Open and save routine of VSDX - missing date and edit date attributes of annotations Bug  DIAGRAMNET-51358 A null pointer error occurred on loading VSDX drawing Bug DIAGRAMNET-51359 Error in element author list after loading a VSDX Bug DIAGRAMNET-51361 VSDX to VDX - the incorrect text font of the shape Bug DIAGRAMNET-51363 Open and save routine of VSDX - Tabs section turns into a self-closed tag Bug DIAGRAMNET-51365 VSD to PNG - incorrect layout of the shapes Bug DIAGRAMNET-51367 VSD drawing import - an error in the element Master Bug DIAGRAMNET-51368 VSD to PNG - an overflow error occurred Bug DIAGRAMNET-51369 VSD to PDF - misplaced text items at the bottom Bug DIAGRAMNET-51371 VSDX to VSDX - additional text items are added Bug DIAGRAMNET-51373 Open and save routine of a VSDX drawing is missing an Asian text font Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.9.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-51261 Add support of converting the specific area of a drawing to image Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51350 Add support to retrieve shape by name Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51351 Add support of retrieving the shape from Annotation Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51295 VSDX to SVG - the low quality of output SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51309 DiagramException occurs on VSDX file saving Bug DIAGRAMNET-51331 VSDM to SVG - the text items are shifted up Bug DIAGRAMNET-51333 VSDM to SVG - incorrect rendering of the circular icons Bug DIAGRAMNET-51339 VSDX to SVG - the truncation of text from the right side of each image Bug DIAGRAMNET-51340 Incorrect comments order Bug  DIAGRAMNET-51342 Out of memory error after using the &amp;ldquo;AddComment&amp;rdquo; method and save file to steam Bug DIAGRAMNET-51344 VSDX to PDF - an argument out of range error occurred Bug DIAGRAMNET-51345 The comment is not deleted together with the shape Bug DIAGRAMNET-51346 VSDM to SVG - the logo quality is downgraded Bug DIAGRAMNET-51347 VSDM to SVG - the logo quality is downgraded Bug DIAGRAMNET-51353 Cannot add another comment in the Visio page Bug DIAGRAMNET-51354 Cannot edit comments in the Visio page Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.8.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-51295 VSDX to SVG - the low quality of output SVG. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51298 SVGSaveOptions - add support to control the level of bitmap compression. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51300 Add support of connecting shapes with connection index. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50577 VSDX to PDF conversion, the circular shape&amp;rsquo;s text is misplaced - I.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.7.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-51204 Printer paper size is changed after diagram saving. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51230 Incorrect values of page margins. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51274 Add support of inserting comments on the shape level. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51297 Input VDX - incorrect reading of SolutionXML. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51061 Missing shapes on converting a VST to PNG.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.6.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-51264 The shadow of shapes is black on converting a VSDM to SVG Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51270 Cannot see a shape of the VSDX in Visio Viewer Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51273 Incorrect display of shape in the Visio Viewer 2013 Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51249 The incorrect appearance of the curved line connecting in VSDM Bug DIAGRAMNET-51250 An additional left parenthesis is added in text on converting a VSD to PDF Bug DIAGRAMNET-51251 The size of the icon is downgraded on converting a VSDM to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51253 Incorrect color of text and borders in shapes when converting a VSDM to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51255 An image at the bottom has been squashed on converting a VSDM to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51258 Open and save routine of VSDM - the length of the walls is changed Bug DIAGRAMNET-51259 Open and save routine of VSDM - the length of the walls is changed Bug DIAGRAMNET-51260 Index out range error occurred on calling the layout method of Diagram class Bug DIAGRAMNET-51263 An additional red color tag appears on converting a VSDM to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51265 The font of title text is changed on converting a VSDM to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51266 The size of background image is reduced to converting a VSDM to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51267 An icon size is downgraded on converting a VSDM to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51268 Retrieves incorrect transparency value of an image from VSDM drawing Bug DIAGRAMNET-51269 Add virtualization protection Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.5.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-51104 Add support of shape&amp;rsquo;s 3D rotation properties New Feature DIAGRAMNET-51229 Open and save process of VSDM removes SolutionXMLs Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50283 VTX to HTML conversion, double line effect on shapes text items Bug DIAGRAMNET-51195 Incorrect rendering of an envelope icon on saving a VDX to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51196 Incorrect text alignment on saving a VDX to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51225 Retrieves an incorrect Calender value of the Shape data for VSDM Bug DIAGRAMNET-51226 Saving to HTML stream do not embed external resources Bug DIAGRAMNET-51227 Cannot set the TimeSaved value of a VSDM Bug DIAGRAMNET-51228 The text items are being displaced on setting shape data in VSDM Bug DIAGRAMNET-51234 Cannot remove and add a same named master in VSDM Bug DIAGRAMNET-51235 Open and save process of VSDM removes vbaProjectSignature.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.4.0.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50940 Improve setting the UIVisibility of Visio Page Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51188 Detecting format of VSDM, VSSM and VSTM files Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51214 Header/footer settings cannot be read from vsdx file Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51217 Cannot modify VBA Project in the VDX Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51218 Cannot retrieve Unique ID of a VSDX drawing Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51224 Retrieves an incorrect type value of the Shape data for VSDM Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51056 The connecting lines are not connected while creating a VDX Bug DIAGRAMNET-51165 The connectors in the VDX are not connecting shapes properly Bug DIAGRAMNET-51166 ObjectDisposedException is thrown when saving a diagram multiple times Bug DIAGRAMNET-51167 Shapes are missing in output VSDX Bug DIAGRAMNET-51168 The Font is not set for a shape Bug DIAGRAMNET-51169 Cannot retrieve from and to part of the connect of VDX Bug DIAGRAMNET-51170 Visio cannot open VSDX file when GIF image is added Bug DIAGRAMNET-51173 Does not preserve compound type of the connector shape in VSDX Bug DIAGRAMNET-51177 The arrow button is not being displayed correctly on converting a VSDM to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51178 A duplicated text line is over-written while converting a VSDM to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51180 Incorrect layout of connectors on saving in the VSDX format Bug DIAGRAMNET-51181 Incorrect layout of connectors on saving in the PDF format Bug DIAGRAMNET-51182 Missing shapes on converting a VSD to PDF Bug DIAGRAMNET-51183 Displaced shapes on converting a VSD to PDF Bug DIAGRAMNET-51187 VDX file is corrupted after saving - II Bug DIAGRAMNET-51191 Responsibility box at bottom of the shape is partially shaded on saving a VDX to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51192 The text phrases are not being spaced correctly on saving a VDX to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51193 An additional text appeared on saving a VDX to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51200 The text items are overlapping on saving a VSDM to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51202 ArgumentOutOfRangeException on diagram saving Bug DIAGRAMNET-51203 Images are missing in saving VSDX Bug DIAGRAMNET-51205 Displaced text and a missing character on converting a VSDM to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51206 Incorrect display at the bottom on converting a VSDM to SVG Bug DIAGRAMNET-51207 VDX file is corrupted after saving - I Bug DIAGRAMNET-51209 An error occurred on saving a drawing in PNG - I Bug DIAGRAMNET-51210 An error occurred on saving a drawing in PNG - II Bug DIAGRAMNET-51213 Cannot retrieve the accurate date and time value when the drawing was last saved Bug DIAGRAMNET-51215 A rectangle shape is being rendered on converting a VSD to JPG Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.3.0.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-51153 Diagram.AddShape method does not place shapes on the right positions. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51156 The blue cylinder shapes are missing on converting a VSD to PDF. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51158 Can&amp;rsquo;t add a hyperlink to a Shape in the VSDM. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51154 The text items are displaced slightly on converting a VSD to PDF.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.02.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-02-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-02-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.02.0.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50018 Added support of CLS compliant. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-51110 Integrated with Meter. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-51143 Ability to get the group of a given shape. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-51144 Ability to get the parent of a given shape. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-50149 VSD to PDF conversion, the background color shade of a group shape is getting changed.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.01 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-01-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-net-17-01-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 17.01.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50210 Save only the area of visible shapes not the whole page. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-50262 Export only selective Visio shapes to the SVG format. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-50195 VSD to PDF conversion, incorrect date format in the title shape. Bug DIAGRAMNET-50779 The background color of the tables is black on saving VSDX to PDF.</description></item></channel></rss>