<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 17.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-2572 Support for converting CMYK PSD to CMYK TIFF Feature IMAGINGNET-2636 Darker colors and color reproducibility Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2620 When PSD is converted to PNG, an ArgumentOutOfRangeException occurs Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2619 GIF not properly converted to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2618 Exception on saving Tiff Image Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2617 Fix PSD test rendering for specific case Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2614 Fix PSD crop operation Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2612 Exception on converting EMF to SVG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2610 Image saving failed when saving JPEG2000 as PNG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2597 OpenTypeInfoCacheProcessor.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 17.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-2457 Aspose.Imaging 17.6.0 : Managing resources while saving Metafile images as SVG Feature IMAGINGNET-2456 Saving SVG with fonts embedded or exported Feature IMAGINGNET-2439 Add possibility to force fonts cache update Feature IMAGINGNET-2396 Provide setting for replacing missing fonts Feature IMAGINGNET-2375 Add support for color replacement in PSD layers Feature IMAGINGNET-2043 Support for ODG (OpenDocument graphics) Feature IMAGINGNET-1842 Support for the combination of ColorType as Grayscale &amp;amp; CompressionType as Progressive for the JpegOptions class Feature IMAGINGNET-2569 PSD Conversion CMYK to RGB with alpha channel doesn&amp;rsquo;t work Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2546 Improperly computed TiffFrame.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 17.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-2439 Add possibility to force fonts cache update Feature IMAGINGNET-2376 Support for CMYK, YCCK color modes in JPEG Lossless. Feature IMAGINGNET-2143 Implementation of Lossy GIF Compressor  Feature IMAGINGNET-2473 When saving a tiff file with a different resolution the frames in the image are not displayed correctly Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2471 Improve performance of DNG partial processing Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2464 Examine and fix partial processing of JPEG 2000 format Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2461 Add support for PSD multiple fonts rendering and other possible style options within a single text layer Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2458 Fix exception when PSD text layer update is performed on previously saved PSD with updated text layer, using RemoveGlobalTextEngineResource option Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2453 Optimize algorithm FloydSteinbergDithering Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2446 Need investigate and support multiple fonts for text layers in PSD Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2443 Examine and fix partial PSD processing during export Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2442 Investigate performance of JPEG when partial processing Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2438 Different SVG image sizes when local and server build Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2436 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 17.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-7-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category MAGINGNET-2425 Need to support gray scale with alpha for PSD Feature IMAGINGNET-2347 Investigate and fix differences in Fonts in Adobe Photoshop and GDI+(Aspose.Imaging) rendering Feature IMAGINGNET-2429 Aspose.Imaging 17.6.0: Evaluation watermark appears when loading SVG document with VentureLicenser Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2381 Examine partial processing mechanism implemented in JPEG DCT loader Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2288 When PSD is saved as PNG, the output looks different Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2256 Image is recolored when using Graphics.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 17.6 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-6-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-2370 Aspose.Imaging SILVERLIGHT configuration decommission Breaking Change IMAGINGNET-2396 Provide setting for replacing missing fonts Feature IMAGINGNET-2343 Support for JPEG-LS with CMYK, YCCK color modes. Feature IMAGINGNET-2342 Support for 2-7 bits per sample in JPEG-LS images. Feature IMAGINGNET-2159 Support for JPEG-LS format Feature IMAGINGNET-2154 Support for Raster Image to SVG Conversion Feature IMAGINGNET-2363 Improve performance saving WMF to WMF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2354 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 17.4 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-4-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-1604 How to determine if the image is transparent or not Feature  IMAGINGNET-2290 EMF image is not converted Bug IMAGINGNET-2280 Stream is unexpectedly closed in multithreaded environment Bug IMAGINGNET-2255 FontSettings.addFontsFolder only loads TTF fonts Bug IMAGINGNET-2251 Saving of large PNG images leads to black resulting images Bug IMAGINGNET-2224 Buffer overflows in PNG for Compact Framework Bug IMAGINGNET-2214 Improve memory usage of DNG file format Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2211 Converting SVG to PNG image is not showing proper shapes in PNG file Bug IMAGINGNET-2150 Support for converting SVG to PDF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2148 Converting SVG to raster image (PNG in this case) file is showing blank resultant PNG file Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2140 Improve quality when resized Enhancement IMAGINGNET-1968 TIFF images with JPEG compression should support all possible bits per sample combinations Enhancement IMAGINGNET-1615 Implementation of rate control algorithm for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 17.03 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-03-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-03-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for .Net has been updated to version 17.03 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-2239 Improve loading DNG file format Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2221 Converting PSD to image is throwing exception Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2209 Modifying and updatding TIFF image stream is not working properly Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2203 Investigate problem with saving TIFF image frames in multithreading environment Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2153 Exporting JPEG image into BMP file format fails Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2146 Syncronize access to mutually exclusive image operations for JPEG images Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2142 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 17.01 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-01-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-net-17-01-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for .Net has been updated to version 17.01 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-2002 Unable to add layers to PSD file Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2132 Implement JPEG lossless decoder Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2206 Converting PSD layer to PNG have lager font size then a PNG saved through Photoshop natively .</description></item></channel></rss>