<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET 22.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-python-net-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-python-net-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This is the first version for Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET. This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET 22.12.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-42315 Support for crtx files - applying custom chart templates New Feature CELLSNET-47895 Images are distorted in Excel to PDF/HTML rendering Bug CELLSNET-47946 Image rotation effect is not displayed correctly in pdf/html Bug CELLSNET-47947 The rectangular box rotation effect in the graphics group is not displayed correctly in pdf/html Bug CELLSNET-52126 Some shapes are changed after converting Excel file to PDF Bug CELLSNET-52197 Boxes changed when converting XLSX document to PDF Bug CELLSNET-52330 Drawing shapes not rendered fine in HTML Bug CELLSNET-50042 The defined name is changed after re-saving Bug CELLSNET-52270 YEARFRAC Function is not calculated correctly Bug CELLSNET-52305 MMULT with OFFSET is not calculated correctly Bug CELLSNET-52307 Broken link formula returns 0 instead of #REF!</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET 22.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-python-net-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-python-net-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This is the first version for Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET. This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET 22.11.
Key Summary Category CELLSPYTHONNET-82 Re-saving an XLSM file having ActiveX controls corrupted the macros in the file Bug CELLSNET-52026 Support copying timeline New Feature CELLSNET-52022 Distinguish or differentiate between CSE legacy array formula and normal array formula Enhancement CELLSNET-52156 Disable merged table cells when saving XLSX to HTML Enhancement CELLSNET-52159 Support to parse collapsed property when converting html to excel Enhancement CELLSNET-51939 XLSX to PDF: Content misalignment Bug CELLSNET-51940 XLS to PDF: Content misalignment in cells Bug CELLSNET-52068 XLSX to PDF: Shapes missing/Layout collapse Bug CELLSNET-52092 Character printing and spacing in the figures of Excel is cut off Bug CELLSNET-52186 Shapes/boxes are empty when converting XLSX document to PDF Bug CELLSNET-52225 XLSX to PDF Characters in text boxes reversed Bug CELLSNET-52086 External connections corrupted in the generated file Bug CELLSNET-52133 Excel formulas are wrapped with curly braces in the re-saved xlsb file Bug CELLSNET-52158 Incorrect circular reference detection Bug CELLSNET-52174 Cell.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET 22.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-python-net-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-python-net-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This is the first version for Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET. This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET 22.10.
Key Summary Category CELLSPYTHONNET-79 Support MacOS version New Feature CELLSNET-42037 PivotTable Timeline Filter disappears after loading excel document and updating New Feature CELLSNET-51963 Support for CRTX files New Feature CELLSNET-51952 MAXIFS formulas take long time to be calculated Enhancement CELLSNET-52064 It&amp;rsquo;s not allowed to push non-empty cells off the end of the worksheet error when using Cells.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET 22.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-python-net-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-python-net-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This is the first version for Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET. This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET 22.9.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-51935 Support discrete group data for xls file New Feature CELLSNET-51925 Support preset gradient settings for gradient fill New Feature CELLSNET-51740 Support to set table formula for the datatable Enhancement CELLSNET-51853 Support to convert ozm to lbm for CONVERT function Enhancement CELLSNET-51931 Improve the recognization of user&amp;rsquo;s input for Style.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET 22.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-python-net-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-python-net-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This is the first version for Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET. This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET 22.8.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-51589 Support expand/collapse button style for PivotTable New Feature CELLSNET-51473 Convert threaded comments to html Enhancement CELLSNET-51570 Copy row height when processing smart markers of a table Enhancement CELLSNET-51590 Delete grouped shapes from group Enhancement CELLSNET-51595 Wrong vertical alignment of cell text on convert to PDF from Excel file with pivot table Bug CELLSNET-51621 Shared formulas were copied incorrectly for different file formats Bug CELLSNET-51524 Wrong word wrapping on converting to PDF from Excel file with pivot table Bug CELLSNET-51675 Shape is lost while converting to pdf Bug CELLSNET-51435 New worksheet relationships are added when converting an XLSB workbook to XLSM Bug CELLSNET-51545 Workbook with MS Excel 5.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET 22.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-python-net-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-python-net-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This is the first version for Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET. This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Python via .NET 22.7.
Key Summary Category CELLSPYTHONNET-55 File Formats and Conversions
- XLS, SpreadsheetML (XLSX, XML),XLSB, XLSM, DOCX, PPTX, JSON, Comma Separated Value (CSV), HTML, OpenDocument Spreadsheet (ODS), PDF, Tab Delimited, Plain Text (TXT) and popular image formats including TIFF, JPG, PNG, BMP, and SVG.</description></item></channel></rss>