<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 22.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.12.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1298 LookupPaths does not work when export GLB with input textures saved in zip file. Task THREEDNET-1293 Allow encode and decode directional/spot light Improvement THREEDNET-1294 Cylinder defined UV but no data Bug fixing THREEDNET-1295 Convert from DXF to GLTF/GLB Bug fixing THREEDNET-1296 FBX model couldn&amp;rsquo;t convert properly Bug fixing THREEDNET-1299 Added properties not accessible in other tools Bug fixing THREEDNET-1306 Cylinder with radius top =0 will generate incorrect model Bug fixing API changes There&amp;rsquo;re no API changes in this version.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 22.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1283 Implement binary maya import support New Feature THREEDNET-1276 Improve mesh quality when converting 3D-PDF to GLTF Improvement THREEDNET-1280 Restore the support of .NET 4.5 Improvement THREEDNET-1289 Materials lost when export to USDZ with only diffuse colors Bug fix API changes Added members to class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 22.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.10.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1241 Allow import Maya ASCII file New Feature API changes Added new type Aspose.ThreeD.Utilities.RotationOrder This is used in Aspose.ThreeD.Utilities.TransformBuilder
Added new methods to class Aspose.ThreeD.Utilities.TransformBuilder: /// &amp;lt;summary&amp;gt; /// Append rotation with specified order /// &amp;lt;/summary&amp;gt; /// &amp;lt;param name=&amp;#34;rot&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Rotation in degrees&amp;lt;/param&amp;gt; /// &amp;lt;param name=&amp;#34;order&amp;#34;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/param&amp;gt; public void RotateDegree(Vector3 rot, RotationOrder order) /// &amp;lt;summary&amp;gt; /// Append rotation with specified order /// &amp;lt;/summary&amp;gt; /// &amp;lt;param name=&amp;#34;rot&amp;#34;&amp;gt;Rotation in radian&amp;lt;/param&amp;gt; /// &amp;lt;param name=&amp;#34;order&amp;#34;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/param&amp;gt; public void RotateRadian(Vector3 rot, RotationOrder order) RotateDegree and RotateRadian allows compose a rotation matrix in specified order.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 22.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.9.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1232 Add internal temporary file system support for FBX importer Improvement THREEDNET-1111 GLTF export is not good Bug fixing THREEDNET-1215 When importing an OBJ file, one node can only read one material? Bug fixing THREEDNET-1216 Converting GLB to GLB loses textures Bug fixing THREEDNET-1225 Analyze issues found in App server - 2022 September Bug fixing THREEDNET-1227 Unsupported options in ASE files: MATERIAL_SOFTEN/PHYSIQUE/MATERIAL_SHINE Bug fixing THREEDNET-1228 Exception when importing JT files: An item with the same key has already been added Bug fixing THREEDNET-1230 STL files with quad face is not supported.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 22.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.8.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1175 Fix release package file issues. Task THREEDNET-1183 Fix default installation directory of MSI package Task THREEDNET-1176 Node with geometry translation cannot be handled properly in USDZ exporter. Bug fixing THREEDNET-1179 Aspose.3D 22.5: Exception when trying to load Vrml file Bug fixing THREEDNET-1181 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 22.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.7.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1169 Add support of .NET 6.0 New Feature THREEDNET-1166 Switch to USDZ as HTML5&amp;rsquo;s default internal format New Feature API changes The old A3DW format was used as HTML5&amp;rsquo;s internal format, now it&amp;rsquo;s obsoleted and replaced by the USDZ, which can provide more features and extensibility.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 22.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.6.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1152 Allow save 3D scene without specify the file format New Feature THREEDNET-1157 SdfValueBlock is not supported in USDZ import Improvement THREEDNET-1156 GLF Exception: Failed to import glTF, byteOffset is not defined in accessor Bug fix THREEDNET-1154 Aspose.ThreeD.ExportException: Spec duplicated while DAE to USDZ conversion Bug fix THREEDNET-1153 Exception occurs while saving USDZ to GLTF Bug fix API changes Added new method to class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 22.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.5.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1149 Mesh triangulate does not support VertexElementUserData with mapping mode Polygon/PolygonVertex New Feature THREEDNET-1148 Add support of VertexElementUserData in TriMesh New Feature THREEDNET-1138 Allow export VertexElementUserData to glTF New Feature THREEDNET-1119 Support for GLTF Custom Vertex Attributes New Feature API changes Updated the property type from Dictionary&amp;lt;String, Object&amp;gt; to object in class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 22.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.4.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1116 Node’s EulerAngle confusion leads to wrong position after model rotation Bug fix THREEDNET-1137 LayeredTexture imported from FBX may generate invalid GLTF file Bug fix THREEDNET-1119 Support for GLTF Custom Vertex Attributes New Feature THREEDNET-1129 GLB to U3D Conversion resulted in wrong orientation New Feature THREEDNET-1121 Point cloud export support in USD/USDZ New Feature THREEDNET-1122 Point cloud import support in USD/USDZ New Feature THREEDNET-1113 Loaded OBJ model lost texture coordinates vt Bug fix THREEDNET-1107 The license cannot be loaded when the application is built as a single executable.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 22.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.3.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1103 Improve large mesh into U3D/PDF file exporting Improvement THREEDNET-1081 Add simplified functions for merging scenes Improvement THREEDNET-1077 Generated glTF cannot pass glTF validator when draco compression enabled. Bug fix API changes Added new static methods to class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 22.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.2.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1054 Allow embed textures in U3D and PDF file New feature THREEDNET-1058 Primitives cannot bind to material in USD exporter/importer Bug fix THREEDNET-1051 Allow access extras and extensions in GLTF file Improvement THREEDNET-1048 Allow encode scene and node&amp;rsquo;s meta data to usd New feature THREEDNET-1049 Allow decode scene and node&amp;rsquo;s meta data from usd New feature API changes Added members to class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 22.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.1.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1017 Restored the support of netstandard2.0 Task THREEDNET-1016 Failed to open usdz files to convert to glb Bug fix THREEDNET-1018 Odd FBX issue causing Mesh to disappear Bug fix THREEDNET-1020 Add primitive entities encoding support in USD exporter New feature THREEDNET-1021 Add primitive entities decoding support in USD exporter New feature THREEDNET-1023 String handling was incorrect in USD importer/exporter Bug fix THREEDNET-1022 USD file with customData cannot be opened Bug fix THREEDNET-1040 Multiple objects with manually assigned object id may cause export to FBX failed Bug fix API changes In the 22.</description></item></channel></rss>