<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.OCR for Java 17.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-ocr-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-ocr-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.OCR for Java has been updated to version 17.11 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.OCR.
Key Summary Category OCRNET-3321 Binary Classificator providing better OCR quality. Enhancement OCRNET-3383 New Neural Network Player (NNNPlayer) providing better OCR performance. Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Removed APIs All OMR-related APIs removed from Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for Java 17.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-ocr-for-java-17-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-ocr-for-java-17-6-release-notes/</guid><description>
Aspose.OCR for Java has been updated to version 17.6 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.OCR.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category OCRNET-3259 hOCR for creation of the searchable PDF Enhancement OCRNET-3260 Improved logic to set the spaces between the words Enhancement OCRNET-3261 Clusterizator to reduce the number of calls to OCR and use the average images for OCR Enhancement OCRNET-3262 Outlines and clustering splitters to separate touching letters Enhancement OCRNET-3263 Words list for verification Enhancement</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for Java 17.03 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-ocr-for-java-17-03-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-ocr-for-java-17-03-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.OCR for Java has been updated to version 17.03 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.OCR.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category OCRNET-3157 Update Dynabic.Metered with recent changes Enhancement OCRNET-3082 Skew correction improvement with better EigenPoints selection and grouping Enhancement</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for Java 17.02 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-ocr-for-java-17-02-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-ocr-for-java-17-02-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.02
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category OCRNET-3010 Incorrect line splitter behaviour processing lines with &amp;lsquo;i&amp;rsquo; letter Enhancement OCRNET-3005 Replace Gauss filter implementation with improved one Enhancement OCRNET-1380 Implement substitution for BigSmallCharCorrector Enhancement OCRNET-3095 Exception within sort rectangles during layout detection Enhancement</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for Java 17.01 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-ocr-for-java-17-01-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-ocr-for-java-17-01-release-notes/</guid><description> Key Summary Category OCRNET-1132 Rotation algorithm ruins image Enhancement OCRNET-1122 Autorotation is not working as expected Enhancement OCRNET-2984 OmrEngine.RotateImage throws Exception Enhancement</description></item></channel></rss>