<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.12.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46479 Tab name not available when single sheet workbook is converted to HTML New Feature CELLSNET-46503 Control loading of VBA data using LoadDataFilterOptions New Feature CELLSNET-42414 Tracked Changes lost during conversion from XLSB to XLSM and XLS to XLSM Enhancement CELLSNET-46090 Text moved a little bit after ungrouping the shape when saving an XLS to XLSX Enhancement CELLSNET-46439 Optimization for memory performance: release original stream after loading Workbook Performance CELLSNET-46371 Gridlines not displayed in some sheets while converting XLSX-&amp;gt;HTML-&amp;gt;XLSX Bug CELLSNET-46447 Formattings lost in HTML to XLS rendering Bug CELLSNET-46494 MHT to XLSX conversion - cell content problem Bug CELLSNET-46468 MS Excel prompts an error when opening the output file Bug CELLSNET-46487 Non-English locale formula not working Bug CELLSNET-46489 Deleting a row with an index and reading the row with the same index returns Cell.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.11.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46377 Check if a cell has circular formula New Feature  CELLSNET-46399 Exception occurred while calling PivotTable.RefreshData() New Feature  CELLSNET-46394 Fetch Pivot Table refresh date similar to Interop.Excel New Feature  CELLSNET-46261 Replacement of the texts in SmartArt doesn&amp;rsquo;t work New Feature  CELLSNET-46435 GetValidationValue returns wrong value for large numbers Enhancement  CELLSNET-46117 Text position changes a bit on ungrouping the shape Enhancement  CELLSNET-46400 It hangs while calling PivotTable.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.10.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46311 Get connection points from shapes New Feature  CELLSNET-46194 Change columns&amp;rsquo; fixed size width (i.e., pt/px) into scalable unit like &amp;ldquo;em&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;percent&amp;rdquo; Enhancement  CELLSNET-46383 Issue with the image source when rendering Excel to HTML file format Bug  CELLSNET-46367 Font size changed from 6.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.9.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-42992 Applying text alignment to partial text inside the TextBox New Feature  CELLSNET-46308 Export custom document properties to PDF  New Feature  CELLSNET-46301 Get XML path from List Object/Table New Feature  CELLSNET-46315 Support stock chart in ODS file  New Feature  CELLSNET-46304 Add Row.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.8.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-42992 Apply text alignment to partial text inside the TextBox New Feature  CELLSNET-44155 Read/write connections of XLSB file  New Feature  CELLSNET-46123 Support parsing formulas of revision logs to binary array  New Feature  CELLSNET-46220 Set ContentCopyForAccessibility option while converting spreadsheet to PDF file format  New Feature  CELLSNET-43560 Encrypt an ODS file New Feature  CELLSNET-43556 Open encrypted ODS file New Feature  CELLSNET-46209 Support reading and writing DConn of XLS file  New Feature  CELLSNET-43326 Add overloads to CopyRows and CopyColumns with Paste Special options New Feature  CELLSNET-41637 Retrieve Subtotaling settings New Feature  CELLSNET-46252 Argument to skip row/rows as data headers in exporting range to datatable Enhancement  CELLSNET-46226 Ink Annotations become regular images after conversion Enhancement  CELLSNET-41693 Auto-fit columns improvement is included Enhancement  CELLSNET-46263 Application hangs while converting XLS to PDF Performance CELLSNET-46262 Cell background is wrong when cell text orientation is inclined in the output PDF  Bug  CELLSNET-44761 Text in a shape has not rendered correctly in PDF Bug  CELLSNET-43916 Shape shadow is missing while converting spreadsheet to HTML  Bug  CELLSNET-46251 Application hangs while converting XLSX to HTML Bug  CELLSNET-46241 Problem with multilines in HTML Bug  CELLSNET-46219 Width from HTML tag is not followed while converting HTML to XLSX Bug  CELLSNET-46280 Exception raised while importing data into Excel file with SmartMarkers  Bug  CELLSNET-46267 Issue with data filtering top rows Bug  CELLSNET-46264 R1C1Formula property has changed its behavior Bug  CELLSNET-46258 Issue calculating reverse VLOOKUP array formula Bug  CELLSNET-46197 Data validation issue - if inserting wrong value and clicking other cell does not automatically restore validation cell to its previous value Bug  CELLSNET-46276 Excel to PDF conversion - an empty page is added Bug  CELLSNET-46275 Large PDF created from XLS Bug  CELLSNET-46259 Converting Excel to PDF adds straight line Bug  CELLSNET-46255 Page number issue (in the footer) in Excel to PDF rendering Bug  CELLSNET-46238 Encrypted ODS file loading failed Bug  CELLSNET-46231 Text in column A cells is not rendered properly in the output PDF Bug  CELLSNET-46165 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.7.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46046 Round images become square images in the output PDF  New Feature  CELLSNET-43538 Support Pivot Table Slicers New Feature  CELLSNET-41946 Handle slicers and Pivot table New Feature  CELLSNET-46163 Support encrypting and decrypting ODS file  New Feature  CELLSNET-46186 Using List or List as DataSource for importing data into worksheet New Feature  CELLSNET-46185 Add WorkbookSettings.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.6.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46159 Render Slicer shape to image format  New Feature  CELLSNET-46179 Update Slicer in XLSB and XLSX file formats New Feature  CELLSNET-46167 Create Slicer in XLSB and XLSX file formats  New Feature  CELLSNET-44455 Create or update Slicer in Excel 2013 using Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.5.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46095 Implement function CEILING.PRECISE New Feature  CELLSNET-46023 Support Strict Open XML Spreadsheet format New Feature  CELLSNET-46080 The color of the image should be black when converting to PDF  Enhancement  CELLSNET-46087 Page Setup PrintErrorType not working in Excel to PDF rendering Enhancement  CELLSNET-46084 PageSetup.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.4.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46045 Set Pdf Page size while using Chart.ToPdf method New Feature  CELLSNET-45590 Support rendering Histogram MS Excel 2016 Chart New Feature  CELLSNET-46007 Add an equivalent property to the &amp;ldquo;FilterMode&amp;rdquo; property of MS Excel Worksheet object (VBA) New Feature  CELLSNET-46026 Support additional cells modification in cellModifiedOnAjax - Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.3.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-42655 Group pivot fields in the Pivot Table  New Feature  CELLSNET-45960 Change the dot from NumPad to decimal separator (&amp;rsquo;,&amp;rsquo;) - Aspose.Cells.GridWeb New Feature  CELLSNET-45966 Cause of exception during backward HTML-to-Cells conversion Enhancement  CELLSNET-45976 Error opening ODS file due to possibly different frameworks keep different precision for float values Enhancement  CELLSNET-45981 Add property to the StyleFlag to be set to false to not override the QuotePrefix value Enhancement  CELLSNET-45957 Support keeping the map chart in the template file  Enhancement  CELLSNET-45941 ActiveX control becomes picture when copying sheet from one workbook to another workbook Enhancement  CELLSNET-45928 Data validation - GridWeb should display a dialog with an error message Enhancement  CELLSNET-45935 Workbook.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.2.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-45889 Convert cell content to Hyperlink - ImportTableOptions.IsFormulas option  New Feature  CELLSNET-45886 Set comment&amp;rsquo;s margins New Feature  CELLSNET-45855 Provide WorkbookSetting.StreamProvider to control external resources New Feature  CELLSNET-45845 Unsupported external stylesheet during round trip conversion Enhancement  CELLSNET-45888 DDE link is not present inside Worksheets.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-net-18-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 18.1.
Major News Xamarin
Aspose.Cells for for .NET now also includes Aspose.Cells for iOS via Xamarin and Aspose.Cells for Android via Xamarin assemblies with its regular .NET Dlls.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-45740 Find the children Pivot Tables of parent Parent Pivot Table New Feature  CELLSNET-45771 Handle automatic axis units like Microsoft Excel New Feature  CELLSNET-45668 Read and write tableSingleCells of XLSB file  New Feature  CELLSNET-45830 Add events after deleting rows and columns in Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>