<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 19.12
Supported Platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1822 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 19.12 features Feature SLIDESNET-41274 Add color to Data Points Feature SLIDESNET-41487 Restrict printing in PDF file Feature SLIDESNET-41510 PDF access permissions Feature SLIDESNET-38950 ODP to PDF: Bullets numbering is missing Enhancement SLIDESNET-41184 Slides are not placed into proper sections Enhancement SLIDESCPP-2140 Add support for the CodePorting.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes forAspose.Slides for C++ 19.11
Supported Platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++) Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang) Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1821 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 19.11 features Feature SLIDESNET-39130 Improve handling of embedded OLE objects in Presentation Feature SLIDESNET-41401 Text get overlapped in generated shape thumbnail Enhancement SLIDESNET-41340 Chart become image on cloning shape Enhancement Public API Changes Obsolete methods AddFromSvg() have been deleted Methods System::SharedPtr AddFromSvg(System::String svgContent) and</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.10
Supported Platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++) Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang) Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1820 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 19.10 features Feature SLIDESNET-40689 Support for accessing prompt text from slides shapes placeholders Feature SLIDESNET-41393 After conversion to PDF/A an image is rendered with blur Enhancement SLIDESCPP-2086 Improve thumbnails rendering quality Enhancement Public API Changes Equals() and GetHashCode() methods have been overridden for Aspose::Slides::Effects classes Equals() and GetHashCode() methods have been overridden for Aspose::Slides::Effects classes, now objects of these classes are compared by their semantic value.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.9
Supported Platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1819 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 19.9 features Feature SLIDESCPP-2009 Decryption of encrypted ODP and OTP presentation formats Feature Public API Changes IsLicensed() method declared as deprecated for ILicense interface and License class ILicense::IsLicensed() and License::IsLicensed() methods declared as deprecated.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.8
Supported Platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1818 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 19.8 features Feature SLIDESNET-36682 Hiding master shapes from slide Feature SLIDESNET-34498 Property for setting layout mode of chart plot area Feature SLIDESNET-41048 Embedding HTML and ZIP files Feature SLIDESNET-35054 Implement Chart_Chart2007.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.7
Supported Platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1817 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 19.7 features Feature SLIDESNET-34685 Default automatic Markers symbols for LineWithMarkers chart Feature SLIDESNET-36453 Support API for animation effects on paragraph level editing Feature SLIDESNET-33742 Setting Font related properties for Chart Area Feature SLIDESNET-35440 Support for clearing the particular chart series datapoint data only in chart data worksheet Feature SLIDESNET-33910 Setting Font related properties for chart entities at one place Feature SLIDESNET-40010 Setter for ExternalWorkbookPath of ExternalWorkbook in charts Feature SLIDESNET-41166 PowerPoint has page numbers that increment even when its just a continuation of that slides notes Enhancement SLIDESNET-41215 OLE embedded objects support for OpenDocument Enhancement SLIDESNET-41185 Poor Quality When converting PPTX to PdfNotes Enhancement SLIDESNET-35712 Enabling and disabling the chart series values Enhancement SLIDESCPP-1922 Improve the processing of culture-dependent information Enhancement SLIDESCPP-1877 Improve thumbnails rendering quality (v19.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.6
Supported Platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1816 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 19.6 features Feature SLIDESCPP-41142 Support for setting lock Aspect Ratio for text box Feature SLIDESNET-41092 IColorFormat.Color doesn’t return effective color Feature SLIDESNET-34681 Support for progress in percentage for PDF conversion Feature SLIDESCPP-41101 Implement a progress in percentage for PDF conversion Feature SLIDESCPP-40958 Option for making every page self-sufficient when saving presentation as HTML Feature SLIDESNET-16733 Fusion Charts support in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.5
Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1787 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 19.5 features Feature SLIDESCPP-1830 Improve thumbnails rendering quality (v19.5) Feature SLIDESNET-40727 Support for Convert SVG images to shapes Feature SLIDESNET-40870 Support for comments replies in Aspose.Slides Feature SLIDESNET-41059 Resolved Aspose.Slides for .NET: Rasterization or vectorization of Shapes without text Feature SLIDESCPP-40730 Support for Office 365 in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.4
Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1746 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 19.4 features Feature SLIDESNET-41018 Supporting of external Excel workbooks Feature SLIDESNET-40897 Support for OpenDocument encryption Feature SLIDESNET-40917 The rendition to PDF format occupies too much RAM memory Enhancement SLIDESNET-40938 PDF text is not searchable when exported to PDF with Notes Enhancement SLIDESCPP-1788 Improve thumbnails rendering quality Enhancement SLIDESCPP-1789 Improve Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.3
Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1720 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 19.3 features Feature SLIDESNET-40600 Support for Text Highlighter feature Feature SLIDESNET-40794 Support for setting Transparency property for shadow effects Feature SLIDESNET-40799 Restricting local file system access when opening a document Feature SLIDESNET-40925 Add encoding meta tag when saving into HTML Enhancement SLIDESNET-40612 Setting for removing width and height attributes of SVG tag when saving as HTML Enhancement SLIDESCPP-1614 Improve EMF/WMF rasterization quality Enhancement Public API Changes get_ColorSource() and set_ColorSource() methods have been added to IHyperlink class New get_ColorSource() and set_ColorSource() methods have been added to IHyperlink and Hyperlink classes.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.2
Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1441 Implement Multi-page Tiff format support Feature SLIDESCPP-1615 Improve thumbnails rendering quality (v19.2) Feature SLIDESCPP-1705 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 19.2 features Feature SLIDESNET-40633 Support for Morph Transition feature Feature SLIDESNET-40783 Support for setting Transparency property for shadow effects Feature Public API Changes MorphTransition and IMorphTransition classes have been added Aspose::Slides::SlideShow::MorphTransition and Aspose::Slides::SlideShow::IMorphTransition classes have been added.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 19.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-cpp-19-1-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1647 Improve thumbnails rendering quality (v19.1) Feature SLIDESCPP-1669 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 19.1 features Feature Public API Changes get_AlternativeTextTitle() and set_AlternativeTextTitle() methods have been added to IShape class New get_AlternativeTextTitle() and set_AlternativeTextTitle() methods have been added to IShape and Shape classes.
These methods allow to get or set the title of alternative text associated with a shape.</description></item></channel></rss>