<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Android via Java 18.12</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.BarCode for Android via Java 18.12.
All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODENET-37024 Not able to read dotted barcodes from TIFF images  Bug BARCODEJAVA-623 Exception occurs for tests related to xml serialization  Bug BARCODEJAVA-625 Unable to Read Complete BarCode Text Bug Usage examples: BARCODENET-37024 - Not able to read dotted barcodes from TIFF images</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Android via Java 18.11</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.BarCode for Android via Java 18.11.
New Features Bring enums names into line with Java naming conventions Add new barcode subsets to DecodeType Not able to detect the barcode Improve the recognition of a 3D-distorted and rotated 2D-barcodes Improve the recognition of a 3D-distorted QR code Add minor fixes to BarCodeReader GS1 DataBar Expanded Stacked barcode did not pass GS1 Canda barcode verification All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODEJAVA-607 Bring enums names into line with Java naming conventions New Feature BARCODENET-37019 Add new barcode subsets to DecodeType New Feature BARCODENET-36945 Not able to detect the barcode New Feature BARCODENET-34367 Improve the recognition of a 3D-distorted and rotated 2D-barcodes New Feature BARCODENET-36389 Improve the recognition of a 3D-distorted QR code New Feature BARCODENET-37020 Add minor fixes to BarCodeReader New Feature BARCODEJAVA-555 GS1 DataBar Expanded Stacked barcode did not pass GS1 Canda barcode verification New Feature BARCODENET-37010 Barcode CODE39 reading problem Bug BARCODENET-37000 Barcode Detection does not constrain to the defined region.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Android via Java 18.10.1</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-10-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-10-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.BarCode for Android via Java 18.10.1.
All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODENET-37001 Using the same instance of BarcodeReader throws exceptions. Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Android via Java 18.10</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Barcode for Android via Java 18.10.
New Features Investigate new architecture of barcodes recognition filters. Implement UpcaGs1Code128Coupon for new barcode generation API. Implementation to read all barcodes from TIFF images. Deprecate BarCodeBuilder. All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36713 Investigate new architecture of barcodes recognition filters. New Feature BARCODENET-36940 Implement UpcaGs1Code128Coupon for new barcode generation API.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Android via Java 18.8</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Barcode for Android via Java 18.8.
New Features Added support of following file formats: BMP, GIF, WebP. All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36872 List or chart of prerequisites required to generate successful barcode image of any barcode type  New Feature BARCODENET-36941 Implement UpcaGs1DatabarCoupon for new barcode generation API  New Feature BARCODENET-36930 Implement Interpolation AutoSize mode  New Feature BARCODENET-36923 Implement MaxiCode for new barcode generation API  New Feature BARCODENET-36922 Implement DotCode for new barcode generation API New Feature BARCODENET-36942 Incorrect draw Code16K barcode, without above and below borders  Bug BARCODENET-36952 GS1 Datamatrix barcode is not wrapping the text in case of CodeLocation.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Android via Java 18.7</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Barcode for Android via Java 18.7.
New Features New BarCode generation API with improved functionality. All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36791 Preview version of new BarCode Generation API New Feature BARCODENET-36215 Unable to Read the DatabarExpandedStacked barcode from a PNG image Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Android via Java 18.6</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-android-via-java-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Android via Java 18.6 has been launched. It is a barcode generation and identification component for Android developers. Aspose.BarCode for Android via Java has been developed on the strong foundations of its Aspose.BarCode for Java ancestor which is a very strong API for creating and reading barcode images of different formats.
General Barcode Features Specify different types of barcode. Control appearance of text (data to be encoded to barcode image) on barcode Customize the bars in the barcode.</description></item></channel></rss>