<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.12
Key Summary Category CADNET-8467 setDrawColor Still not working Enhancement CADNET-8444 Read name CadInsertObject corresponding to AutoCAD notation Enhancement CADNET-8382 The result EMF image looks as empty. Enhancement CADNET-8377 FBX failed to export to WEBP, DICOM, EMF and hang on export to BMP Enhancement CADNET-8354 Implement merging of MText and Xrrecord&amp;rsquo;s texts and review test results Enhancement CADNET-8344 Dashed line exported wrong as continuous in rotated images Enhancement CADNET-8356 DWG image is not rendering all elements in PDF conversion Enhancement CADNET-8351 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Index was outside the bounds of the array.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.11
Key Summary Category CADNET-8346 new ACI changes and IsViewTop changes Enhancement CADNET-8303 Fix on multi-thread export of Region entity Enhancement CADNET-8298 PCL raster data is not exported. Enhancement CADNET-8271 Render and placement issue of composite glyphs Enhancement CADNET-8258 Issue with VPORT creation and validation of coordinate preservation Enhancement CADNET-8083 Unify entities access API for all formats Enhancement CADNET-8341 Regression: Filling of 4-sided SOLID entities Enhancement CADNET-8335 Solid not filled on left view Enhancement CADNET-8330 Polyline not converted from DXF Enhancement CADNET-8322 UpdateSize produces wrong size for specific DWG document Enhancement CADNET-8284 Autocad Rendering Issue Enhancement CADNET-8261 Missing Text block after conversion from DWG file Enhancement CADNET-8241 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Cannot process loading further due to incorrect file format structure.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.10 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.10
Key Summary Category CADNET-8299 Implement Width and Height for FBX Enhancement CADNET-8282 Export from DGN/DWF to DWF failed Enhancement CADNET-8160 Implement aps element to render 3d scenes Enhancement CADNET-8159 Implement Exporter to fbx (ascii) Enhancement CADNET-8142 Implement vertical alignment, proper tab size and codepage support for MTEXT.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.9
Key Summary Category CADNET-8285 Export from FBX failed Enhancement CADNET-8283 Export from DWG to OBJ failed Enhancement CADNET-8223 DWG to OBJ conversion hang Enhancement CADNET-8220 Implement aps element to render 3d scenes Enhancement CADNET-8204 Improve PCL exporter Enhancement CADNET-8184 Parse specific color storage for DWG Enhancement CADNET-8179 Implement Exporter to fbx (ascii) Enhancement CADNET-8175 Implement justifications processing for MTEXT and item placement.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.8
Key Summary Category CADNET-8196 Export result disappears because of new viewport border change Enhancement CADNET-8191 Implement Exporter to fbx (ascii) Enhancement CADNET-8165 Support ObserverPoint functionality on Iges file format rendering Enhancement CADNET-8127 Support dcm, emf, webp output formats Enhancement CADNET-8108 Investigate and implement proper tab behaviour for MTEXT Enhancement CADNET-8042 Parse spline parametrization flag for DWG 2013 Enhancement CADNET-8219 Blank Image is rendered on exporting DWG to image Enhancement CADNET-8211 Extra lines in exported SVG Enhancement CADNET-8176 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.7
Key Summary Category CADNET-8235 Converting DWG to PNG the process hangs Enhancement CADNET-8232 ImageLoadException on loading IGES file Enhancement CADNET-8172 DWG file to PDF: How to center the drawing in the DWG into the PDF and display it in proportion Enhancement CADNET-8158 Implement FBX ascii reader Enhancement CADNET-8152 Rework MTEXT rendering Enhancement CADNET-8140 Implement FBX format support Enhancement CADNET-8131 Implement webp export Enhancement CADNET-8129 Implement dcm export Enhancement CADNET-8112 Obj file rendering fix Enhancement CADNET-8109 Implement extraction of camera parameters from camera matrix Enhancement CADNET-8056 Watermark export option Enhancement CADNET-1316 Add PCL5 support for PLT format.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.6
Key Summary Category CADNET-8202 Implement correct iges file rendering Enhancement CADNET-8201 Implement parsing of missed entities for Iges file format Enhancement CADNET-8200 Fix iges parsing infinite loop Enhancement CADNET-8181 Implement pantone colors support Enhancement CADNET-8178 Fix coloring of some entities Enhancement CADNET-8177 Fix issue with MTEXT align Enhancement CADNET-8170 Improve hatch export performance for the file in parent issue Enhancement CADNET-8139 Implement correct rendering of Rotated dimension from scratch Enhancement CADNET-1323 Exception on saving image as PNG Enhancement CADNET-1249 &amp;ldquo;Image export failed.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.5 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.5
Key Summary Category CADNET-1354 Implement strikeout text support for MText entity Enhancement CADNET-1314 Imporve DWF import performance Enhancement CADNET-1264 Aspose.CAD 20.10: Failed to open PLT Enhancement CADNET-1193 Improving performance of parsing dwf files Enhancement CADNET-8049 Fix the issue with mixing colors for RGB DWF internal image Enhancement CADNET-1364 Specific IFC files failed to open Enhancement CADNET-1362 Customer properties are not getting saved in DWG/DXF Enhancement CADNET-1350 DWG is not completely exported to PDF Enhancement CADNET-1295 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Cannot create an instance of an interface.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.4
Key Summary Category CADNET-8052 Parameter is not valid exception on creating Images from DXF Enhancement CADNET-8048 Optimizing Cad2DPoint, Cad3dPoint and CadSize Enhancement CADNET-1188 Reducing memory usage dwg/dxf Enhancement CADNET-845 There is no creation of the new object CadData in some constructors of BitThickness and BitThicknessR13R14 classes.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.3 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.3
Key Summary Category CADNET-1335 Unify CAD 2D/3D exporters (remove 2D) Enhancement CADNET-1310 Implement export to DXF from all supported formats Feature CADNET-1358 Line Type Not Converting in exported PDF Enhancement CADNET-1347 Missing Block Attribute values in exported PDF Enhancement CADNET-1323 Exception on saving image as PNG Enhancement CADNET-1309 DWG to PDF results in unneccassary lines getting rendered Enhancement CADNET-1288 Exception on loading DWG Enhancement CADNET-1286 How to avoid margin in converting DWF to image Feature CADNET-1229 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: The Ifc version isn&amp;rsquo;t valid.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.2 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.2
Key Summary Category CADNET-1124 Implement IFC4 support Feature CADNET-1352 Fix Torus export to 3D format Enhancement CADNET-1315 Text objects is not exporting from ifc image. Enhancement CADNET-1313 Improve moving of hatch origin point Enhancement CADNET-1291 Implement functionality allows to extract all text from underlying drawing Enhancement CADNET-1359 Exception on exporting DXF with special symbols to PDF Enhancement CADNET-1344 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Index was out of range.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.1 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-net-21-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 21.1
Key Summary Category CADNET-1100 HoloLens 2 support in Aspose.CAD Feature CADNET-1298 Extract DWG different entities and save them in JSON or YML Enhancement CADNET-1293 Implement possibility to add/delete/modify entities for OBJ file format Enhancement CADNET-1015 Chinesse character are garbled and layers missing in exported PDF Enhancement CADNET-1322 Problems with Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>