<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.12.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the December release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have made various improvements related to splitting algorithms, here are some of them:
updated the SVG image validation algorithm; improved flex elements splitting and rendering algorithms; increased the accuracy of word wrapping; improved the positioned elements splitting algorithm; updated the CSS serialization algorithm according to the latest documentation; improved the table border splitting algorithm.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.11.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the November release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release we have made various improvements related to parsing algorithms, here are some of them:
updated the fragment parsing algorithm according to the latest documentation; improved the attribute parsing algorithm, now it supports more properties; updated the absolutely positioned element splitting algorithm; improved UNC path parsing; updated the transparency processing algorithm.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.9.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the September release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have significantly decreased memory consumption and improved various rendering algorithms, here are some of these improvements:
increased the precision of text decorations rendering; significantly decreased memory consumption, by more than 3 times; updated the CSS media queries parsing algorithm according to the latest documentation; improved the splitted elements backgrounds rendering algorithm.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.8.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the August release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have made a number of improvements related to the SVG elements and tables rendering. These include:
Improved text splitting algorithm Updated pattern paint server algorithm as per the latest documentation Increased performance of the nested elements rendering Improved fixed table layout algorithm Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLNET-2748 Exception during svg to pdf conversion Bug HTMLNET-2751 MHT to PNG do not render symbols Bug HTMLNET-2636 Converting HTML to PDF with multi-column CSS doesn’t work as expected Bug HTMLNET-2753 Nested DIV Tags slow Conversion Significantly Bug HTMLNET-1708 Problem rendering multi column HTML to PDF Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Added APIs namespace Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.7.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the July release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have made a number of improvements related to the columns processing algorithm and bookmarks rendering, here are some of them:
improved the font matching algorithm; updated the “columns” property processing algorithm according to the latest documentation; improved rendering of the SVG anchor element; introduced the processing of page bookmarks.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.6.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the June release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release we have added the support of new output format - DOCX. Now you can convert MHTML, EPUB, SVG and HTML to DOCX with just a couple lines of code! We have also made the number of rendering quality improvements, here are some of them:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.5.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the May release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. This release contains a long-awaited feature - the new rendering engine. It was designed according to the latest HTML and CSS specifications, which means that its rendering quality, speed, memory usage and precision are much better than in the previous one.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.4.
As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the April release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release, we have made a number of improvements related to the CSS processing algorithm and the quality of rendering. These include:
Increase in quality of inline styles serialization Updated parsing of the font-family property according to the CSS3 documentation Introduction of processing of the column group borders Improved positioning of the float images We have also made some minor usability improvements in this release such as clarified the URL parsing exceptions and added new signatures to the Document creation methods.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.3.
As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the March release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release, we have improved the handling of broken fonts and invalid URLs. We have also made some improvements to the rendering process that includes:
Handling of the negative table margins Improved JavaScript parsing algorithm Improved PDF document encryption Increased accuracy of the table size calculation algorithm We have also changed the default behavior of MarkdownSaveOption.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.2.
As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the February release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release we have made some improvements to the quality of rendering, these improvements include:
Improvements in the splitting of float elements Improvements in the font selection algorithm Improvements in the size calculation of SVG images Also, we have introduced new property, which allows you to specify the JavaScript processing timeout.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-html-for-net-20-1-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 20.1.
As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the January release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. This release contains a number of improvements related to the processing of resources and references, these improvements are:
Improved processing of resources embedded into HTML document using &amp;ldquo;data&amp;rdquo; protocol Updated processing of image attributes according to the latest documentation Improved links processing during markdown to HTML conversion Improvements Key Summary Category HTMLNET-2317 Image from HTML is missing in converted PDF Bug HTMLNET-2309 Links are not correctly rendered in Markdown Bug</description></item></channel></rss>