<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 21.12 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: File extension aware Image Save Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-4554 File extension aware Image Save Feature IMAGINGNET-4894 Cloud eps tests are failed on Imaging v21.11 beta Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4885 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed.&amp;rdquo; exception when open TGA document Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4862 Export SVG with embedded WebP image Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4834 Tiff to pdf Issue: file size increasing drastically Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4752 Incorrect conversion from tif to pdf Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4724 Error on use copied TiffFrame Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4717 &amp;ldquo;Unable to cast object of type &amp;lsquo;Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 21.11 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Support of FlateDecode decoder in EPS Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-4708 Support of FlateDecode decoder in EPS Feature IMAGINGNET-4825 Incorrect output when decompressing the BMP with DXT1 compression Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4800 Convert SVG to PNG Problem Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4785 Regression in compression methods when exporting to PSD format Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4783 Unable to open the Tiff file Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4679 Occasionally an exception occurs when running Image.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 21.10 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Method Image.GetOriginalOptions returns null for an existing image - support of GetOriginalOptions in Tiff format Support Image scoped fonts Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-4629 Method Image.GetOriginalOptions returns null for an existing image - support of GetOriginalOptions in Tiff format Feature IMAGINGNET-4448 Support Image scoped fonts Feature IMAGINGNET-4775 The trouble with Tiff file from the GIS team Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4746 [Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 21.9 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Implement support a &amp;ldquo;PANTONE goe coated&amp;rdquo; pallete in the CDR format Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-4439 Implement support a &amp;ldquo;PANTONE goe coated&amp;rdquo; pallete in the CDR format Feature IMAGINGNET-4648 Blurred output GIF to PDF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4644 Exception on converting WMZ to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4612 SVG to PNG, output image distorted Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4589 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 21.8 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Measure String for Graphics.DrawString method Implement missed functionality in SvgImage.Resize Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-4467 Measure String for Graphics.DrawString method Feature IMAGINGNET-2223 Implement missed functionality in SvgImage.Resize Feature IMAGINGNET-4608 Cannot set number of cycles in exported GIF animation Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4607 Incorrect number of cycles in exported GIF animation Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4594 Particular CDR file cannot be opened/rasterized Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4574 Fix bug with failed loading image Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4552 Text in saved EMF is garbled Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4547 Image saving failed when converting WMF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4545 Convert EMF to PNG will generate too many font files under TempFontsGraphics Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4537 Improve handling of the Png images without the IEND chunk Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4529 Improve original (prior to Version 2.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 21.7 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Support set of gif frame duration for all frames Implement support a tables in the cdr format Support the option of the number of cycles in the GIF animation Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-4553 Support set of gif frame duration for all frames Feature IMAGINGNET-4438 Implement support a tables in the cdr format Feature IMAGINGNET-3792 Support the option of the number of cycles in the GIF animation Feature IMAGINGNET-4478 Chart missing when exporting SVG to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4475 Support the same DPI when export raster image to PDF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4466 ImageSave exception on saving EMF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4464 Stackoverflow exception on loading JPG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4445 Incorrect conversion from SVG to PNG - part of image is lost.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 21.6 - Release notes | NET5 supported</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Support NET5 configuration for Aspose.Imaging .NET Implement ApngImage.GetOriginalOptions, ApngImage.GetDefaultOptions and ApngImage.GetModifyDate methods Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-4290 Add NET5 configuration for Aspose.Imaging .NET Feature IMAGINGNET-4079 Implement ApngImage.GetOriginalOptions, ApngImage.GetDefaultOptions and ApngImage.GetModifyDate methods Feature IMAGINGNET-4480 Resizing the image crops the output image Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4452 Cannot load particular WEBP image Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4446 Incorrect conversion from animated Gif to APNG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4434 Exception on exporting CDR to PDF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4418 ImageSaveException on saving CDR to PDF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4397 Fix set of CDR file text reading issues Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4382 Exception on loading SVG image Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4381 System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 21.5 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Eps can not be converted to vectorized APS (to svg for example) Support export to Dxf format in Aspose.Imaging Investigate and implement the object of the CDR - PowerClip Net Standard 2.1 replacement notice - Please note, since 21.6 release Net Standard 2.1 configuration will be replaced with newest NET5 configuration.
Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-4388 Support of Eps export as vector to svg Feature IMAGINGNET-4380 Support export to Dxf format in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 21.4 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-4057 Improve default font option usage on Linux Feature IMAGINGNET-4337 Incorrect export from CDR to PSD Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4335 EMF to PNG: Output is missing characters Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4268 Exception while converting GIF to APNG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4260 Blank PDF created of CDR file using Aspose Imaging for .net Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4257 Output SVG is not valid when converting EMF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4250 Exception while converting WMZ to PDF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4249 Exception while converting EMZ to JPG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4223 Exception while saving EMF image Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4200 &amp;ldquo;Image export failed.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 21.3 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Support to set DPI for exported PDF Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-4326 Support to set DPI for exported PDF Feature IMAGINGNET-4322 Aspose.Imaging 20.12: Incorrect saving SVG to JPG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4314 Dicom loader throws an OverflowException Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4301 Exception on converting SVG to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4300 Aspose.Imaging 20.11: Cannot convert Gif Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4298 ArgumentOutOfRange exception during the export from WMF to PNG format Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4294 ImageMasking GraphCut produces incorrect result with CalculateDefaultStrokes option Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4262 ImageLoadException on exporting CDR to PDF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4247 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 21.2 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-imaging-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Support BMP RLE4 compressed images in BmpLoader Explore the file format (CMX v11) and add support for it Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-4076 Support BMP RLE4 compressed images in BmpLoader Feature IMAGINGNET-3862 Explore the file format (CMX v11) and add support for it Feature IMAGINGNET-4286 Exception while converting GIF to DICOM Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4282 Support feathering feature in ImageMasking.</description></item></channel></rss>