<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.7
Key Summary Category PSDNET-802 Add ability to Export each layer of PSD File to the Animated Gif File Feature PSDNET-1441 Assign Fill property of Shape layer form vscg resource Feature PSDNET-1534 Add new types of warp (arc &amp;amp; arch) Feature PSDNET-1543 Change the application that saves the PSD File to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.6
Key Summary Category PSDNET-1401 Refactor TimeLine API Enhancement PSDNET-1517 Remove artifacts when rendering warp Enhancement PSDNET-1528 Warp rendering optimization Enhancement PSDNET-147 Support of Threshold Adjustment Layer Feature PSDNET-149 Support of Selective Color Adjustment Layer Feature PSDNET-801 Ability to export PSD TimeLine to the Animated Gif file Feature PSDNET-1555 Add support for TextLayer without rectangular borders Feature PSDNET-1582 Support of ShapeLayer Feature PSDNET-864 Replacing image in Smart object is not updating Bug PSDNET-1404 PSD file can not be saved as PSD with the following exception: Rgb and Lab modes can not contain less than 3 channels and more than 4 channels Bug PSDNET-1546 Text Justification is lost if open TextLayer by the edit mode of Photoshop Bug PSDNET-1548 Null reference exception on saving PSD file Bug PSDNET-1578 Exception on the loading of the ShapeLayer: Points for vector origin bounds is not supported yet Bug PSDNET-1579 Exception on loading of VogkResource: Points are saved as DoubleStructures, we read as UnitStructures Bug PSDNET-1581 LayerType of ShapeLayer is empty Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.5 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.5
Key Summary Category PSDNET-343 Support of Filter: Sharpen -&amp;gt; Sharpen Feature PSDNET-1179 PSD file (RGB/8bit or RGB/16bit) saving without layers to 32bit Feature PSDNET-1408 Implement handling path objects from vsms or vmsk resources for ShapeLayer Feature PSDNET-1508 Add the influence of mesh points on each other Feature Public API Changes Added APIs: M:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.4
Key Summary Category PSDNET-1409 Design RawColor class for the public API to use it in PSD API instead of obsolete Color struct Enhancement PSDNET-1332 Integrate Gradient Map Adjustment Layer from Probation to main Aspose.PSD code Feature PSDNET-1448 Editing of text using Text Portions doesn&amp;rsquo;t save the correct result Bug PSDNET-1449 The starting and ending of the styles or paragraphs appear in the incorrect place on the editing of Text Layer by ITextPortion Bug PSDNET-1509 Formatting move when editing in photoshop Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: T:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.3 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.3
Key Summary Category PSDNET-146 Support of Posterize Adjustment Layer Feature PSDNET-1366 Implement support of VscgResource Feature PSDNET-1437 Add support of PostResource resource for data of Posterize Adjustment Layer Feature PSDNET-931 Incorrect export to PNG layer with Curves adjustment and CMYK color mode Bug PSDNET-1403 Style of Paragraph is missed after the saving of file and updating of file by PS Bug PSDNET-1453 Broken rendering of glow and shadow effects on text Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: P:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.2 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.2
Key Summary Category PSDNET-1359 Rework text rendering to improve text positioning, rendering, and support Enhancement PSDNET-1270 Add ability to process Warp Effect though the public API Feature PSDNET-1391 Add support of Bottom-to-bottom and Top-to-Top leading modes from Paragraph settings Feature PSDNET-912 Change Font and Color for TextLayer PSD Bug PSDNET-1022 Incorrect export of text at test TextUpdateTests, text is missing Bug PSDNET-1221 Extra small text is missing after resizing of the bigger PSD image Bug PSDNET-1301 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.1 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-psd-for-net-23-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 23.1
Key Summary Category PSDNET-401 Support of vstkResource Feature PSDNET-1346 Add the editable BaselineDirection/IsStandardVerticalRomanAlignmentEnabled property to the IText interface Feature PSDNET-181 PSD is not properly converted to JPEG Bug PSDNET-958 PSB to PDF fails for large files Bug PSDNET-1171 Add processing of clipping mask to adjustment layer Bug PSDNET-1252 After the resize of whole image and then after resize of the specific layer Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>