<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.12.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-42315 Support for crtx files - applying custom chart templates New Feature CELLSNET-47895 Images are distorted in Excel to PDF/HTML rendering Bug CELLSNET-47946 Image rotation effect is not displayed correctly in pdf/html Bug CELLSNET-47947 The rectangular box rotation effect in the graphics group is not displayed correctly in pdf/html Bug CELLSNET-52126 Some shapes are changed after converting Excel file to PDF Bug CELLSNET-52197 Boxes changed when converting XLSX document to PDF Bug CELLSNET-52330 Drawing shapes not rendered fine in HTML Bug CELLSNET-50042 The defined name is changed after re-saving Bug CELLSNET-52270 YEARFRAC Function is not calculated correctly Bug CELLSNET-52305 MMULT with OFFSET is not calculated correctly Bug CELLSNET-52307 Broken link formula returns 0 instead of #REF!</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.11.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-52026 Support copying timeline New Feature CELLSNET-52022 Distinguish or differentiate between CSE legacy array formula and normal array formula Enhancement CELLSNET-52156 Disable merged table cells when saving XLSX to HTML Enhancement CELLSNET-52159 Support to parse collapsed property when converting html to excel Enhancement CELLSNET-51939 XLSX to PDF: Content misalignment Bug CELLSNET-51940 XLS to PDF: Content misalignment in cells Bug CELLSNET-52068 XLSX to PDF: Shapes missing/Layout collapse Bug CELLSNET-52092 Character printing and spacing in the figures of Excel is cut off Bug CELLSNET-52186 Shapes/boxes are empty when converting XLSX document to PDF Bug CELLSNET-52225 XLSX to PDF Characters in text boxes reversed Bug CELLSNET-52086 External connections corrupted in the generated file Bug CELLSNET-52133 Excel formulas are wrapped with curly braces in the re-saved xlsb file Bug CELLSNET-52158 Incorrect circular reference detection Bug CELLSNET-52174 Cell.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.10.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-42037 PivotTable Timeline Filter disappears after loading excel document and updating New Feature CELLSNET-51963 Support for CRTX files New Feature CELLSNET-51952 MAXIFS formulas take long time to be calculated Enhancement CELLSNET-52064 It&amp;rsquo;s not allowed to push non-empty cells off the end of the worksheet error when using Cells.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.9.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-51935 Support discrete group data for xls file New Feature CELLSNET-51925 Support preset gradient settings for gradient fill New Feature CELLSNET-51740 Support to set table formula for the datatable Enhancement CELLSNET-51853 Support to convert ozm to lbm for CONVERT function Enhancement CELLSNET-51931 Improve the recognization of user&amp;rsquo;s input for Style.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.8.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-51589 Support expand/collapse button style for PivotTable New Feature CELLSNET-51473 Convert threaded comments to html Enhancement CELLSNET-51570 Copy row height when processing smart markers of a table Enhancement CELLSNET-51590 Delete grouped shapes from group Enhancement CELLSNET-51595 Wrong vertical alignment of cell text on convert to PDF from Excel file with pivot table Bug CELLSNET-51621 Shared formulas were copied incorrectly for different file formats Bug CELLSNET-51524 Wrong word wrapping on converting to PDF from Excel file with pivot table Bug CELLSNET-51675 Shape is lost while converting to pdf Bug CELLSNET-51435 New worksheet relationships are added when converting an XLSB workbook to XLSM Bug CELLSNET-51545 Workbook with MS Excel 5.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.7.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-51296 Gridweb keeps jumping back to top when trying to copy and paste Enhancement CELLSNET-51355 And Range.Top, Left, Width ,Height in unit of points Enhancement CELLSNET-51367 Convert all sheets to one page when saving as html. Enhancement CELLSNET-51486 The text rendered as small squares Bug CELLSNET-51492 Default font is not applied when converting XLSX to HTML Bug CELLSNET-51306 Pivot table styles not copied properly using the latest version of Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.6.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-50880 New apis to convert data to ICellsDataTable for user&amp;rsquo;s convenience New Feature CELLSNET-51140 Support data storage 5.0 of .numbers New Feature CELLSNET-51144 Support reading images of Numbers13 New Feature CELLSNET-51230 Support to set style for CellRange Enhancement CELLSNET-50996 Add ChartCollection.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.5.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-50663 Improve performance of deleting blank columns Enhancement CELLSNET-50877 Initialize cell&amp;rsquo;s calculated value when setting dynamic array formula Enhancement CELLSNET-51006 Remove method SetDataSource(string variable, object[] dataArray) method. Enhancement CELLSNET-50685 Issue with retrieving Linked OLE attachments in ODS file Bug CELLSNET-50920 Excel to Tiff conversion issue Bug CELLSNET-50820 Issue of exporting JSON string to Excel Bug CELLSNET-50853 Slicers filter disappears after resaving by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.4.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-50624 Support to remove tailing blank cells for saving csv New Feature CELLSNET-50747 Add Style.HasBorders to check whether there are borders for it Enhancement CELLSNET-50627 Get merged range with respect to worksheet cell in Aspose.Cells.GridDesktop Enhancement CELLSNET-50675 add GridLoadDataFilterOptions for GridDesktop and Worksheet.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.3.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-50375 Support sorting PivotField via values in selected row/column New Feature CELLSNET-50559 Support to get cell&amp;rsquo;s leafs recursively New Feature CELLSNET-50512 Support to re-calculate cells which reference to defined name when the defined name is changed and calculation chain is enabled Enhancement CELLSNET-50403 Add SaveFormat.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.2.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-50332 Extract all the NameCollections of a particular worksheet New Feature CELLSNET-50353 Add StandardHeightInch property in Cells class New Feature CELLSNET-50152 Various formatting and other shapes rendering issues in PDF and HTML of Excel file Bug CELLSNET-50300 Some shapes are not rendered properly in Excel to PDF conversion Bug CELLSNET-50301 Invalid value for external reference in DataSource field of Pivot Table Bug CELLSNET-50241 Regression: CSV to PDF conversion not working Bug CELLSNET-50268 Empty CellsArea array returned for CSV/TSV files Bug CELLSNET-50269 Finnish language - Numbers formatted as Percentage are missing the space before the percent symbol Bug CELLSNET-50333 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cells-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 22.1.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-50082 Support to return original indices of sorted rows/columns for sort() function New Feature CELLSNET-50088 Support to set print job name with PrinterSettings while rendering to printer New Feature CELLSNET-50060 Detect whether text file is csv or tsv. New Feature CELLSNET-49939 Ingore hidden rows and columns when getting Cells.</description></item></channel></rss>