<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 20.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 20.12
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-950 Image loading failed: The arithmetic operation caused an overflow Enhancement CADJAVA-791 Unstable drawing of diameter symbol at Cad3DTests.dimensionTest test on Win10/Ubuntu Enhancement CADJAVA-957 Invisible text in PDF has missing characters if font doesn&amp;rsquo;t have symbols for them. Enhancement CADJAVA-955 API hangs forever on loading DXF files using latest version Enhancement CADJAVA-954 ImageLaoding failed exception on loading DXF files Enhancement CADJAVA-953 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 20.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 20.11
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-917 Support for PC3 files Feature CADJAVA-915 HoloLens 2 support in Aspose.CAD Feature CADJAVA-914 Export to OBJ file format support Feature CADJAVA-908 Implement writer methods for DWG DataSectionReader Enhancement CADJAVA-858 Export to DXF from APS Enhancement CADJAVA-916 Freezes on format detection Enhancement CADJAVA-913 System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 20.10 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 20.10
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-886 Incorrect export to gdi pdf Enhancement CADJAVA-882 Redundant namespaces on documentation Enhancement CADJAVA-889 Exception in multi-threaded environment on IFC loaded Enhancement CADJAVA-888 Error while converting dwt format to image Enhancement CADJAVA-885 Drawing of 3D solids is incorrect Enhancement CADJAVA-881 Missing drawing elements when converting DWG Enhancement CADJAVA-880 Bad fonts and too big result file Enhancement CADJAVA-853 Index was out of range exception when converting DWG Enhancement CADJAVA-772 Cannot open an image.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 20.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 20.9
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-849 Dxf, editing entities (line, ellipse, arc, circle, xline, ray, 3dface) Enhancement CADJAVA-845 Investigate empty acds for 3D vertex entities Enhancement CADJAVA-844 Aspose.CAD 20.7: Loading particular DWF document raises exception Enhancement CADJAVA-840 Implement internal mechanism to put watermark on drawing for PDF export Enhancement CADJAVA-857 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 20.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 20.8
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-806 Text Alignment is disturbed in generated PDF Enhancement CADJAVA-684 Exception on loading DWG Enhancement CADJAVA-822 Error while save DWG to DXF Enhancement CADJAVA-820 The problems of file with large coordinate and high resolution Enhancement CADJAVA-819 Convert text from DWG/DXF to SVG as text rather shapes Enhancement CADJAVA-818 Multiline text in DXF saved by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 20.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 20.7
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-789 An ability to update metadata in .dwg, .dxf Feature CADJAVA-730 Support to detect file format without loading Feature CADJAVA-782 Implement writing Classes section for Dxf format Enhancement CADJAVA-778 Implement unit-tests, debugging Enhancement CADJAVA-777 Implement correct reads from dwg and writing for dxf of SoftPointer Enhancement CADJAVA-774 Unable to read Dwf content: Error on reading hoops object exception when loading DWF Enhancement CADJAVA-773 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 20.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 20.6
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-746 Aspose.CAD 20.3: Support for AC1015 DXF files Enhancement CADJAVA-659 How to interrupt or put a timeout on Save Enhancement CADJAVA-748 Fix reading of ARC entities for DWG Enhancement CADJAVA-749 Shaded 3D entities in DWG are not rendered correctly. Enhancement CADJAVA-745 Tiny image when saving DWG Enhancement CADJAVA-742 NullReferenceException on saving DWG Enhancement CADJAVA-741 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 20.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 20.4
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-703 Converting a particular area of DWG to PDF New Feature CADJAVA-698 DWG to PDF: Automatically ignoring hidden layers during rendering (C#) New Feature CADJAVA-697 Fix clip for global canvas algorithm Enhancement CADJAVA-693 Object reference exception on exporting IFC to PDF Enhancement CADJAVA-696 DWG to PDF: Some texts are not being printed (C# .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 20.3 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 20.3
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-669 Support for DWFX files New Feature CADJAVA-659 How to interrupt or put a timeout on Save New Feature CADJAVA-345 Support for DXF Version New Feature CADJAVA-661 Prepare SEO-friendly endpoints and provide usage examples on Cloud API Enhancement CADJAVA-650 Integrate the latest Imaging module changes Enhancement CADJAVA-638 Investigate and improve the coloring of separate and blocked entities Enhancement CADJAVA-634 The API documentation is not available Enhancement CADJAVA-526 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 20.1 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-cad-for-java-20-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 20.1
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-600 Support for conversion of DWG to DWF Feature CADJAVA-598 Support for OBJ format Feature CADJAVA-537 Read hyperlinks and OLE object links section Feature CADJAVA-596 DWG drawings take a long time to convert to PDF Enhancement CADJAVA-595 Last Author metadata information failed to get extracted Enhancement CADJAVA-587 Text Color problem in exported PDF Enhancement CADJAVA-503 Create PDF from DWG file Enhancement CADJAVA-534 Issue in API docs links Bug CADJAVA-602 Exception on extracting text from DGN and DWF Bug CADJAVA-599 ArgumentNullException is thrown when saving DWG drawing as an image stream Bug CADJAVA-597 Exception on converting DXF file to PNG Bug CADJAVA-593 Hidden layers are ignored when rendering drawing Bug CADJAVA-592 Hidden layers have same Flags values as a visible one Bug CADJAVA-591 Default font setting stopped working Bug CADJAVA-590 Empty folder called TempFonts created in a temp directory Bug CADJAVA-589 Blank output when saving STL file Bug CADJAVA-586 Export of STL to WMF failed Bug CADJAVA-585 DWT file format detection issue Bug CADJAVA-565 DXF file not properly converted to PNG Bug CADJAVA-538 Exception in a multi-threaded environment Bug CADJAVA-536 NullPointerException when converting DWG to image in java Bug CADJAVA-535 DWF not properly converted to PNG Bug CADJAVA-532 Exception on converting DWG to PDF Bug CADJAVA-531 Blank page PNG generated from DXF Bug CADJAVA-527 DWG not converted to PDF Bug CADJAVA-501 DWG not properly converted to PDF Bug CADJAVA-497 Exception on loading DWG Bug CADJAVA-166 CadException: The DGN version is not valid when loading a DGN file Bug Added APIs: Class com.</description></item></channel></rss>