<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 23.10 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-10-release-notes/</guid><description>Improvement: Reduced the size of library by 2 Mb.
Competitive features: Improving EPS graphics rendering : Eps -&amp;gt; svg: System.ApplicationException: Unknown name ‘gcheck&amp;rsquo; Improving EPS graphics rendering : Can&amp;rsquo;t convert EPS to PDF Improving EPS graphics rendering : Cannot convert the EPS image to PDF Improving EPS graphics rendering : EPS export issue Improving EPS graphics rendering : Cannot load the EPS file Improving EPS graphics rendering : Fix bug with Eps file parsing Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8576 Eps -&amp;gt; svg: System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 23.11 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-11-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Implement support text styles italic/underline in CDR format Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8584 Implement support text styles italic/underline in CDR format Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8583 Failed to open CMX file Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8577 Converting the Png to Psd issue Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8559 SVG to PNG conversion issues Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8556 Cannot convert the CMX image to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8555 Emf file not correctly converted to png Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8554 System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 23.12 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-12-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Add RemoveBackground &amp;amp; ChangeBackground API entries for VectorImage Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8625 Add RemoveBackground &amp;amp; ChangeBackground API entries for VectorImage Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8622 System.NullReferenceException when DataStreamSupporter.Save Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8621 Cannot resize the PNG image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8617 Cannot convert the EMF file to PDF Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8586 Incorrect conversion the EMF image to SVG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8552 Emf not converting to SVG in trial mode Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 23.9 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-9-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Implement Remove watermark filter Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8545 Implement Remove watermark filter Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8534 Exception on creating palette of large image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8533 Can&amp;rsquo;t load EPS image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8522 DICOM load issue Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8516 Required palette is missing exception loading BMP Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8512 The GIF file loading issue Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 23.8 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-8-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Implement Magic Wand tool Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8500 Implement Magic Wand tool Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8501 Fix bugs with fonts when Svg export Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8499 Improvement request for multi frame Gif to composite image formats export Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8494 Saving of images with dimensions more than 65535 to Jpeg format works incorrect Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8493 Memory leak if Image.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for JAVA 23.7 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-7-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Add alpha blending feature for RasterImage Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8477 UnIfy naming conventions Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8476 Synchronize use of Pages and format specific collections for multi page images Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8475 Add alpha blending feature for RasterImage Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8470 EMF export error Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 23.6 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-6-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8466 Evaluation watermark is added to the output when converting DCM Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8450 EMF to SVG NullReferenceException Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8444 Regression: Exif Data is missing exception Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.Imaging for .NET 23.6 version
Removed APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 23.5 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-5-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Support of TIFF with Cmyk Alpha color mode Support of tiled Tiff writing Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8440 Support of TIFF with Cmyk Alpha color mode Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8427 Support of tiled Tiff writing Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8441 wk: Converting PNG to TIFF using CMYK colorspace and preserving transparency Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8431 SVG to PDF: Arrows not rendered correctly Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8426 Cannot convert the CDR image to JPG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8395 Resizing operation is incorrect for GIF animation Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8394 &amp;ldquo;Bit depth of 8 bits are supported for RGBA images.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 23.4 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-4-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Support of image raw data rendering from EPS Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8404 Support of image raw data rendering from EPS Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8420 The EMF image on export to PNG has bottom-right shifted content Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8419 NullReferenceException during an operation of conversion from tiff to pdf in the multithread mode. Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8411 Can&amp;rsquo;t convert EPS to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8409 Cannot convert the EPS image to EMF Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8408 Cannot load EPS image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8401 Can&amp;rsquo;t convert CMX to JPG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8397 Issue with PNG images converted from EPS Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8396 Cannot access a disposed object after conversion of ICO image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8389 DICOM loading issue under ARM64 mode Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8388 WMF loading issue Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8332 Incorrect text offsets in Emf formulas rasterization Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8315 Cdr to png misses lines Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 23.3 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-3-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Add support of BigTiff Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8383 Add support of BigTiff Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8372 Resultant PNG cannot be opened by Photoshop Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8371 Cannot access a closed file when converting EMZ on Linux Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8370 Two conversion issues (cdr to wmf, wmf to tiff) Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8369 Tiff image is corrupted when saved Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8366 WmfImage.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 23.2 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-java-23-2-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Keep transparency, when indexing Png images Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8339 Keep transparency, when indexing Png images Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8344 SVG export issue Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8343 Image export failed when converting DCM to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8342 Convert TIFF to PDF loses color Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8341 ICO to PDF export bug Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8331 ImageExtensions.toJava takes too long to convert Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>