<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.12.
Major Features There are 97 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added an ability to specify the page layout to be used when the document is opened in a PDF reader. Implemented the way to control how ZIP64 format extensions will be used for OOXML documents. Introduced support for WebP images.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.11.
Major Features There are 68 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added an ability to specify the default font formatting for legend entries of DrawingML charts. Provided an ability to write all sections of the document to the same XLSX worksheet. Python 3.5 will no longer be supported starting with version Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.10.
Major Features There are 124 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented various PDF rendering optimizations to reduce output size when utilizing PdfSaveOptions.OptimizeOutput settings. Added the capability to retrieve the foreground color without modifiers in the Fill and Stroke classes. Expanded the functionality of ChartDataPointCollection, ChartSeries, and ChartFormat classes with new options.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.9.
Major Features There are 69 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Released version Aspose.Words for Python via .Net for MacOs X x86/64 Added an ability to set axis title of charts. Extended MarkdownSaveOptions with ImagesFolderAlias property. Added an ability to specify fonts vertical position on a line for paragraph. Implemented metafile rendering emulation of rasterization size for WMF pen width and EMF cosmetic pen.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.8.
Major Features There are 106 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Introduced functionality to automatically generate a Table of Contents (TOC) for MOBI documents. Expanded PdfEncryptionDetails constructor with PdfPermissions. Introduced a new public property to specify the size of rendered images in pixels. Implemented shaping of vertical text for EMF metafiles.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.7.
Major Features There are 114 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
The possibility to save the document page or shape into EPS format has been implemented. The ability to retrieve the digital signature value from a digitally signed document as a byte array has been added. The Row and Cell classes have been extended with new public members.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.6.
Major Features There are 87 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented an ability to save documents as XLSX. Added support of Advanced Typography in WMF, EMF and EMF+ rendering. Added public property (PageInfo.Colored) indicating whether the page is in color or not. Added a new way of dynamic HTML insertion for LINQ Reporting Engine.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.5.
Major Features There are 174 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Provided the feature to get and modify chart series data. Implemented support for text wrapping in headers/footers. Fixed rendering of MathML formula with embedded images. Added an ability to remove digital signatures from ODT documents. Added public properties to obtain base and ruby text of phonetic guide Run.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.4.
Major Features There are 70 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added an ability to set distance between table and surrounding text. Provided an ability to determine whether a Run is a phonetic guide run. Implemented the simple way to work with series and axes of a combo charts. Provided the new public properties connected to the shape relative positioning and sizing.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.3.
Major Features There are 78 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Extended set of public properties for working with fill colors. Implemented rendering of radial gradients with SkiaSharp native shader for .NET Standard. Added support of InvertIfNegative property for bar chart rendering. Implemented saving progress notifications for MOBI and AZW3 formats.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.2.
Major Features There are 77 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
MOBI (also called PRC, AZW - Amazon Kindle&amp;rsquo;s proprietary e-book file format) is now supported for import and export. Added an ability to specify the character spacing adjustment of a document. Provided the way to instruct Aspose.Words whether to include textboxes, footnotes and endnotes in word count statistics.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2023/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-23-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 23.1.
Major Features There are 75 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Significantly improved performance and quality of emulation of raster operations with metafiles. Implemented an ability to work with shading theme colors. Added the ability to generate TOC (table of contents) for AZW3 documents. Provided the way to control how the list items are exported to the Markdown format.</description></item></channel></rss>