<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.12
GPU version: 20.12.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRNET-280 Implement the possibility to get result in .doc, .docx, .odt and .txt formats Enhancement OCRNET-290 Increase performance by reducing image loading time Enhancement Enhancements added ability to save the recognition result in the plain text, Microsoft Word, Office Open XML or ODF Text Document format improving overall API performance by reducing image loading times Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API added method Save to the RecognitionResult object Removed APIs All methods of the previous release are supported.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.11
GPU version: 20.11.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRNET-246 Add the language choose option Enhancement Enhancements Added ability to recognize a batch of images (in zip archive or in a folder). Pass archive name or folder name as a parameter and get an array of results from each page) Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API Method Description public RecognitionResult[] RecognizeMultipleImages(string path, RecognitionSettings settings) path - path to the zip archive (include extension) or path to the folder, settings - object for parameters Removed APIs All methods of the previous release are supported.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.10 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.10
GPU version: 20.10.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRNET-243 Add the language choose option Enhancement OCRNET-247 Make an option to set a custom angle for the skew correction feature. Enhancement Enhancements added language choose option (supported languages: English, German, Portuguese, Spanish, French, Italian) added option for manually setting angle for the skew correction feature.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.9
GPU version: 20.9.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRNET-261 Add new recognition result format:JSON Enhancement OCRNET-242 Extend API with method which gets the uri-link on image in parameters Enhancement Enhancements API method with the next opportunities:
send URI-link for recognition; send recognition options as an object get recognition result as an object with different properties Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API Method Description RecognitionResult RecognizeImageFromUri(string uri, RecognitionSettings settings) uri- link on the image, settings - object for parameters Removed APIs No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.8
GPU version: 20.8.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRNET-238 New ML model with improved symbols recognition. Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API No Changes
Removed APIs No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.7
GPU version: 20.7.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRNET-209 Remove vertical and horizontal lines from tables Enhancement OCRNET-197 Add image recognition using GPU and CUDA technology (available in separate assembly Aspose.OCR.Gpu) Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API No Changes
Removed APIs No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.6
Enhancements API does not need to be disposed of. Recognition quality improved. Added API support for working with streams. Added API support for working with recognition areas. Added ability to specify characters for recognition. Added the ability to calculate skew of the image. Flag for text area detection. Optional flag for skew correction. Supported Characters space !</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-net-20-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 20.4
In this release, we are introducing a new recognition engine based on effective CPU calculations to increase the performance of text recognition. Machine Learning approaches allow using GPU to improve performance significantly,
Enhancements Improved performance using CPU/GPU. New text search approach tuned for complex layouts. Supported Characters space !</description></item></channel></rss>