<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.12
In this release was fixed a regression with 16-bit export was.
Key Summary Category PSDNET-1336 Add the editable TextOrientation property to the IText interface Feature PSDNET-725 Resizing of the specified PSD file with a layer mask produce incorrect mask Bug PSDNET-1277 Add the ability to save and load a mask for 16 images Bug PSDNET-1281 Incorrect transparency on saving of 16 bit image to 16 or 8 bit image Bug PSDNET-1375 Fix CMYK in 16 bit color Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: T:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.11
This release has a regression in the case of 16-bit exports, so we recommend caution when using this feature in this release. Please do not update Aspose.PSD to 22.9-22.11 if 16-bit image processing is your primary functionality. We are working on solutions to these problems.
Key Summary Category PSDNET-1320 Can not export extremely big PSB files Enhancement PSDNET-659 Make the center of the radial gradient movable Feature PSDNET-1330 Unsupported ZipWithoutPrediction compression method for the specific files Feature PSDNET-735 After using a transformation method for a layer only, the saved layer has incorrect bounding box Bug PSDNET-1234 Exception on loading PSD image with pattern Bug PSDNET-1244 Image export failed (IndexOutOfRangeException) on the saving of PSD file with Chinese symbols Bug PSDNET-1303 TimeLine ActiveFrame applies incorrect Bug PSDNET-1307 Regression 22.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.10 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.10
This release has a regression in the case of 16-bit exports, so we recommend caution when using this feature in this release. Please do not update Aspose.PSD to 22.9-22.10 if 16-bit image processing is your primary functionality. We are working on solutions to these problems.
Key Summary Category PSDNET-1287 Remove obsolete properties in Lfx2Resource Enhancement PSDNET-1071 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.9
This release has a regression in the case of 16-bit exports, so we recommend caution when using this feature in this release. Please do not update Aspose.PSD to 22.9 if 16-bit image processing is your primary functionality. For several versions of Photoshop, users may encounter a window with an error reading layer, this will not affect the work with the PSD file.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.8
Key Summary Category PSDNET-1225 Investigate and fix the issues in the installer Enhancement PSDNET-800 Support of Frame TimeLine from PSD File Feature PSDNET-1219 Support of &amp;lsquo;mlst&amp;rsquo; resource that contains in ShmdResource as a sub-resource Feature PSDNET-814 Hash of Layer changes if we call layer.BlendingOptions.Effects Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: T:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.7
Key Summary Category PSDNET-482 Support of Image Section Resource #4000-4999 Plug-In resource(s) Feature PSDNET-875 An unhandled exception of &amp;ldquo;System.OutOfMemoryException&amp;rdquo; type occurs in Aspose.PSD.dll Bug PSDNET-1050 After exporting the PSD file, the result is much larger than the source file Bug PSDNET-1083 Incorrect parsing data for XmpResource Bug PSDNET-1205 After exporting, the size of PSD files with subfolders has increased Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: T:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.6
Key Summary Category PSDNET-940 Create API for getting the unique hash for similar layers in different files Enhancement PSDNET-678 Incorrect rendering of FillLayer with pattern in the case when patterns are more than one and layers order changed Bug PSDNET-1125 Exception on loading of specific PSD file with CMYK color mode Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: T:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.5 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.5
Key Summary Category PSDNET-952 Add EffectType property to ILayerEffect Interface Feature PSDNET-1146 Refactoring of ChannelData Class Enhancement PSDNET-657 Make the opacity property work for DropShadowEffect Bug PSDNET-825 Incorrect drawing of adjustment layer through the transparent layer in a specific case Bug PSDNET-1168 Improve Colorize method.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.4
Key Summary Category PSDNET-261 Rendering of Outer Glow Layer Effect Feature PSDNET-1123 Add support of Sha256 License Enhancement PSDNET-1107 Positioning multi-line text does not match the result in Photoshop Bug PSDNET-1113 The issue with loading PSD file on text resource data parsing Bug PSDNET-1129 Incorrect position of the custom pattern after saving as PSD Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: T:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.3 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.3
Key Summary Category PSDNET-210 Add property IsOpen for Layer Group Feature PSDNET-643 PSD image with raster layer masks discards masks on saving to 16 bit PSD image Bug PSDNET-899 Blend mode Dissolve does not apply to the folder with mask Bug PSDNET-1047 Specific file can not be opened by Photoshop after the saving in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.2 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.2
Key Summary Category PSDNET-1032 Adding support of .Net 6 Enhancement PSDNET-142 Support of Vibrance Adjustment Layers Feature PSDNET-396 Support of vibAResource Feature PSDNET-1057 Create an example of adding custom smart filters that are not supported in Aspose.PSD Feature PSDNET-642 Disabled raster layer masks don&amp;rsquo;t render correctly Bug PSDNET-644 Exception on resizing PSD files with 16bit per channel and a raster mask Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: M:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.1 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-psd-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 22.1
Key Summary Category PSDNET-1017 PatternOverlay can be applied only once Bug PSDNET-1056 Temp files overflow when opening a file from stream Bug PSDNET-991 Rendering optimization for Gaussian blur smart filter Feature PSDNET-1044 Support of many patterns data at PattResource Feature Public API Changes Added APIs: M:Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>