<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/cpp/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/cpp/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Cells for CPP 20.7 Release Notes Linux</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-cells-for-cpp-linux-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-cells-for-cpp-linux-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for C++ 20.7 for Linux.
We are pleased to announce the release of Aspose.Cells for C++ 20.7 for Linux.
Key Summary Category CELLSCPP-6 Apply Conditional formatting to the cells New Feature CELLSCPP-7 Read/Write Custom Document Properties New Feature CELLSCPP-8 Read/Write Built-in document properties New Feature CELLSCPP-9 Add Hyperlinks to the cells New Feature CELLSCPP-11 Support MS Excel Themes New Feature CELLSCPP-12 Add and manipulate PivotTables in the spreadsheets New Feature CELLSCPP-13 Group rows and columns in the worksheet New Feature CELLSCPP-14 Add Table/List Object to the worksheet New Feature CELLSCPP-20 Open/Save XLS, OOXML file formats New Feature CELLSCPP-21 Set Styles and Formatting to worksheet cells New Feature CELLSCPP-22 Apply data validation to the cells New Feature CELLSCPP-23 Set data and Formulas to the cells New Feature CELLSCPP-24 Apply Page Setup options New Feature CELLSCPP-25 Filter data by using an AutoFilter New Feature CELLSCPP-35 Read / Write XLSM file format New Feature CELLSCPP-36 Read / Write CSV file format New Feature CELLSCPP-37 Read / Write XLSB file format New Feature CELLSCPP-38 Create and manipulate Named Ranges New Feature CELLSCPP-39 Read / Write Tab Delimited file format New Feature CELLSCPP-41 Calculate formulas in Excel file(s) New Feature</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for CPP 20.7 Release Notes Windows</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-cells-for-cpp-windows-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-cells-for-cpp-windows-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for C++ 20.7 for Windows.
Key Summary Category CELLSCPP-250 Aspose.Cells for C++ does not work in VS 2019 when referenced through NuGet package manager New Feature CELLSCPP-234 Exception raised while saving a workbook as HTML without absolute/relative directory path in Save function Bug</description></item></channel></rss>