<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.OCR for Java 20.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-java-20-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-java-20-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for Java 20.11
GPU version: 20.11.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRJAVA-87 Extend API with next feature: support the recognition of the multiple images Enhancement Enhancements The next opportunities:
Added ability to recognize a batch of images (in zip archive or in a folder). Pass archive name or folder name as a parameter and get an array of results from each page) Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API Method Description ArrayList RecognizeMultiplePages(String path, RecognitionSettings settings) path - path to the zip archive (include extension) or path to the folder, settings - object for parameters Removed APIs All methods of the previous release are supported.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for Java 20.10 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-java-20-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-java-20-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for Java 20.10
GPU version: 20.10.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRJAVA-86 Extend API: add the language choose options Enhancement OCRJAVA-80 Make an option to set a custom angle for the skew correction feature Enhancement Enhancements The next opportunities:
skew (default 0) - allows setting skew correction language(default Language.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for Java 20.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-java-20-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-java-20-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for Java 20.9
GPU version: 20.9.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRJAVA-77 Add new recognition result format:JSON Enhancement OCRJAVA-76 Extend API with method which gets the uri-link on image in parameters Enhancement Enhancements API method with the next opportunities:
send URI-link for recognition; send recognition options as an object get recognition result as an object with different properties Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API Method Description RecognitionResult RecognizePageFromUri(string uri, RecognitionSettings settings) uri- link on the image, settings - object for parameters Removed APIs No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for Java 20.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-java-20-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-java-20-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for Java 20.8
GPU version: 20.8.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRJAVA-71, OCRJAVA-72 New ML model with improved symbols recognition. Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API No Changes
Removed APIs No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for Java 20.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-java-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-java-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for Java 20.7
GPU version: 20.7.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRJAVA-47 Recognizing text in the tables (remove vertical and horizontal lines from tables). Enhancement OCRJAVA-60 Add image recognition using GPU and CUDA technology (available in separate assembly Aspose.OCR.Gpu) Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for Java 20.5 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-java-20-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-ocr-for-java-20-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for Java 20.5
Aspose.OCR for Java is a library for optical character recognition and document scanning. It allows you to scan documents and recognize characters include diacritic.
Input Formats For loading images used Image.IO build-in package in the Java core 1.8.
The Image I/O has built-in support for GIF, PNG, JPEG, BMP, and WBMP. The Image I/O is also extensible so that developers or administrators can &amp;ldquo;plug-in&amp;rdquo; support for additional formats.</description></item></channel></rss>