<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 17.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-note-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-note-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Note for Java 17.11 release.
Major Changes This release includes enhancement where conflict history pages can be manipulated using the API.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category NOTENET-2262 Page size is reset to Auto after document saving Bug NOTENET-2386 Page metadata node is missed exception is raised while loading attached onenote files Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Public Methods Added Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 17.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-note-for-java-17-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-note-for-java-17-8-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes about Aspose.Note for Java 17.8.
Major Change We have stopped support for JDK 1.6 from this release onward. The minimum version of JDK supported by API from this release is 1.7.
Improvements Key Summary Category NOTENET-2269 Exception raised while loading the attached one note file Bug NOTENET-2353 API shows incorrect number of pages in the document Bug NOTEJAVA-286 Page history is not accessible Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 17.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-note-for-java-17-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-note-for-java-17-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Note for Java 17.3.
Major Features Added support for documents printing Added support for hyperlinks in images Features and Improvements Key Summary Category NOTENET-1668 Add support for hyperlinks in images. New Feature NOTEJAVA-269 Add support to print document. New Feature NOTENET-2212 Optimize file size and saving time of Documents with many page versions.</description></item></channel></rss>