<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/androidjava/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/androidjava/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.PDF for Android via Java 20.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/androidjava/release-notes/2020/aspose-pdf-for-android-via-java-20-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/androidjava/release-notes/2020/aspose-pdf-for-android-via-java-20-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for Android via Java 20.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFANDROID-610 PDF to CSV conversion support New Feature PDFANDROID-612 Support DICOM image to PD New Feature PDFANDROID-609 Extracting the text content from stamp annotation. New Feature PDFANDROID-571 PDF to XPS conversion problem New Feature PDFANDROID-613 Can&amp;rsquo;t add base64 image file format to pdf file Enhancement PDFANDROID-611 Add the ability to use an image file as the background of a table cell Enhancement PDFANDROID-605 Can&amp;rsquo;t visit images from pdf document Bug PDFANDROID-606 Metered license doesn&amp;rsquo;t work when convert pdf to image Bug PDFANDROID-607 Metered license doesn&amp;rsquo;t work when extracting text from pdf Bug PDFANDROID-608 Metered license doesn&amp;rsquo;t work when adding attachment to pdf Bug PDFANDROID-570 PDF to XLS conversion problem Bug PDFANDROID-603 Unable to convert PDF to Excel Bug PDFANDROID-600 Actualize information of third party components at Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>