<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.12
Key Summary Category CADNET-8909 DXF -&amp;gt; JPEG ArgumentOutOfRangeException Enhancement CADNET-8902 Aspose.CAD throwing exception in Docker Container for windows Enhancement CADNET-8901 Add tolerance symbols for SHX support Enhancement CADNET-8896 Missing lines during DWG -&amp;gt;PDF Enhancement CADNET-8880 Converting complex dwg to pdf Enhancement CADNET-8879 Add support for MTEXT fonts in line for SHX Enhancement CADNET-8860 The file &amp;lsquo;Campus All.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.11
Key Summary Category CADNET-8877 JS session host of WASM Enhancement CADNET-8822 FBX export runs too long Enhancement CADNET-8803 Export DWG to PDF Enhancement CADNET-8800 [Aspose.CAD] After converting DWG to PDF, the program crashes Enhancement CADNET-8790 DWG to PDF - modelspace rotation impacts on layout rendering?</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.10 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.10
Key Summary Category CADNET-8853 DXF to PDF Conversion Error Enhancement CADNET-8836 SHX font in DWG, export the square behind PDF Enhancement CADNET-8817 Wrongly exported hungarian special characters from DWG to PDF Enhancement CADNET-8804 Rendering issue in dwg file Enhancement CADNET-8754 Incorrect reading some symbols.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.9
Key Summary Category CADNET-8817 Wrongly exported hungarian special characters from DWG to PDF Enhancement CADNET-8816 DWG TO PDF OutOfMemoryError Enhancement CADNET-8690 Rework AntihackNamespaceDef Enhancement CADNET-8687 ImageLoadException on method CadImage.load(filePath) on java 1.7 Enhancement CADNET-8677 Empty DWG export result Enhancement CADNET-8658 Update WMF maximum image size Enhancement CADNET-8652 Getting ImageSaveException on macos Enhancement CADNET-8648 Improve sensitivity of scene moving Enhancement CADNET-8646 Check what is needed to implement font loading from DWFX Enhancement CADNET-8643 Abandon .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.8
Key Summary Category CADNET-8737 Render double-side planes Enhancement CADNET-8733 Preserve 3D wired models Enhancement CADNET-8719 Parse negative ID of normales and textures for OBJ Enhancement CADNET-8681 Add support for gbcbig01.shx Enhancement CADNET-8679 Some blocks missing after export Enhancement CADNET-8666 Add scaling up of watermark Enhancement CADNET-8598 I cannot load IGES image Enhancement CADNET-8568 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.7
Key Summary Category CADNET-8702 Some SHX symbols are missing Enhancement CADNET-8671 Text thickness normalization does not work for SHX Enhancement CADNET-8638 SHX width factor ignored for big font Enhancement CADNET-8636 Implement export to STEP format Enhancement CADNET-8628 Prepare gbcbig.shx changes for merge Enhancement CADNET-8621 Add support for tssdchn.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.6
Key Summary Category CADNET-8663 CAD Open / Save Issue Enhancement CADNET-8662 PNG Line widths Enhancement CADNET-8656 DWF to PDF does not convert all pages correct. Enhancement CADNET-8655 Export hangs for .net framework 4.8 and x64 Enhancement CADNET-8647 Lines are missing for Acrobat Reader but present in FoxIt Enhancement CADNET-8633 Unable to load APP S103 LAYOUT.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.5 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.5
Key Summary Category CADNET-8622 Mtext is not vertical Enhancement CADNET-8578 CadText and CadMText entities export takes a lot of time and leads to a memory leak. Enhancement CADNET-8577 CadHatch entities export takes a lot of time and leads to a memory leak. Enhancement CADNET-8564 Improve export DWG-&amp;gt;WMF Enhancement CADNET-8451 Enormous file size on export OBJ to DXF Enhancement CADNET-8434 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Cannot open an image.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.4
Key Summary Category CADNET-8615 Memory leak when converting from DXF to TIFF when using Aspose CAD 22.2 Enhancement CADNET-8599 Error When Saving DXF File Enhancement CADNET-8579 Dimension text position wrong, after conversion to PDF Enhancement CADNET-8569 Investigate cause of incorrect path processing in CADNET-1192 DWFX sample file Enhancement CADNET-8564 Improve export DWG-&amp;gt;WMF Enhancement CADNET-8559 Support export to PSD file format from IFC with on-the-fly algorithm Enhancement CADNET-8556 DWG/DXF export specific option to respect CTB file Enhancement CADNET-8550 Out of memory Converting a dwg to svg Enhancement CADNET-8490 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Unable to read DWF block&amp;rdquo; exception when open DWF file Enhancement CADNET-8482 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Cannot open an image.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.3 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.3
Key Summary Category CADNET-8587 Convert DWG to PDF eat 14G memory Enhancement CADNET-8576 Out of memory exception for .Net framework Enhancement CADNET-8572 IFC to PDF conversion performance for huge files (C# .NET) Enhancement CADNET-8571 Shifted layout occurs for DWG R13 Enhancement CADNET-8546 Fix ACIDCOMPLEXENTITY parsing for dxf file format Enhancement CADNET-8526 DAE to OBJ export failed Enhancement CADNET-8525 Export from SVG failed Enhancement CADNET-8524 Stack overflow on export from DWF to OBJ Enhancement CADNET-8522 Continue to improve dxf file saving to have a valid result that successfully opens with Autocad.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.2 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.2
Key Summary Category CADNET-8507 Aspose.Cad 21.12: &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Cannot open an image. The image file format may be not supported at the moment.&amp;rdquo; exception when opening PLT file Enhancement CADNET-8506 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Cannot open an image. The image file format may be not supported at the moment.&amp;rdquo; exception when opening PLT file Enhancement CADNET-8505 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Cannot open an image.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.1 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for .NET 22.1
Key Summary Category CADNET-8494 Content of the external DWG file is missing Enhancement CADNET-8414 Improve STL file processing Enhancement CADNET-8069 Implement Collada format support Enhancement CADNET-8309 PLT Image loading failed: Cannot open an image. The image file format may be not supported at the moment Enhancement CADNET-8336 How to get Polyline Segment Enhancement CADNET-1327 License fails intermittently in Azure function Enhancement</description></item></channel></rss>