<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 17.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 17.12 version
Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILJAVA-34325 Task and contact attachments converted to EML Enhancement EMAILNET-38774 Processing attached encrypted messages Bug EMAILNET-38867 HTML data/links not set properly in contact body Bug EMAILNET-38875 Formatting lost while converting EML to XPS Bug EMAILNET-38877 Attachments in EML file not detected by API Bug EMAILNET-38880 MSG to MHTML removes line spaces Bug EMAILNET-38882 MSG body Text formatting different than the source HTML Bug EMAILJAVA-34324 Converting EML to MSG calendar Item shifts date by local time difference Bug EMAILNET-38876 Outlook raises exception while loading MSG file converted by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 17.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 17.11 release.
Major Features Support to create, update and retrieve extended attributes information using EWS Support for raising events while working with sub-folders in a PST Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38844 EWS: Support for create, retrieve and update Extended Attributes for Emails New Feature EMAILNET-38855 Item moved event not fired for sub-folders Enhancement EMAILNET-38850 Imap client attachment names issue.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 17.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes of Aspose.Email for Java 17.10.
Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38574 Possibility of retrieving appointments with recurrences and dates filters Enhancement EMAILNET-38821 EWSClient.GetMailboxSize behaviour Enhancement EMAILNET-38823 Attachment name jibbrish on Non-Japanese Windows Bug EMAILNET-38670 EWS client can&amp;rsquo;t load emails in folders containing large number of messages. Bug EMAILNET-38827 MapiMessage.BodyHtml does not return correct value Bug EMAILNET-38828 Attached Word document in Outlook message is corrupted on Save Bug EMAILNET-38829 Multi-octet character split across adjacent encoded-word with UTF8 encoding Bug EMAILNET-38830 Mht empty when converting from msg with SkipInlineImages = true Bug EMAILNET-38831 Duplicated recipients when saving EML as MHTML Bug EMAILNET-38833 Content-disposition filename duplicated Bug EMAILJAVA-34309 Merging PST with sample PST loses Properties of Calendar Bug EMAILNET-38836 Creating message body from HTML includes header information in output Bug EMAILNET-38837 Converting EML to HTML resulting in incorrect HTML Bug EMAILNET-38838 After EML file is opened and re-saved, in output EML file From and Sender are null Bug EMAILJAVA-34307 Calendar added to PST doesn&amp;rsquo;t open in MS Outlook Bug EMAILNET-38841 Issues while using Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 17.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Email for Java 17.9.
Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38808 PSTs generated from Aspose much bigger in size Bug EMAILNET-38806 Aspose.Email is unable to process the EML file when it has extra line breaks in the message Bug EMAILNET-38807 EML to EMLx: Resultant message body not visible in Apple Mail Bug EMAILNET-38811 Pop3Client connection - thread leak.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 17.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Email for Java 17.8.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-34292 Ability to save images inside a message (as embedded image) as separate files next to html file while converting MSG to HTML Enhancement EMAILNET-38635 Add support Exchange 2016 Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34291 Pop3Client connection - process not finishing. Bug EMAILNET-38773 Smtp functionality with System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 17.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains information about Aspose.Email for Java 17.7.
Features and Improvements ID Description Category EMAILNET-38674 Support paging with MailQuery Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34280 Get mail size using Aspose.Email While working with Thunderbird (MboxrdStorageReader) Enhancement EMAILNET-38776 Behavior of API in case of attachment MSG file in TNEF Enhancement EMAILNET-38766 Read multiple events from a ICS file Enhancement EMAILNET-38767 Investigate ability to use web service for Exchange 2016 with more earlier versions of Exchange Enhancement EMAILNET-38772 FolderInfo.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 17.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains information about Aspose.Email for Java 17.6.
Features and Improvements Setting custom flag using Imap Option to render MSG to Mhtml without images for the sake of performance Provision of flag for hidden/cache folders retrieved from Exchange server Removing credentials from the activity log file Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38735 Set custom flag using Imap New Feature EMAILNET-38737 Option to render MSG to Mhtml without images for the sake of performance Enhancement EMAILNET-38747 Provision of flag for hidden/cache folders retrieved from Exchange server Enhancement EMAILNET-38761 Removing credentials from the activity log file Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34288 Exception TnefPropertyType.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 17.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
The API has now been upgraded to version 17.5.0 that comes with several new features, enhancements and improvements in terms of bug fixes as shown below.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 17.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
The API has now been upgraded to version 17.4.0 that comes with several new features, enhancements and improvements in terms of bug fixes as shown below.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 17.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
Features and Improvements Support for email threading Enum/class for possible values of FormatTemplates Key Summary Category EMAILNET-35022 Add support for email threading New Feature EMAILNET-38644 Provide enum or class for FormatTemplates possible values Enhancement EMAILJava-34230  Render contact information to MHTML Bug EMAILNET-38622 MSG to HTML: Alignment of table is shifted to right Bug EMAILNET-38630 Image attachment in eml is corrupted while opening it in Outlook Bug EMAILNET-38631 ICS extracted from EML contains empty line at the start Bug EMAILJAVA-34240 ReplyTo collection not read from MSG file (Java) Bug EMAILNET-38636 ReplyTo collection not read from MSG file Bug EMAILNET-38638 EML to MSG: Information disturbed in output Bug EMAILNET-38657 Loading MSG file is slower than 16.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 17.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38453 EWS: Retrieve Extended Properties for Items Enhancement EMAILNET-34620 Exclude the public MhtFormatter class Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34225 EML to MHTML: Provision to determine output From and To fields automatically Enhancement EMAILNET-38605 In MapiContact BirthDay, Anniversary etc.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 17.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-java-17-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38554 Create ListTasks method in EWS client Enhancement EMAILNET-38559 Provision of additional properties for Contact Enhancement EMAILNET-38561 Migrate from IExchangeClientBase.</description></item></channel></rss>