<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Font for .NET 21.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Font for .NET 21.12.
Problem with setting license under .NET 6.0 has been fixed.
Key Summary Category FONTNET-294 Incorrect calculation of transformation matrix for CFF fonts Bug FONTNET-288 SetLicense method throws an exception under .NET 6.0 Bug Got Queries? If you have any query related to Aspose.Font for .NET API, please feel free to write to reach us on Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Font for .NET 21.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Font for .NET 21.10.
Conversion functionality for CFF and WOFF2 format has been fixed.
Key Summary Category FONTNET-286 Incorrect calculation of transformation matrix for CFF fonts Bug FONTNET-274 Encoding problem for TTF to WOFF2 conversion Bug FONTNET-275 Null reference exception when converting font &amp;lsquo;OpenSans&amp;rsquo; from CFF to TTF format Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Added APIs Class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Font for .NET 21.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Font for .NET 21.8.
CFF to TTF/WOFF converters were added. All TTF and WOFF/WOFF2 tables&amp;rsquo; support was implemented.
Key Summary Category FONTNET-193 Support of CFF to TTF/WOFF converter New Feature FONTNET-237 Support all tables for TTF/WOFF formats New Feature FONTNET-244 Saving capability for all TTF/WOFF tables New Feature FONTNET-229 Problem in local table while saving WOFF2 file Bug FONTNET-238 OutOfMemoryException thrown while rendering glyths Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Added APIs Class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Font for .NET 21.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Font for .NET 21.4.
WOFF2 converting and saving support has been added. SHA-256 license type has been supported. Specific functionality for working with glyphs has been added.
Key Summary Category FONTNET-185 Combining characters from different fonts New Feature FONTNET-192 Support for converting to WOFF2 format New Feature FONTNET-213 Support for TTC fonts New Feature FONTNET-211 Support SHA-256 Licenses Enhancement FONTNET-181 Incorrect data in loca table after it was restored from WOFF2 file Bug FONTNET-229 Problems with loca table byte content in saved WOFF2 files Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Added APIs Enumeration member Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Font for .NET 21.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Font for .NET 21.2.
WOFF/WOFF2 formats have been added. .NETSTANDARD 2.1 and .NET 5 target framework support has been optimized. Some enhancements have been added.
Key Summary Category FONTNET-191 Support for reading WOFF2 format New Feature FONTNET-186 Redesign functionality for reading WOFF/WOFF2 formats Enhancement FONTNET-189 Extend the compress/decompress functionality Enhancement FONTNET-197 Optimize .</description></item></channel></rss>