<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2014 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2014 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 14.10.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-10-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-10-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 14.10.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 14.10 Release Notes Major Features There are 97 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved DocumentBuilder to handle mixed LTR/RTL text Improved breaking of floating tables in layout Improved custom tab stop beyond line ending Implemented new features and effects in DrawingML rendering Added LoadOptions.WebRequestTimeout property All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10037 HTML to Doc/Docx/XPS conversion issue with image/Shape rendering Bug WORDSNET-10047 FILENAME filed does not appear in output Pdf file Bug WORDSNET-10200 Issue with MailMerge.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 14.9.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-9-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-9-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 14.9.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 14.9 Release Notes Major Features There are 111 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
New reporting engine that allows to use LINQ Method Syntax in report templates Databinding for image SDTs is supported DrawingML is now a composite node (breaking change to the public API) DrawingML supports linked textboxes Rendering of &amp;lsquo;keep with next&amp;rsquo; paragraphs is improved Implemented &amp;lsquo;Use printer metrics to lay out document&amp;rsquo; compatibility option (Windows/GDI only) Improved tabs handling logic for Word 2013 and compatible modes in rendering Extrusion effect for DrawingML shapes rendering implemented (cold rendering) Rounding corners rendering in DrawingML charts implemented Improved 3D lighting rendering for WordArt objects Added support of Gradient background in HTML output All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10068 A DrawingML is converted to Shape Textbox during open/save a DOCX Bug WORDSNET-10091 Custom XML to SDT binding: images inside XML are not working Bug WORDSNET-10144 Color of text in Text Boxes is not preserved during open/save a DOCX Bug WORDSNET-10145 Gradient background colors of text boxes are not preserved during open/save a DOCX Bug WORDSNET-10209 Image position is incorectly exported to HTML Bug WORDSNET-10216 &amp;ldquo;Keep with next&amp;rdquo; option is not preserved during rendering Bug WORDSNET-10248 DrawingML TextBox is converted to Shape during open/save a DOCX Bug WORDSNET-10250 Drawing Canvas is changed to GroupShape after re-saving the Docx Bug WORDSNET-10262 Space between ListLabel and List item is increased after import StructuredDocumentTag Bug WORDSNET-10270 Custom XML to SDT binding issue with date and time format Bug WORDSNET-10282 Negative numbers are prefixed with a SPACES during mail merge Bug WORDSNET-10379 Shape alignment is changed after conversion from Docx to HTML Bug WORDSNET-10389 Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 14.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 14.8.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 14.8 Release Notes Major Features There are 75 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved how TOC field culture and formatting is handled Timestamping of PDF digital signature using external timestamp server implemented Improvements to advanced rendering features e.g. pre-blending semi-transparent images Horizontal rotation of characters having HorizontalRotatedFarEast orientation supported Improved page layout for additional compatibility modes Improved floater positioning in complex cases All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10074 /negative page margins/ Content wraps to the next page not like in Word Bug WORDSNET-10097 Shape becomes shifted down after DOCX-HTMl-DOCX round-trip Bug WORDSNET-10135 Contents move to next pages after conversion from Docx to fixed file format Bug WORDSNET-10189 Doc to Pdf conversion issue with text alignment in a cell Bug WORDSNET-10242 Leading spaces are lost after conversion from RTF to HTML Bug WORDSNET-10247 Contents move to next page after conversion from Doc to PDF Bug WORDSNET-10286 Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 14.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 14.7.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 14.7 Release Notes Major Features There are 114 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improvements to DrawingML shadow, extrusion and 3D rendering algorithms New public API to specify revision marks appearance for rendering Vertical text is supported in HTML, MHTML and EPUB Improvements to rendering and line wrapping for Arabic and Far East scripts Improvements to rendering of inline shapes within rotated text All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10032 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 14.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 14.6.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 14.6 Release Notes Major Features There are 104 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Support of automatic change tracking on a document Added vertical text support to HTML\Epub\MHT Footnote and endnote references now can be rendered as hyperlinks into output PDF CJK (Chinese, Japanese, Korean) text is now properly rendered in multiline DrawingML textboxes Default text AntiAliasing on Java is optimized for Chinese, Japanese and Korean fonts Font substitution feature is added to public API All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10026 DocumentBuilder.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 14.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 14.5.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 14.5 Release Notes Major Features There are 84 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved justification around inline paragraph breaks Hyphenation API updated and extended with a callback mechanism Table row wrapping around floaters in compatibility mode improved OOXML (MS Word 2010) Text effects rendering implemented Image export to HTML, MHTML and EPUB improved FitText attribute supported for all flow formats All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10020 /w:cr/ A Paragraph with Justified alignment is not rendering correctly in PDF Bug WORDSNET-10040 Docx to Pdf conversion issue with fonts (Open Type) Bug WORDSNET-10057 Last line of text wraps in the middle of words in PDF Bug WORDSNET-10058 Last line of text wraps in the middle of words in PDF Bug WORDSNET-10059 Leading line break of preformatted text is ignored during HTML import Bug WORDSNET-10062 DrawingML does not render in output Pdf file Bug WORDSNET-10063 Trailing whitespace of preformatted text is trimmed during HTML import Bug WORDSNET-10067 Text position is changed after conversion from Docx to Tiff file format Bug WORDSNET-10069 CoverPage layout changes when imported to another document Bug WORDSNET-10070 CoverPage layout changes when imported to another document Bug WORDSNET-10076 Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 14.4 Release Notes Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-4-release-notes-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-4-release-notes-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 14.4 Release Notes
Aspose.Words for .NET 14.4 Release Notes Major Features There are 78 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improvements to rendering of Arabic texts Improvements to rendering of complex document layouts Improved handling of themes, list styles and building blocks when joining documents Added support of text frames in ODT import/export Improvements in TXT import capabilities Gradient fill with transparency rendering in PDF implemented 3D rotated DrawingML shapes (and images) rendering implemented Better support of tab stops and underlines in HTML import/export All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10014 Logo in top left corners of pages is missing from Pdf Bug WORDSNET-6333 Language information of the &amp;lsquo;Field with CARDTEXT switch&amp;rsquo; is lost upon calling UpdateFields Bug WORDSNET-6355 Shape with BehindText wrapping is shifted towards right in HTML Bug WORDSNET-6600 Html to Doc conversion issue with table width, border and cell merge Bug WORDSNET-7974 Contents are misplaced after conversion from Doc to ODT Bug WORDSNET-8321 UpdateFields updates the REF field values incorrectly Bug WORDSNET-9412 Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 14.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 14.3.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 14.3 Release Notes Major Features There are 88 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Public API for insertion of OLE objects both linked and embedded Outline, Shadow, Reflection, Glow and Fill text effects for rendering text inside DrawingML shapes EUDC fonts rendering partially supported “PDF Logical Structure” export reworked, significantly improving memory usage All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-6074 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 14.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 14.2.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 14.2 Release Notes Major Features There are 118 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved export of tabs and tab stop positions to HTML Tab leaders are preserved when exporting to HTML Move revisions are supported in RTF Hyphenation is now supported in the layout engine (with external dictionaries) Drop caps positioning improved Improved rendering of hidden text Improved rendering of Asian text, ordering of Arabic punctuation marks DrawingML &amp;ldquo;Inner Shadow&amp;rdquo; effect rendering implemented Multiline watermark rendering supports &amp;ldquo;Fit to Bezier curves&amp;rdquo; cases Digitally signing XPS documents is possible now All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-2150 MS Word does not highlight white spaces.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 14.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-14-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 14.1.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 14.1 Release Notes Major Features There are 101 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Support for password-protected documents created in MS Word 2013 New public API to control rendering of tracking changes / revisions Reduced peak memory usage for large documents Performance improvements to the page layout engine Rendering of hidden text is improved Calculation of line height for Chinese characters improved Export comments to HTML as footnotes Export of drop-down fields and form fields as text into HTML Document headers and footers can now be preserved in DOC-HTML-DOC roundtrip DrawingML Soft Edge rendering effect implemented DrawingML preset shadows rendering implemented Hyperlink fragmentation in PDF resolved All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-3025 Some characters are not displayed during inserting.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 13.12.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-13-12-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-net-13-12-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 13.12.0
Aspose.Words for .NET has been updated to version 13.12.0 and we are pleased to announce this release brings the addition of 103 new useful improvements.
Using Aspose.Words for .NET you can work with DOC, OOXML, RTF, HTML, OpenDocument, PDF, XPS, EPUB and other formats in your applications. You can also view, generate, modify, convert, render and print documents all without using Microsoft Word.</description></item></channel></rss>