<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 18.12 - December 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 18.12.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-451 Relative path not working for ImageRenderOptions.AssetDirectory Bug THREEDNET-452 Add support for standard 3d printing format AMF  New Feature THREEDNET-454 Archive-based file format detection  Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 18.11 - November 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 18.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-429 Problem with UnitScaleFactor property Bug THREEDNET-447 Problem with Embedded Textures Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 18.10 - October 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 18.10.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-434 Support for .NET Core platform New Feature THREEDNET-431 Allow user to turn off compression when saving FBX binary files New Feature THREEDNET-424 Improve FBX import performance Enhancement THREEDNET-432 Improve FBX Binary write performance Enhancement THREEDNET-428 ImportException while opening huge FBX files Bug THREEDNET-429 Problem with UnitScaleFactor property Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 18.9 - September 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 18.9.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-414 CancellationToken support New Feature THREEDNET-423 FBX ExportException - High Polygon Count Bug THREEDNET-419 ImportException while opening huge FBX files Bug THREEDNET-421 Not all properties from FBX&amp;rsquo;s global settings are loaded into the AssetInfo Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 18.8 - August 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 18.8.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-409 Export glTF files with draco compression New Feature THREEDNET-401 Use Aspose.3D with Unity3D Bug THREEDNET-413 Read COLLADA files referencing in same folder Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 18.7 - July 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 18.7.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-405 Add Draco 2.2 import support New Feature THREEDNET-406 Add Draco 2.2 export support New Feature THREEDNET-408 Import glTF files with draco compression New Feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 18.6 - June 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 18.6.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category **  THREEDNET-387 Siemens JT Version 9 import support New Feature THREEDNET-393 FBX to GLTF - the output GLTF loader fails in three.js Bug THREEDNET-396 Input FBX - an import error occurred Bug THREEDNET-395 Rendering - the wrong operand type error Bug THREEDNET-399 RVM to glTF - an empty document is created Bug THREEDNET-398 RVM to WavefrontOBJ - an empty document is created Bug THREEDNET-400 Input FBX - Unsupported VertexElement attribute BinormalsIndex error occurred Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 18.5 - May 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 18.5.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-386 Siemens JT Version 8 import support New Feature THREEDNET-349 Investigation: Collada is missing Material ID Enhancement THREEDNET-392 Incorrect Quaternion and Euler angle rotation Bug THREEDNET-382 RVM to FBX - incomplete export of multi-site RVM Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 18.4 - April 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 18.4.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-376 Add skin controller export support in Collada New Feature THREEDNET-377 Add property animation support in Collada exporting New Feature THREEDNET-373 Add property animation support in Collada importing New Feature THREEDNET-375 Add skin controller import support in Collada New Feature THREEDNET-349 Collada is missing Material ID Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 18.3 - March 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 18.3.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-364 Order-independent transparency Enhancement THREEDNET-359 3DS to GLTF export throws an out of index error Bug THREEDNET-358 Cannot render model transparency Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 18.2 - February 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 18.2.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-335 Implement adding Targets to the MorphChannel New feature THREEDNET-348 Add support of skeleton/morphing animation exporting New feature THREEDNET-332 Add support for NURBS curve New feature THREEDNET-333 Add support for NURBS surface New feature THREEDNET-338 Add support of Pre/Post Rotation New feature THREEDNET-351 Cannot render transparency on PNG image of the scene Enhancement THREEDNET-334 Output FBX - the null pointer error occurred Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 18.1 - January 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-net-18-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 18.1.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-331 Add new entity - Rectangular torus support New feature THREEDNET-323 Import an ASE document New feature THREEDNET-327 Invalid transform for RVM file with multiple primitives under same node. Bug THREEDNET-325 RVM file with sloped cylinder is not supported.</description></item></channel></rss>