<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 18.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-113 Add support of Gif saving for Android Feature SLIDESJAVA-36712 Slow performance when exporting presentation to PDF Feature SLIDESANDROID-79 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 18.12 features Feature SLIDESJAVA-36722 Text is not exported to PDF Bug SLIDESJAVA-36887 Exception on loading presentation Bug SLIDESJAVA-36888 Exception on loading presentation Bug SLIDESJAVA-36889 Exception on loading presentation Bug SLIDESJAVA-36947 Date Changed after saving PPT to PPTX Bug SLIDESJAVA-37342 Wrong outline gradient direction Bug SLIDESJAVA-37352 Font changed after converting PPTX to PDF Bug SLIDESJAVA-37377 Spaces lost in generated Thumbnail Bug SLIDESJAVA-37404 Font substitution not rendering non-latin character-based languages correctly Bug SLIDESJAVA-37415 PPTX not properly converted to PDF Bug SLIDESJAVA-37416 PPTX not properly converted to PDF Bug Public API Changes No change</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 18.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESJAVA-37110 OutOfMemoryError on loading presentation Investigation SLIDESJAVA-37317 Classes inside the Aspose.Slides Investigation SLIDESJAVA-36732 RCA for sample failing in 16.11 but working in 17.12 Investigation SLIDESJAVA-37295 Exception on adding sections Investigation SLIDESANDROID-77 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 18.11 features Feature SLIDESANDROID-118 Add support of Tiff format for Android Feature SLIDESJAVA-37272 Support for setting callout shape for series data label Feature SLIDESJAVA-37135 Use Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 18.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-75 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 18.10 features Feature SLIDESJAVA-37101 Uknown Field type returned for Field Enhancement SLIDESNET-37354 Support for rendering shape Soft Edges (EffectFormat) effect Enhancement SLIDESNET-40366 Turning off updates automatically option for Date time in PPT while converting to PDF Feature SLIDESNET-40544 Connector fails to draw in straight line Feature SLIDESJAVA-35696 PPT document failed to load Bug SLIDESJAVA-35894 Exception on loading PPTX Bug SLIDESJAVA-37011 OutOfMemory is thrown for converting to PDF Bug SLIDESJAVA-37311 Connector draws wrong Bug SLIDESJAVA-37322 Slide not properly rendered Bug SLIDESJAVA-37329 Empty table cells return 0 portions Bug SLIDESJAVA-37332 Charts are missing in exported PDF Bug Public API Changes No change</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 18.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-18-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-18-9-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-18 Support for Presentation to PDF Conversion in Aspose.Slides for Android Feature SLIDESANDROID-25 Create images of a Slide in a PPTX file Feature SLIDESANDROID-32 converting slide to images Feature SLIDESANDROID-96 Implement Graphics.DrawString methods for Android Feature SLIDESANDROID-98 Implement TextureBrush for Android Feature SLIDESANDROID-100 Implement LinearGradientBrush for Android Feature SLIDESANDROID-114 Add support of Metafiles for Android Feature SLIDESANDROID-73 Use Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 18.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-18-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-18-2-release-notes/</guid><description>
This is restricted Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 18.2 version based on Aspose.Slides for Java 18.2. It supports the following features.
Open existing and create new presentations. Access and edit presentation parts. Save presentations (restricted). The following features are not supported yet.
Create slide thumbnails. Export to PDF, XPS, and other formats.</description></item></channel></rss>