<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 22.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 22.12
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10883 Extra empty sheets appear at export Enhancement CADJAVA-10877 DXF to PDF Conversion Error Enhancement CADJAVA-10867 Read IFC metadata Enhancement CADJAVA-10866 Add support for MTEXT fonts in line for SHX Enhancement CADJAVA-10859 Add tolerance symbols for SHX support Enhancement CADJAVA-10858 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 22.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 22.11
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10829 DXF to JPEG results in a cropped image in Amazon Linux 2 Enhancement CADJAVA-10827 Implement conversion of DWG format from Inverter to standard DWG format Enhancement CADJAVA-10826 Implement change of ViewPort properties and entity position when converting to a standard DWG file. Enhancement CADJAVA-10825 DWG to PDF - modelspace rotation impacts on layout rendering?</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 22.10 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 22.10
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10771 Aspose.CAD v22.4: Size options were not applied when converting CAD documents Enhancement CADJAVA-10758 Converting DXF to JPG takes very long time Enhancement CADJAVA-10757 Add support for ignoring layers in 3D models Enhancement CADJAVA-10756 Incorrect reading some symbols. Enhancement CADJAVA-10750 Containerization on Linux Enhancement CADJAVA-10748 Convert IfcSlab type to 3D Enhancement CADJAVA-10747 Exception with 22.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 22.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 22.9
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10733 Fix triangulation issue for 3D pipeline Enhancement CADJAVA-10732 Improve processes of reading and exporting for dwf files. Enhancement CADJAVA-10712 Improve sensitivity of scene moving Enhancement CADJAVA-10711 Getting ImageSaveException on macos Enhancement CADJAVA-10710 Update WMF maximum image size Enhancement CADJAVA-10612 DWG TO PDF OutOfMemoryError Enhancement CADJAVA-10611 DXF Linux conversion error 22.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 22.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 22.8
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10687 Aspose.CAD 22.1: Wrong layout when converting particular DWG Enhancement CADJAVA-10684 Add support for gbcbig01.shx Enhancement CADJAVA-10683 Issue publishing second time Enhancement CADJAVA-10682 Parse negative ID of normales and textures for OBJ Enhancement CADJAVA-10679 Preserve 3D wired models Enhancement CADJAVA-10678 Render double-side planes Enhancement CADJAVA-10676 Test and prepare changes for OBJ to 3D export Enhancement CADJAVA-10690 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 22.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 22.7
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10649 Improve performance of view Enhancement CADJAVA-10648 Add support for hztxt.shx Enhancement CADJAVA-10647 Add support for tssdchn.shx Enhancement CADJAVA-10646 Prepare gbcbig.shx changes for merge Enhancement CADJAVA-10643 Implement export to STEP format Enhancement CADJAVA-10642 SHX width factor ignored for big font Enhancement CADJAVA-10638 Text thickness normalization does not work for SHX Enhancement CADJAVA-10637 Some SHX symbols are missing Enhancement CADJAVA-10599 Out of memory Converting a dwg to svg Enhancement CADJAVA-10506 I cannot load IGES image Enhancement CADJAVA-10505 Bad display of SHX fonts Enhancement CADJAVA-10425 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: FieldDecoderAscii.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 22.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 22.6
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10625 Implement DXB format support Enhancement CADJAVA-10623 Add cancellation support on document load for CAD files with Venture licenser support. Enhancement CADJAVA-10622 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Cannot process loading further due to incorrect file format structure.&amp;rdquo; exception when open DWG file. Enhancement CADJAVA-10621 Unable to Open attached file Enhancement CADJAVA-10620 Cropped image output Enhancement CADJAVA-10619 Weekly activities 01.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 22.5 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 22.5
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10569 Mtext is not vertical Enhancement CADJAVA-10508 Convert DWG to PDF eat 14G memory Enhancement CADJAVA-10331 Failed to save DWF file as PDF Enhancement CADJAVA-774 Unable to read Dwf content: Error on reading hoops object exception when loading DWF Enhancement CADJAVA-584 Digital sign support by ECDSA and RSA algorithms for updated drawings Enhancement CADJAVA-10330 Failed to load PLT file Enhancement CADJAVA-10329 Failed to save Obj file as svg Enhancement CADJAVA-10300 DWG to PNG export has line color issues Enhancement CADJAVA-919 Chinese can not display right when export to DWG Enhancement CADJAVA-862 NullPointerException on saving Aspsoe sample DXF Enhancement CADJAVA-737 DWG to PDF conversion hangs and leaks memory Enhancement CADJAVA-10279 Quality of images generated with Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 22.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 22.4
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10604 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Unknown &amp;quot; exception when opening DWF file Enhancement CADJAVA-10603 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Object reference not set to an instance of an object.&amp;rdquo; exception when open IFC file Enhancement CADJAVA-10602 &amp;ldquo;The given key &amp;lsquo;ACADVER&amp;rsquo; was not present in the dictionary&amp;rdquo; exception when rendering to SVG Enhancement CADJAVA-10601 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Unable to read DWF block&amp;rdquo; exception when open DWF file Enhancement CADJAVA-10598 DWG/DXF export specific option to respect CTB file Enhancement CADJAVA-10595 Support export to PSD file format from IFC with on-the-fly algorithm Enhancement CADJAVA-10590 Investigate cause of incorrect path processing in CADNET-1192 DWFX sample file Enhancement CADJAVA-10586 Dimension text position wrong, after conversion to PDF Enhancement CADJAVA-10577 Error When Saving DXF File Enhancement CADJAVA-10572 Fix glyph size Enhancement CADJAVA-10533 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Cannot open an image.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 22.3 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 22.3
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10541 Fix transparency issue for binary dxf Enhancement CADJAVA-10536 PLT=&amp;gt;PDF Conversion hangs without error message Enhancement CADJAVA-10535 Specific DWG file rendered blank, but output data is present. Enhancement CADJAVA-10534 &amp;ldquo;Image export failed. Object reference not set to an instance of an object.&amp;rdquo; exception when rendering DWF to PNG Enhancement CADJAVA-10532 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: The Dxf version isn&amp;rsquo;t valid.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 22.2 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 22.2
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10507 DXF Linux conversion error Enhancement CADJAVA-10481 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: String &amp;lsquo;-17790918:104545&amp;rsquo; was not recognized as a valid DateTime.&amp;rdquo; exception when open IGS file Enhancement CADJAVA-10479 &amp;ldquo;Parameter is not valid&amp;rdquo; exception when rendering DWG file to PNG Enhancement CADJAVA-10478 Positive and negative validation of Antihack functionality as blackbox integration tests Enhancement CADJAVA-10477 After convert DWG to SVG some point is different from source Enhancement CADJAVA-10476 Default fallback font Enhancement CADJAVA-10473 Get page size/dimenstions from DWF Enhancement CADJAVA-10472 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Cannot open an image.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 22.1 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-cad-for-java-22-1-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 22.1
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10461 Implement Collada format support Enhancement CADJAVA-10458 Improve STL file processing Enhancement CADJAVA-10395 setDrawColor Still not working Enhancement CADJAVA-10460 PLT Image loading failed: Cannot open an image. The image file format may be not supported at the moment Enhancement CADJAVA-10462 License fails intermittently in Azure function Internal CADJAVA-10459 How to get Polyline Segment Internal CADJAVA-10222 The problem with Block reference Internal</description></item></channel></rss>