<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.12.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-788 Provide ability to save multi-volume ZIP. Feature ZIPNET-943 Compose SHAR archive. Feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description Aspose.Zip.Saving.SplitArchiveSaveOptions Options for saving a multi-volume zip archive.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.11.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-946 Release file handle on 7z decryption with wrong password. Bug ZIPNET-930 Proper compression and encryption coder combination within 7z archive. Bug ZIPNET-935 Report progress of compression for 7z entry. Enhancement ZIPNET-922 Support PPMd compression within 7z archive. Feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.10.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-931 Fetch entry comment within zip container. Feature ZIPNET-929 Get rid of System.Drawing.Common. Enhancement ZIPNET-934 Display modification time for 7z entry. Enhancement ZIPNET-933 Extract to stream method for 7z entry. Enhancement ZIPNET-928 Set arbitrary encoding on zip archive extraction.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.9.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-313 Parallel BZip2 compression. Feature ZIPNET-914 XZ compression for zip container. Feature ZIPNET-923 Verify RAR password on decompression. Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.8.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-913 Set the number of fast bytes for LZMA2 compression. Enhancement ZIPNET-905 Introduced metered license. Feature ZIPNET-917 Drop obsolete UnRAR namespace and classes. Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.7.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-895 Support Snappy algorithm. Feature ZIPNET-904 Compress cpio archives to GZip, BZip2 and XZ. Feature ZIPNET-893 Respect tar and cpio formats while saving those archives to BZip2. Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.6.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-862 Support Enhanced Deflate within ZIP container. Feature ZIPNET-857 Extract WIM with LZMS compression. Feature ZIPNET-870 Extract particular entry within 7z archive. Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.5.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-878 Fix multi-folder 7z extraction. Bug ZIPNET-875 Respect .NET 6 breaking changes. Enhancement ZIPNET-837 Extract XAR archive. Feature ZIPNET-855 Extract WIM archives with Xpress compression. Feature ZIPNET-843 Extract WIM archives with LZX compression. Feature ZIPNET-889 Implement LZMA archive format.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.3.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-858 Run program after self-extracting archive is extracted. Feature ZIPNET-865 Fix wrong offset of local file header for zip64 archives. Bug ZIPNET-859 Fix bug with delayed extraction. Bug ZIPNET-869 Fix extracting encrypted RAR5 in .NET6. Bug ZIPNET-766 Extract CAB archives compressed using LZX and Deflate algorithms.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-zip-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 22.1.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-832 Extract Z archives. Enhancement ZIPNET-841 Bug on cpio extraction. Bug ZIPNET-840 Bug on tar extraction. Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public methods and properties were added: Description Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>