<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.12.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the December release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have made various improvements to our parsing and saving algorithms, here are some of them:
Improved the HTML parsing algorithm, now it processes attribute names according to the latest documentation.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.11.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the November release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have made various improvements to our rendering engine, here are some of them:
Improved processing of different unit types during the CSS media query parsing algorithm. Updated the whitespace collapsing algorithm according to the latest documentation.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.10.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the October release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have made various improvements to our rendering and scraping algorithms, here are some of them:
Improved the positioning of PDF form elements. Introduced the new page sizing options, they allow to resize page to fit content.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.9.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the September release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have made various improvements to our rendering algorithm, here are some of them:
Improved splitting of the large images. Updated the user agent style sheets according to the latest documentation.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.8.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the August release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have made many improvements to our MHTML processing algorithm, here are some of them:
Introduced the ability to change properties of the output PDF documents. Increased the accuracy of font relative size calculation algorithm.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.7.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the July release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have made many improvements to our web page saver, here are some of them:
Increased the accuracy of absolutely positioned elements rendering. Introduced the new resource handling option, which allows to ignore certain resources.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.6.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the June release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have made many improvements to our rendering algorithms, here are some of them:
Improved the processing of images which have zero dimensions; Increased the performance of the CSS processing algorithm by 40%; Introduced the support of flex columns; Increased the accuracy of the bounding box calculation algorithm; Introduced the support of JavaScript named property getters.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.5.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the May release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have made many improvements to our splitting algorithms, here are some of them:
Improved the processing of forced breaks in the line splitting algorithm; Updated the font aliases matching algorithm according to the latest documentation; Extended the support of complex font styles used during the conversion to DOCX; Increased the accuracy of collapsed blocks width calculation algorithm; Improved the positioning of splitted flex elements.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-4-release-note/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-4-release-note/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.4.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the April release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have made various improvements to our saving algorithms, here are some of them:
improved the float elements splitting algorithm; introduced the ability to save documents and their resources to streams; improved the processing of special characters in file names; improved the gradient serialization algorithm; introduced the multimedia scraping classes.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.3.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the March release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have improved various aspect of our serialization and size calculation algorithms, here are some of them:
increased the accuracy of flex element size calculation algorithm; updated the SVG and XHTML serialization algorithms according to the latest documentation; improved the body background rendering and size calculation algorithms.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.2.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the February release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release we have improved various aspects of our IO systems, here are some of them:
updated the URL parsing algorithm according to the latest documentation; improved the path resolution algorithm, now it correctly encodes special characters; introduced the ability to control entities loading; improved the XPS and image validation algorithms, now they correctly create large output files.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-html-for-net-21-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 21.1.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the January release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release we have improved various elements of rendering and JavaScript engines, here are some of them:
improved the table splitting algorithm; introduced DOMTokenList support; extended jQuery support; improved the counter processing algorithm.</description></item></channel></rss>