<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 16.12.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-16-12-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-16-12-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 16.12.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-51081 Add support to modify the individual gradient stop. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-51071 The gradient color of the shape is not being preserved on saving in VSDX. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51075 The gradient color of circle shape is not shown on saving in VSDX.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 16.11.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-16-11-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-16-11-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 16.11.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50221 Add support to insert text labels. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-51000 Performance issue with exporting a VSD to PDF. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-51095 Can&amp;rsquo;t add shape menu item (action). Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50344 VSDX to PDF conversion, incorrect sequence of line breaks in the text items.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 16.10.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-16-10-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-16-10-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 16.10.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50545 Master-Ability to add masters without a stencil, diagram or template. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-50192 VSD to PDF conversion, the text of the shape appears not bold. Bug DIAGRAMNET-50524 Shape.GluedShapes method call is not returning all shape ids. Bug DIAGRAMNET-50578 VSDX to PDF conversion, the connecting lines are not straight-I.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.8.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50946 Add support of inserting ActiveX controls in the Visio Page. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-51003 Add support to set color checkbox of the layer. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-50026 The shapes are missing from VSDX drawing. Bug DIAGRAMNET-50781 The small icons of the tables are missing on saving a VSDX to PDF.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.7.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50136 VSD to PDF conversion - the red cross image appears instead of the shape. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50324 VSD to HTML conversion - the background color of the shape is not preserved. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50500 VSD to PDF conversion - the Color of the shapes are not preserved.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.6.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50156 Add support to import the macro enabled Drawing (.VSDM). New Feature DIAGRAMNET-50332 Add support to replace the OLE object. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-50566 Writing support for new MS Visio Macro-Enabled Drawing 2013 VSDM format. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-50567 Writing support for new MS Visio Macro-Enabled Stencil 2013 VSSM format.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.5.0
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50555 Can&amp;rsquo;t retrieve connections from VSS stencil file. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50699 Support loading comment for vsd file. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50340 VSDX to PDF conversion, the arrows of dynamic connectors are not preserved. Bug DIAGRAMNET-50341 VSDX to HTML conversion, the arrows of dynamic connectors are not preserved.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50766 VSD to PDF export - the color of circles inside the traffic signal boxes is not preserved. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50767 VSD to PDF export - Dashed lines are converted to solid lines. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50044 Misplaced text or incorrect line breaks when converting VSD to PDF format. Bug DIAGRAMNET-50178 VSD to PDF conversion, Shape&amp;rsquo;s text with incorrect wrapping/layout.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50739 Add support of detecting the Visio diagram type. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-50746 Prevent export of the hidden Visio pages in the PDF. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-50747 Prevent export of the hidden Visio pages in the HTML. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-50750 Prevent export of the hidden Visio pages in the PNG. New Feature DIAGRAMNET-50751 Prevent export of the hidden Visio pages in the JPEG.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50316 Can&amp;rsquo;t get 2D shape ids when called Shape.GluedShapes method. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50377 VSD to VDX conversion - missing or misplaced text items. Bug DIAGRAMNET-50445 VSD to PDF conversion - form menu text &amp;ldquo;options&amp;rdquo; is duplicated. Bug DIAGRAMNET-50581 VSDX to PDF conversion - the text item of the shape is slightly misplaced.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Other Improvements and Changes This release introduces the features, enhancements and bug fixes as detailed below:
Key Summary Category DIAGRAMNET-50570 Add support to modify comments in the Visio diagram. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50665 ImageSaveOptions.ImageBrightness property does not work. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50684 VSD to SVG export does not preserve the shape IDs. Enhancement DIAGRAMNET-50188 VSD to PDF export adds an extra word &amp;ldquo;text&amp;rdquo; in the shape&amp;rsquo;s text.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for .NET 6.0.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-0-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-net-6-0-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This release introduces the features, enhancements and bug fixes as detailed below:
Enhancements DIAGRAMNET-50551-Add support of loading VSSX format file in the Diagram class  DIAGRAMNET-50617-Add support to determine two shapes are glued or connected  DIAGRAMNET-50641-VSD to VDX export, missing shadow of the shapes Bugs DIAGRAMNET-50303-VSD to PDF export, empty PDF having white spot is generated  DIAGRAMNET-50466-VSD to VDX conversion, curve dynamic connectors turn into stright  DIAGRAMNET-50472-VSD to HTML conversion, the text shape is misplaced  DIAGRAMNET-50473-VSD to PDF conversion, the text &amp;ldquo;Iloprost&amp;rdquo; is added in header of all pages  DIAGRAMNET-50474-VSD to PDF conversion, the list items are misplaced  DIAGRAMNET-50480-VSD to HTML conversion, the text &amp;ldquo;Iloprost&amp;rdquo; is added in header of all pages  DIAGRAMNET-50622-Can&amp;rsquo;t detect incoming nodes of the connected shapes  DIAGRAMNET-50623-Geometry of the connector shapes is incorrect  DIAGRAMNET-50624-Geometry of the connector shapes is incorrect  DIAGRAMNET-50629-Output format HTML] - Can&amp;rsquo;t place a group shape from another Visio diagram  DIAGRAMNET-50634-Copying a Visio diagram page operation does not preserve style of the shapes  DIAGRAMNET-50635-Copying a Visio diagram page does not preserve shapes completely  DIAGRAMNET-50636-Copying a Visio diagram page does not preserve shapes completely  DIAGRAMNET-50639-VDX to VDX export, shape&amp;rsquo;s text is not bold  DIAGRAMNET-50652-Source VSD - ConnectCollection class returns additional connect and incorrect shape ids  DIAGRAMNET-50654-Shape.</description></item></channel></rss>