<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.12.
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the December release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release we have made a number of improvements related to documents saving, these improvements include:
Improved serialization algorithm according to the latest HTML documentation Improved document saving by the introduction of HTML entities support Fixing Issue with CSS Import Rule processing and its relative URL resolution You can share your queries and feedback with us by visiting Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-11-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes information for Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.11.
Improvements and Changes As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the November release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release, we have made some improvements related to rendering quality. These improvements include:
Addition of scripts support to template merging, which allows creating interactive documents Increased quality of MHTML rendering by implementing processing of resources referenced by content ID More precise rendering of table layouts Support of input elements &amp;ldquo;type&amp;rdquo; attribute according to the latest documentation Key Summary Category HTMLNET-2220 MHT to XPS crash during conversion Bug HTMLNET-2188 ArgumentException while converting HTML file to PDF Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.10.
As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the October release of Aspose.HTML for .NET.
In this release, we have implemented a set of features that will increase the quality of text rendering. The most significant of them is Kerning. Kerning is used to adjust the spacing between character and it&amp;rsquo;s supported by a majority of fonts.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.9
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the September release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release, we added support for CSS Drop Shadows functional, located and fixed the text alignment issue for some specific cases when the text is inside the table cells and made some internal bug fixes and exceptions processing for MHTML and HTML files.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-8-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.8
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the August release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release, we have made some internal bug fixes that include the processing of table elements, rendering rounded borders of elements and integration HTML DOM elements with JavaScript.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLNET-2036 HTML to PDF Landscape conversion fails Investigation HTMLNET-2078 An exception is thrown when loading HTML to PDF with a max-width set Bug HTMLNET-2025 The table radius borders are not honoring the background color properties Bug HTMLNET-2089 On loading HTML files the Null Reference Exception is throw Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.7
As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honoured to announce the July release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release, we have made some internal bug fixes that include the rendering of the background color for particular elements, rendering of the &amp;lsquo;right-to-left&amp;rsquo; fonts and memory leaks inside ePub and MHTML documents.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.6 Release Notes As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the June release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release, we have introduced a new function of conversion from Markdown, which is developed as an easy-to-read, easy-to-write plain text format, to HTML document. Along with the new functional, we did improvements in processing table elements and revised the MHTML document process.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-5-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.5 Release Notes As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honoured to announce the May release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release, we have introduced a new function that is called &amp;lsquo;Template Merging&amp;rsquo;. This function is used to create HTML documents based on user templates and populate them from the various data sources. Additionally, we have prepared a specialized &amp;lsquo;Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.4 Release Notes We are pleased to announce that our JavaScript Engine has been completely reworked and now it is integrated with Jint project which provides full ECMA 5.1 compliance and many features from ECMAScript 6.0. Along with improvement JavaScript Engine and performance itself, we extended &amp;ldquo;User Agent Service&amp;rdquo; by adding ability to customize the font lookup folders.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLNET-1810 HTML to PDF - Images do not render Bug HTMLNET-1830 Rendering to PDF/XPS some input data causes exception Bug HTMLNET-1800 Margins of SVG images change together with HTML Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.3 Release Notes As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honoured to announce the March release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release, we have focused on improving the quality and performance of &amp;ldquo;Font Selection and Fallback&amp;rdquo; algorithm. Apart from that, we revised dependencies for .NET Standard library type.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLNET-1764 Remove Microsoft.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-2-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.2 Release Notes As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honoured to announce the February release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release, we have made some internal bug fixes related to the document rendering and page splitting algorithms.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLNET-1629 Problem repeating header on each page Bug HTMLNET-1736 An exception raises while loading an HTML file Bug HTMLNET-1550 Problem converting HTML to PDF Bug Added APIs: Added the overridden method ICSSStyleDeclaration.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-net-19-1-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for .NET 19.1 Release Notes As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the January release of Aspose.HTML for .NET. In this release, we have focused on issues related to improving performance and decreasing memory consumption. Apart from that we have made some internal bug fixes related to Cascading Style Sheets processing.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLNET-1520 Problems converting HTML to PDF Bug HTMLNET-1671 Memory leak upon MHT conversion Bug</description></item></channel></rss>