<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 17.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-12-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-849 Support for converting CMYK PSD to CMYK TIFF Feature IMAGINGJAVA-870 TypeTool6ResourceProcessor.ReplaceTextInGlobalResources does not work Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-869 Incorrect condition statement in DgImage.RawProcess Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-868 Incorrect condition statement in DgImage.Unpack Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-867 Improve Djvu performance Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-866 Corrupted DngImage.Width and DngImage.Height after calling the Image.GetPixel method Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-865 GIF image is not properly converted to Png Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-864 Incorrect number conversion in OpenDocument support class: OdEnhancedGeometryReader.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 17.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-825 Aspose.Imaging 17.6.0 : Managing resources while saving Metafile images as SVG Feature IMAGINGJAVA-824 Saving SVG with fonts embedded or exported Feature IMAGINGJAVA-823 Add support for color replacement in PSD layers Feature IMAGINGJAVA-822 Support for ODG (OpenDocument graphics) Feature IMAGINGJAVA-821 Support for the combination of ColorType as Grayscale &amp;amp; CompressionType as Progressive for the JpegOptions class Feature IMAGINGJAVA-789 Add possibility to force fonts cache update Feature IMAGINGJAVA-736 Provide setting for replacing missing fonts Feature IMAGINGJAVA-820 PSD Conversion CMYK to RGB with alpha channel doesn&amp;rsquo;t work.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 17.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-9-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-789 Add possibility to force fonts cache update Feature IMAGINGJAVA-765 Support for CMYK, YCCK color modes in JPEG Lossless. Feature IMAGINGJAVA-585 Implementation of Lossy GIF Compressor Feature IMAGINGJAVA-790 Fix exception when PSD text layer update is performed on previously saved PSD with updated text layer, using RemoveGlobalTextEngineResource option Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-782 Unable to get width and height of DNG image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-778 Corrupted, partially or completely invisible watermark for particularly saved images.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 17.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-7-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-750 Investigate and fix differences in Fonts in Adobe Photoshop and GDI+(Aspose.Imaging) rendering Feature IMAGINGJAVA-749 Need to support gray scale with alpha for PSD. Feature IMAGINGJAVA-754 Wrong text color when using Graphics.DrawString to add watermark Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-753 Image is recolored when using Graphics.DrawImage Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-752 Examine partial processing mechanism implemented in JPEG DCT loader.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 17.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-6-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-736 Provide setting for replacing missing fonts  Feature IMAGINGJAVA-733 Support for 2-7 bits per sample in JPEG-LS images.  Feature IMAGINGJAVA-732 Support for JPEG-LS with CMYK, YCCK color modes.  Feature IMAGINGJAVA-709 Support for Raster Image to SVG Conversion  Feature IMAGINGJAVA-708 Support for JPEG-LS format  Feature IMAGINGJAVA-735 Synchronize access to mutually exclusive image operations for WEBP images  Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-734 Loading SVG image from XML file and then converting the SVG to PNG is showing incorrect height &amp;amp; width  Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-731 Improve performance saving WMF to WMF  Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-724 The pattern protrudes after conversion PSD to PNG (and JPG) Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-723 The background turns to black when converting PSD file to JPG and PNG format.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 17.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-4-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-685 Implementation of rate control algorithm for Aspose.Imaging Jpeg-2000 codec Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-684 TIFF images with JPEG compression should support all possible bits per sample combinations Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-683 Improve quality when resized Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-682 Converting SVG to raster image (PNG in this case) file is showing blank resultant PNG file Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-681 Support for converting SVG to PDF Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-680 Converting SVG to PNG image is not showing proper shapes in PNG file Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-679 Improve memory usage of DNG file format Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-678 Saving of large PNG images leads to black resulting images Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-677 Stream is unexpectedly closed in multithreaded environment Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-676 Emf image is not converted properly Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-643 FontSettings.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 17.03 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-03-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-03-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for Java has been updated to version 17.03 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-660 Subsequent reading of scan line data for PNG image produces a different results - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-659 Incorrect working of LoadArgb32Pixels - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-658 Djvu converted to PDF successfully but it took a long time to convert - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-657 Syncronize access to mutually exclusive image operations for JPEG2000 images - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-656 Syncronize access to mutually exclusive image operations for PNG images - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-655 Syncronize access to mutually exclusive image operations for PSD images - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-654 Syncronize access to mutually exclusive image operations for BMP images - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-653 Syncronize access to mutually exclusive image operations for GIF images - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-652 The PNG codec research regarding increase in productivity - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-651 Syncronize access to mutually exclusive image operations for JPEG images - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-650 Exporting JPEG image into BMP file format fails -Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-649 Investigate problem with saving TIFF image frames in multithreading environment - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-648 Modifying and updatding TIFF image stream is not working properly - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-647 Memory leak when load multiple images from MemoryStream - Java Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-629 Converting PSD to image is throwing exception Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-584 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 17.01 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-01-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-imaging-for-java-17-01-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-598 DNG format support New Feature IMAGINGJAVA-597 ThreadSafe API support stage 1 New Feature IMAGINGJAVA-599 Thread safe API for TIFF images Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-594 Updating text layer with non-English characters using Aspose, the characters are replaced by box Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-593 [Updating text layer with many more characters than the source is showing incorrect results](https://www.</description></item></channel></rss>