<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.12.
Major Features There are 108 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Java 11 compatibility is checked and updated. ExternalImageLibTest utility class added to check external image libraries on user side. Implemented WMF fonts scaling, according to metafile size on the page, and public option to control it (MetafileRenderingOptions.ScaleWmfFontsToMetafileSize). Improved the default font fallback mechanism to better fit the MW behavior.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.10.
Major Features There are 84 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
API&amp;rsquo;s codebase is upgraded to the version Aspose.Words for Java 18.10 Aspose.Words for Java is FIPS compliant now. The single sentence &amp;lsquo;SecuritySettings.startFipsMode()&amp;rsquo; switches current Aspose.Words thread to the FIPS mode. Support Conholdate.Total for Java licensing system. Compatibility within GroupDocs Total package is improved.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.7.
Major Features There are 90 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
API&amp;rsquo;s codebase is upgraded to the version Aspose.Words for Java 18.7. New typed (generic) collections and enumerators were introduced in Aspose.Words public API Added public property HeaderFooterBookmarksExportMode in PdfSaveOptions  Added FontSourceBase.GetAvailableFonts method  Added public API for revision groups  Introduced new comparison settings  A new limo stretch algorithm for VML shapes rendering was developed, which most accurately repeats the output of MS Word (limo-stretched shapes) Public property OutlineOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.5.
Major Features There are 70+ improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
API&amp;rsquo;s codebase is upgraded to the latest version of Aspose.Words for Java. Added public property StructuredDocumentTag.Color  Improved logic to detect the encoding of a short TXT file. Fixed line wrapping with trailing spaces at the end Fixed issue with paragraph after spacing in headers/footers Fixed issue with table width when widthAfter is specified for a jagged table Fixed issue with table width with complex column layout and default widths Fixed breaking of floating table row in compatibility mode Fixed issue with floating frame pushed from the page because of invalid wrap point Implemented support for &amp;ldquo;distribute space&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;distribute letter&amp;rdquo; types of alignment when rendering Ruby objects Improved rendering of a Doughnut DrawingML Chart with multiple series Improved rendering of DrawingML Charts data labels with the direct layout and a layout specified in the extension properties Fixed a problem with metafile rendering when glyph offsets were wrongly read for EMF_EXTTEXTOUT record with glyph indices Fixed a problem with processing of control character (U+0019) in the text when rendering Fixed a problem with Adobe “Fast Find” function (words searching) in rendered PDF documents Fixed a bug with inaccurate processing of EMR_ALPHABLEND record while rendering metafiles.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.4.
Major Features There are 70+ improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added public Ref&amp;lt;T&amp;gt; class for out/ref emulation in public API. Provide an ability to work with password-protected ODT and OTT file formats Preserve PaperTray information in PCL  Added ShapeBase.IsLayoutInCell property  Implemented optimization of metafile rendering vector output.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.3.
Major Features There are 70+ improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Public API to get Subject and Issuer names from DigitalCertificate (instead obsolete properties). Add support of CssClassNamesPrefix in HtmlSaveOptions A number of obsolete properties were removed from PdfSaveOptions class. Please refer to public API changes section for details PdfSaveOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.2.
Major Features There are 100+ improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
FontSettings.EnableFontSubstitution option added Support to insert Style Separator to put different Paragraph styles HtmlSaveOptions.MetafileFormat property added  KeepSourceFormatting logic improved Rendering of SVG graphics elements embedded into DrawingML objects (svgBlip) implemented Added option to disable the internal font substitution mechanism and use the default font instead while rendering to PDF.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-18-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Android via Java 18.1.
Major Features There are 60+ improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Performance improvements. Improved character spacing control logic. Improved space shrinking for Verdana font. Improved &amp;ldquo;allow handing punctuation&amp;rdquo; handling when kerning is enabled. Fixed clip issue with semi-broken tables. Fixed draw order of wrapped shapes in 2013 mode. Fixed repeated header height problem during field update.</description></item></channel></rss>