<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.12.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50290 Provide the single API to convert a Visio shape to PDF Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50291 Provide the single API to convert a Visio shape to HTML Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50572 Shape.connectedShapes method does not retrieve outgoing nodes Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50391 The flipped images and arrows are generated on converting a VSD to SVG Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50570 VSD to PDF - the additional text items are added Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50571 Import VSDX - an error occurred in the shape element Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50573 VSD to SVG - the lines of a group shape are missing Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50575 VSD to SVG - the text items are missing Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50576 Import VDX procedure throws a page element error Bug Adds Copy member in Shape class The copy member takes a target shape instance, as a parameter to clone this shape.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50557 Output VSDX - AutoFitPageToDrawingContent does not work as expected Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50563 Open and save routine of VSDM is missing Macros Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50564 Output VSDX - the member shape of two groups behaves weird Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50163 VST to VDX conversion, pictures are missing from the each rectangle shape Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50336 VSDX to PDF export - Shadows of Shapes are not being preserved properly Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50556 Output VSDX - misplaced text of the dynamic connector Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50567 Output VSDX - invisible connecting lines on generating a network drawing Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50568 VSD to SVG - an unknown source error is thrown Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50569 VSD to SVG - incorrect formatting of the text Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50509 VSD to SVG - the text items are displaced Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.10.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50560 JpegQuality does not make any effect on output document Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50548 Output VSDX - the connecting line passing through the boundary of the shape Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50550 Shape Transform section does not preserve formulas Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50551 VSDX to PNG - incorrect rendering of the shape corners Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50552 The fill colors are not being preserved on saving a Visio drawing to SVG Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50553 Incorrect rendering of lines when saving a Visio drawing to SVG Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50554 The fill colors are not being preserved on saving a Visio drawing to SVG Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50555 Incorrect rendering of lines when saving a Visio drawing to SVG Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50559 VSDM to VDX - the connecting lines are not connected to the shapes Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50561 The VSDX drawing is corrupt after adding SolutionXML element Bug Adds SameAsPdfConversionArea in ImageSaveOptions It specifies whether to save area in the same way as PDF.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.9.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50485 Add support of auto spacing shapes in Visio Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50521 Output VSDX - incorrect layout of the connector line  Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50522 Output PNG - the text of shape goes out of the boundary Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50527 Output VSDX - the connecting line is touching the boundary of shape Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50540 Output VSDX - incorrect layout of the connecting lines Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50543 Output VSDX - incorrect layout and misplaced text of the connecting lines Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50545 Output VSDX - Cannot formulate the position of text in shape Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50547 Output VSDX - cannot set property value as String Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list for any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.8.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50412 Missing shapes on converting a VST to PNG. Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50497 Output VSDX - incorrect layout of all connecting lines. Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50500 Output VSDX - the manually added shape size is not being changed. Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50511 Output VSDX - misplaced text of the dynamic connector.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.7.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50491 Cannot retrieve the new formulated shape height. Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50510 VSD to SVG - incorrect fill color pattern in the shapes. Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50483 Incomplete connection of shapes when saving a drawing in VSDX format. Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50488 Additional text items are added when converting a VSD to SVG.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.6.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50500 Output VSDX - the manually added shape size is not being changed Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50503 Output VSDX - the text overflow when adding multi-line text Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50505 A null pointer error occurred on converting the drawing page to image Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50484 Vertical text display of decision box shape when saving a drawing in VSDX format Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50486 Vertical text display of Predefined process shape when saving a drawing in VSDX format Bug  DIAGRAMJAVA-50492 The formulas in Width and Height cells are not being preserved Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50493 Missing characters on converting a VSD to SVG Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50494 Output VSDX - the connecting lines are not connecting in the mid of process shapes Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50499 VSDX to PNG - a white horizontal line appears at the bottom of shape Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list for any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.5.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50472 Generate the warning about font substitution during Visio to PDF conversion. Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50480  Cannot add a SolutionXML element in a VSDX Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50473 Incomplete connections of shapes on converting a VDX to VSDM Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50475 Connector line is passing through the other shapes on converting a VDX to VSDM Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50476 Incomplete connections of shapes on converting a VDX to VSDM Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50479 Cannot retrieve Solution XMLs from a VSDX Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50481 Incorrect color of rectangle shape on converting a VSDX to PDF Bug There are no public API changes in the version 17.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.4.0.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50222 Add support to import a bitmap image as a shape Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50404  The connecting lines are not connected while creating a VDX Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50468 Missing shapes on converting a VDX to VSDM Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50469 The text items are rendered vertically on converting a VDX to VSDM Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50471 Connectors are not in the right positions with changing the page layout in VSDX Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list for any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.3.0.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50459 Incorrect position of shape&amp;rsquo;s shadow on converting a VSD to SVG. Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50460 The slash line symbols are missing on converting a Visio page to SVG. Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50467 Arrows have not rendered while converting VSD to SVG. Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50470 Macros are not being preserved on converting a VDX to VSDM.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.02.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-02-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-02-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.02.0.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50037 VSD to PDF conversion, the background color shade of a group shape is getting changed. Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50365 A blank page is generated while converting a Visio page with equations to PNG. Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50461 Borders are missing while converting VSDX to PNG.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.01 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-01-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-diagram-for-java-17-01-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 17.1.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50396 Can&amp;rsquo;t retrieve the fill color of rectangle shape from a VSDX diagram. Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50367 The color of shapes is not being preserved on converting a VSDX to PDF. Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50370 The formatting of rectangle shape is missing on converting a VSDX to PNG.</description></item></channel></rss>