<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2015 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2015 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Tasks For Java 9.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-9-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-9-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have implemented Task.DurationText field for mpp writing and reading. New constructor has been added to Project class to work with Primavera Project. Also reading all project UID from Primavera XML has been implemented.About three bugs have been fixed.
All Changes Issue Type Key Summary Investigation TASKS-34323 Read Task.DurationText field from project file New Feature TASKS-34271 Provide constructor for Project(Stream steam,PrimaveraXmlReadingOptions options) New Feature TASKS-34270 Read all projects UID from Primavera XML to get list of UID Task TASKS-34326 TASKS-33909 Implement Task.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks For Java 9.0.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-9-0-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-9-0-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have implemented enhancement which allow to read subproject info (inserted project information). Also about six bugs have been fixed. Please see the list of changes below.
All Changes Issue Type Key Summary Bug TASKS-34281 Exception while adding resource assignment to task with duration ZERO Bug TASKS-34280 Calendar exceptions lost when MPP saved and used again Bug TASKS-34279 Wrong AssignmentBaselineWork retrieved from Timephased data Bug TASKS-34275 Wrong monthly hours extracted while reading Timephased data Bug TASKS-34274 Timephased data shown far beyond the project task dates Bug TASKS-34273 Wrong timephased data read against holidays Enhancement TASKS-34258 Unable to set Task as another SubProject</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks For Java 8.9.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-9-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-9-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have supported export and import Project Data for HTML format. It will allow to work with GroupDocs Editor https://www.groupdocs.com/.
We have implemented reading Primavera XML file with multiple projects. Primavera Xml Save Option has been supported. We have also implemented adding an image to header and legend of project. About nine bugs have been fixed. Please see the list of changes below.
All Changes Issue Type Key Summary New Feature TASKS-34257 Implement Primavera Xml Save Option Investigation TASKS-34230 Reading Primavera XML file with multiple projects Enhancement TASKS-34223 Provision of including Image in Page Header/Footer Task TASKS-34116 Implement Export/Import Project Data as HTML Task TASKS-34232 TASKS-34231 Implement ResourceRateNodeReader, ProjectCurrencyNodeReader for PrimaveraXml Reader Bug TASKS-34260 HtmlSaveOptions class is missing in latest version Bug TASKS-34259 MSP does not show task split when opening resaved mpp file.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks For Java 8.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have significantly improved writing and reading for mpp format. We have also implemented Task ExtendedAttributes and ExtendedAttributeDefinitions reading from Microsoft Project Server. About ten bugs have been fixed. Please see the list of changes below.
All Changes Issue Type Key Summary Enhancement TASKS-34120 Date localization while exporting to PDF Task TASKS-34220 Implement reading/writing TableField.WrapText and TableField.WrapHeader fields to mpp format Task TASKS-34219 Implement reading/writing Table.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks For Java 8.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have supported several important features in this release. Risk analysis tool based on Monte Carlo with pdf report has been implemented. We have implemented reading project data from Microsoft Project database. It allows to cover a lot of scenarios of working with Microsoft Project Server and Aspose.Tasks library. Note, now it can work for default calendar only. Microsoft Project 2016 file format has been supported. Three bugs have been fixed.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks For Java 8.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have supported major feature - reading project data from Primavera database. It allows to cover a lot of scenarios of working with Primavera database and Aspose.Tasks library. Five bugs have been fixed. Please see the list of changes below.
All Changes Issue Type Key Summary Task TASKS-34079 Implement Project data reading from Primavera DB Enhancement TASKS-34111 Project Structure verification functionality missing in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 8.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have supported several important features this release. Ability to extract objects embedded in task or resource view form, page settings writing into mpp format, reading Header and Footer data from MPP files have been implemented. One bug has been fixed. Please, see details below.
All Changes Issue Type Key Summary New Feature TASKS-16019 Read Header and Footer data from MPP files.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 8.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features Four bugs have been fixed this release. Please, see list of all details below.
All Changes Issue Type Key Summary Bug TASKS-33990 Calendar Add ( String name, Calendar baseCalendar ) doesn&amp;rsquo;t add new calendar to the project Bug TASKS-34003 Calculation bug: Setting Minutes Per Day for 24-Hour Calendar results in wrong Start and Finish time of task Bug TASKS-34026 Project reading exception while reading the slack values in scientific notation Bug TASKS-34032 Attached MPP raises project reading exception while loading it</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 8.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have implemented converting MPP to MPX format. Option to set start date for GanttChart view has been supported. Also formula calculation and evaluation of functions in formulas have been implemented. About eight bugs have been fixed. Please, see list of all features below.
All Changes Issue Type Key Summary New Feature TASKS-33967 TASKS-33909 Implement reading recurring tasks data from mpp New Feature TASKS-33978 TASKS-33909 Implement recurring task data writing to mpp New Feature TASKS-33748 Option to convert MPP to MPX format New Feature TASKS-33925 Implement formula calculation New Feature TASKS-33938 Implement evaluation of functions in formulas Investigation TASKS-33945 Updating MPP raises ArgumentOutOfRangeException Enhancement TASKS-33886 Provide option to set start date for GanttChart view while saving as MPP Bug TASKS-33963 Normal tasks become summary task after saving the project by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 8.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have implemented several new features this release. &amp;ldquo;Display Details columns in chart area&amp;rdquo; feature has been supported. Formula calculation and evaluation of functions in formulas have been implemented. Eight bugs have been fixed. Please, see list of all features below.
All Changes Issue Type Key Summary Investigation TASKS-33936 Aspose.Tasks 8.1.0 does not have a strong name Enhancement TASKS-33797 Display Details columns in chart area Task TASKS-33916 TASKS-33797 Implement cost usage fields rendering in Details Column according to Usage Details settings Task TASKS-33932 TASKS-33925 Implement Task and Resource work/cost/number fields calculation in expressions Task TASKS-33935 TASKS-33925 Implement Task and Resource DateTime/boolean fields calculation in expressions Task TASKS-33939 TASKS-33925 Implement calculation of Project fields in expressions Task TASKS-33947 TASKS-33938 Implement calculation of Math functions Task TASKS-33950 TASKS-33938 Implement calculation of Text functions Task TASKS-33951 TASKS-33938 Implement calculation of Date/Time functions Bug TASKS-33930 Not correct reading &amp;ldquo;timephased data&amp;rdquo; from .</description></item></channel></rss>