<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/java/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/java/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Font for Java 21.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-java-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-java-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Font for Java 21.12.
Key Summary Category FONTNET-294 Incorrect calculation of transformation matrix for CFF fonts Bug Got Queries? If you have any query related to Aspose.Font for Java API, please feel free to write to reach us on Aspose.Font forum. We&amp;rsquo;ll be glad to assist you with your inquiries.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Font for Java 21.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-java-21-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-java-21-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Font for Java 21.10.
Conversion functionality for CFF and WOFF2 format has been fixed.
Key Summary Category FONTNET-286 Incorrect calculation of transformation matrix for CFF fonts Bug FONTNET-274 Encoding problem for ttf to woff2 conversion Bug FONTNET-275 Null reference exception when converting font OpenSans from cff to ttf format Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Added APIs Type com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Font for Java 21.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-java-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-java-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Font for Java 21.8.
CFF to TTF/WOFF converters were added. All TTF and WOFF/WOFF2 tables&amp;rsquo; support was implemented.
Key Summary Category FONTNET-193 Support of CFF to TTF/WOFF converter New Feature FONTNET-237 Support all tables for TTF/WOFF formats New Feature FONTNET-244 Saving capability for all TTF/WOFF tables New Feature FONTNET-229 Problem in local table while saving WOFF2 file Bug FONTNET-238 OutOfMemoryException thrown while rendering glyths Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Added APIs Type com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Font for Java 21.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-java-21-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-font-for-java-21-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Font for Java 21.4.
This release of Aspose.Font for Java API provides the capability to edit font names for TTF/OTF fonts. In addition, you can now save TTF fonts after editing. WOFF/WOFF2 formats have been added. TTF and WOFF conversion option has been implemented. WOFF2 converting and saving support has been added. SHA-256 license type has been supported. Specific functionality for working with glyphs has been added.</description></item></channel></rss>