<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.12
Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-148 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 19.12 features Feature SLIDESANDROID-216 Bad performance of Aspose.Slides for Android via Java Bug Public API Changes Data Points of Treemap and Sunburst Chart Among other types of PowerPoint charts, there are two &amp;ldquo;hierarchical&amp;rdquo; types - Treemap and Sunburst chart (also known as Sunburst Graph, Sunburst Diagram, Radial Chart, Radial Graph or Multi Level Pie Chart).</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.11
Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-147 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 19.11 features Feature Public API Changes Obsolete methods addFromSvg have been deleted Methods IPPImage addFromSvg(String svgContent) and IPPImage addFromSvg(String svgContent, IExternalResourceResolver externalResResolver, String baseUri) have been removed from ImageCollection class and corresponding IImageCollection interface.
Please use method addImage(ISvgImage svgImage) instead.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.10
Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-146 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 19.10 features Feature Public API Changes Introducing new API for control a FontFallBack functionality A new API for initialization and managing of FontFallBack functionality was introduced. FontFallBack is used when the font specified for text is present but this font doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain a necessary glyph.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.9
Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-145 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 19.9 features Feature Public API Changes isLicensed method declared as deprecated for ILicense interface and License class ILicense.isLicensed and License.isLicensed methods declared as deprecated. These methods will be removed after release of version 19.12.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.8
Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-144 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 19.8 features Feature SLIDESNET-36682 Hiding master shapes from slide Feature SLIDESNET-41189 Decryption of encrypted ODP and OTP presentation formats Feature SLIDESNET-41048 Embedding HTML and ZIP files Feature SLIDESNET-34498 Property for setting layout mode of chart plot area Feature SLIDESNET-41062 Support for Widescreen predefined type Feature SLIDESNET-35054 Implement Chart_Chart2007.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.7
Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-143 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 19.7 Feature SLIDESNET-34685 Default automatic Markers symbols for LineWithMarkers chart Feature SLIDESNET-36453 Support API for animation effects on paragraph level editing Feature SLIDESNET-33742 Setting Font related properties for Chart Area Feature SLIDESNET-35440 Support for clearing the particular chart series datapoint data only in chart data worksheet Feature SLIDESNET-33910 Setting Font related properties for chart entities at one place Feature SLIDESNET-40010 Setter for ExternalWorkbookPath of ExternalWorkbook in charts Feature SLIDESNET-41166 PowerPoint has page numbers that increment even when its just a continuation of that slides notes Enhancement SLIDESNET-35712 Enabling and disabling the chart series values Enhancement SLIDESNET-41215 OLE embedded objects support for OpenDocument Enhancement SLIDESNET-41185 Poor Quality When converting PPTX to PdfNotes Enhancement Public API Changes Another option has been added for setting external workbook path Method setExternalWorkbook(String workbookPath, boolean updateChartData) has been added.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for Andriod via Java 19.6
Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-142 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 19.6 features Feature SLIDESNET-41092 IColorFormat.Color doesn’t return effective color Feature SLIDESNET-34681 Support for progress in percentage for PDF conversion Feature SLIDESNET-41101 Implement a progress in percentage for PDF conversion Feature SLIDESNET-40958 Option for making every page self-sufficient when saving presentation as HTML Feature SLIDESNET-16733 Fusion Charts support in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for Andriod via Java 19.5
Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-141 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 19.5 features Feature SLIDESNET-40727 Support for Convert SVG images to shapes Feature SLIDESNET-40870 Support for comments replies in Aspose.Slides Feature SLIDESNET-41059 Aspose.Slides for .NET: Rasterization or vectorization of Shapes without text Feature SLIDESNET-40730 Support for Office 365 in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for Andriod via Java 19.4
Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-154 Add support for Android KitKat 19 Feature SLIDESANDROID-140 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 19.4 features Feature SLIDESNET-41018 Supporting of external Excel workbooks Feature SLIDESNET-40897 Support for OpenDocument encryption Feature SLIDESNET-40938 PDF text is not searchable when exported to PDF with Notes Enhancement SLIDESANDROID-156 Out of memory exception during the conversion to PDF Bug Public API Changes New Size and SizeF classes have been added New classes Size and SizeF have been added to com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for Andriod via Java 19.3
Key Summary Category SLIDESNET-40600 Support for Text Highlighter feature Feature SLIDESNET-40794 Change the color of hyperlink text throughout a presentation Feature SLIDESNET-40799 Restricting local file system access when opening a document Feature SLIDESJAVA-37442 Use Aspose.Slides for NET 19.3 features Feature SLIDESNET-40925 Add encoding meta tag when saving into HTML Enhancement SLIDESNET-40612 Setting for removing width and height attributes of SVG tag when saving as HTML Enhancement SLIDESNET-39845 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for Andriod via Java 19.2
Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-101 Implement PathGradientBrush for Android Feature SLIDESANDROID-138 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 19.2 features Feature SLIDESNET-40783 Support for setting Transparency property for shadow effects Feature SLIDESJAVA-36692 The text has corrupted after PDF rendition. Bug SLIDESJAVA-36388 Small caps effect lost after saving PPT Bug SLIDESJAVA-37459 PPTX to PDF not properly converted Bug SLIDESJAVA-37462 Water Mark issue Bug SLIDESJAVA-37471 ODP file not properly converted to PPTX Bug SLIDESJAVA-37472 ODP file not properly converted to PPTX Bug SLIDESJAVA-37541 Exception on generating Thumbnails Bug SLIDESJAVA-37544 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for Android via Java 19.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-slides-for-android-via-java-19-1-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESANDROID-99 Implement HatchBrush for Android Feature SLIDESANDROID-137 Use Aspose.Slides for Java 19.1 features Feature SLIDESJAVA-37157 Option for setting locale in application Feature SLIDESJAVA-36680 WordArt text shadow has lost when converting to thumbnail image Bug SLIDESJAVA-36930 PPTX to PDF text shadowing not same Bug SLIDESJAVA-35532 PowerPoint Loses Alt Text Fields Bug SLIDESJAVA-35578 Wrong Underline color appeared after saving PPT Bug SLIDESJAVA-35682 Text Type difference in PPT and PPTX files Bug SLIDESJAVA-37109 Exception on loading presentation Bug SLIDESJAVA-37180 All caps effect lost on save Bug SLIDESJAVA-37374 Line Alignment Issue after conversion to PDF Bug SLIDESJAVA-37384 Wrong text spacing for generated slide thumbnail Bug SLIDESJAVA-37398 getShapeStyle method returns null Bug SLIDESJAVA-37421 Exception on loading presentation Bug SLIDESJAVA-37425 Text rendered inverted in exported PDF Bug SLIDESJAVA-37426 NullPointer exception on loading presentation Bug SLIDESJAVA-37457 Exception on loading and saving PPTX Bug Public API Changes CurrentThreadSettings class has been added Android The CurrentThreadSettings class has been added to com.</description></item></channel></rss>