<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2015 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2015 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 15.12.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-12-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-12-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 15.12.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 15.12 Release Notes Major Features There are 80 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Access ActiveX control properties New InsertOleObject method Preset text wrap (“follow path”, “warp”) for DrawingML textboxes rendering implemented DrawingML textboxes rendering improved Apply styles from the template during HTML insertion HTML Import supports ruby tags now All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10181 Some words are trimmed from the right side.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 15.11.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-11-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-11-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 15.11.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 15.11 Release Notes Major Features There are 127 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improvements to rendering of images on Mono. Some new public methods and properties for picture bullets, checkboxes, fields, styles. Performance improvements. Many improvements in rendering of WordArt, gradient fill, SmartArt, DrawingML. Fixes and improvements in all document format conversions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 15.10.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-10-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-10-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 15.10.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 15.10 Release Notes Major Features There are 85 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improvements in text wrapping around shapes and frames Improvements in rendering of Arabic and Chinese documents Improvements in rendering of shapes and EMF images Ruby is supported in HTML export Ruby import/export is supported for OpenDocument (ODT) documents DrawingML Charts can be rendered into images using ShapeRenderer All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10994 Alignment of cell&amp;rsquo;s text is changed after re-saving Docx Bug WORDSNET-11020 Table layout issue after conversion from RTF to HTML Bug WORDSNET-11091 Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 15.9.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-9-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-9-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 15.9.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 15.9 Release Notes Major Features There are 81 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Creation of EditableRange objects in DocumentBuilder SVM image support in ODT DrawingML textbox wrapping is now rendered correctly (while cold rendering i.e. using DmlRenderingMode.DrawingML) Bookmark hyperlinks are now rendered correctly into PDF/A standard documents Overlapping problem while rendering of Chinese characters into HTML Fixed format resolved Improvements to DrawmingML Charts rendering All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10594 Docx to Pdf conversion issue wiht SmartArt rendering Bug WORDSNET-11175 Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 15.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 15.8.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 15.8 Release Notes Major Features There are 89 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added assemblies that target .NET CLR 4.0.
Implemented fixed table grid calculation.
Improved footnote balancing.
Supported roundtrip of ruby a.k.a phonetic guide in flow formats. Limited support for rendering to PDF is also provided.
EMF+ rendering is improved (line caps and shadows).</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 15.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 15.7.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 15.7 Release Notes Major Features There are 103 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added API to work with Themes
Allow inserting of TIFF images
API to change footnote/endnote separator
Improved footnote balancing
Improved text wrapping around objects in footers
Ternary raster operations for EMF/WMF rendering implemented
PDF background rendering improved</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 15.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 15.6.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 15.6 Release Notes Major Features There are 81 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Public Chart API
Public API for Custom Mark in footnotes
LINQ Reporting Engine supports charts
HTML/MHTML with framesets is preserved during open/save
Using IImageSavingCallback allows to change image filenames
Password verification in write-protected documents
Support for culture invariant languages in DOCX/WML e.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 15.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 15.5.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 15.5 Release Notes Major Features There are 82 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
CustomXML nodes are removed
Support for conditional blocks added to the LINQ Reporting Engine
Improved rendering of floating shapes in complex tables
Implemented Arabic Abjad list numbering style in the layout
Improved performance of importing HTML documents with complex CSS selectors</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 15.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 15.4.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 15.4 Release Notes Major Features There are 99 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
MathML equations rendering inside shapes implemented
MathML equations vertical positioning improved when rendering
Improved Iso29500 support for MS Word for Mac 2011 documents
Improved page number calculation, footnote balancing, nested floating tables and text wrapping around floating objects</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 15.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 15.3.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 15.3 Release Notes Major Features There are 131 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improvements in the layout engine for handling RTL text, text boxes, cell vertical alignment and others.
Improvements in import/export for all file formats.
Optimized output size of PDF documents for some cases.
Document.WarningCallback property can now send you loss of formatting warnings at anytime during document lifetime, not only during saving.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 15.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 15.2.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 15.2 Release Notes Major Features There are 116 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Document comparison feature is introduced, see Document.Compare
DrawingML API breaking changes (Shape and DrawingML classes merged into Shape)
Implemented text justification for multiline WordArt objects
Implemented multi line text rendering in DrawingML text boxes, SmartArt and charts</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 15.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-15-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 15.1.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 15.1 Release Notes Major Features There are 75 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Fields Public API New public API members for structured document tags
OpenDocument (ODT) import/export fidelity improvements
Rendering of spacing and kerning in WordArt supported
HTML export/import improved for better round-tripping
Comment numbering in rendering</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 14.12.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-14-12-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2015/aspose-words-for-net-14-12-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 14.12.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 14.12 Release Notes Major Features There are 101 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
WordArt rendering does not rely on GDI+ now and supported on .NET, Mono and Java New mode of handling styles during Import via public ImportFormatMode.KeepDifferentStyles Public API for specifying text effects for Revisions during rendering to fixed formats Shape connectors supported Improved tight wrapping mode for floating objects Improved rendering of overlapped and nested floating objects Enhanced inter-characters spacing calculation for Asian documents with kerning Improved text direction detection for documents with missing RTL attributes Hyperlinks on shapes and text inside textboxes are exported correctly to HTML All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10053 Font formatting of generated DOC is not correct when importing from RTF Bug WORDSNET-10109 Docx-HTML-Docx : Author details for all inserts and deletes revision become unknown Bug WORDSNET-10396 Links on Shapes don&amp;rsquo;t work when exported to HTML Bug WORDSNET-10744 Some characters garbled during converting RTF to DOC Bug WORDSNET-10832 Footer content overlaps during rendering to PDF Bug WORDSNET-10875 A Drawing partially renders byond the right page edge in PDF Bug WORDSNET-10879 A picture in header goes behind a Table in PDF Bug WORDSNET-10886 background-color style does not reflected in output document Bug WORDSNET-10940 Content position is changed after re-saving Docx Bug WORDSNET-10943 Document.</description></item></channel></rss>