<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 18.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 18.12.
Major Features There are 108 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Java 11 compatibility is checked and updated. ExternalImageLibTest utility class added to check external image libraries on user side. Implemented WMF fonts scaling, according to metafile size on the page, and public option to control it (MetafileRenderingOptions.ScaleWmfFontsToMetafileSize). Improved the default font fallback mechanism to better fit the MW behavior.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 18.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 18.11.
Major Features There are 81 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Aspose.Words for Java release jar is tested on Java 11. Compatibility with GroupDocs Total License is improved. GraphicsQualityOptions is better mapped to Java. We did yet another step to shrink (already small) pixel difference between .NET and Java generated images, borders, etc.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 18.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 18.10.
Major Features There are 84 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Aspose.Words for Java is FIPS compliant now. The single sentence &amp;lsquo;SecuritySettings.startFipsMode()&amp;rsquo; switches current Aspose.Words thread to the FIPS mode. Support Conholdate.Total for Java licensing system. Compatibility within GroupDocs Total package is improved. Just another Veracode Security Scan Report is fixed. Java 10/11 compatibility updates caused few bugs on some old Java Runtime Environments.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 18.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 18.9.
Major Features There are 85 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Animated GIF is fully supported now MANIFEST.MF updated to support new OSGI versions TIFF colors accuracy improved Java10&amp;amp;11 compatibility improved: reflection for safe using of optional external libraries is removed. Bookmarks are allowed on block, cell, row level  Added load option to treat Shapes with math XML as Shapes in the model  Provided option to choose between Old and New Mail Merge behaviors  Improved PDF encryption in case when owner password is not specified  Metafile rendering improved: fixed drawing records processing when path bracket is opened, fixed processing of EMR_SETBKMODE record when incorrect values specified Improved output image quality when rendering metafiles with raster operations set Fixed handling of glyphs without outlines when parsing glyph data while rendering Fixed a bug with a glow effect, if the specified glow size is less than 10 Fixed several problems in DrawingML Charts rendering: incorrect default axis color, bug with the date format for axis values, bug with rendering of the trend line with unsorted x-values Improved rendering of the mathematical element &amp;ldquo;Apostrophe&amp;rdquo; of the MathML object  Improved justification of Asian texts Improved rendering of revisions in balloons Improved text placement around floating shapes Fixed issue with paragraph spacing in footnotes Fixed issue with line wrapping when it has single glyph wider than the line followed by page break Fixed issue with table row height calculation when cells in vertical merge have horizontal borders Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-1578 Right-aligned tab-stops conversion issue in resultant MHTML Bug WORDSJAVA-1837 Image sometimes do not render in exported HTML Bug WORDSJAVA-1840 Math symbols are being read incorrectly Bug WORDSJAVA-1847 Animated GIF rendered to PDF with a bottom gray band Bug WORDSJAVA-1848 ReportingEngine.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 18.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 18.8.
Major Features There are 86 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Java 10 tested and supported now New and updated Samples and Examples Change SHA-1 to SHA-256 and public asymmetric key from 1024 to 2048 for the license mechanism Implemented support for “underline trailing spaces” compatibility option Implemented support for paragraph alignment in Omath when inserted using EQ fields Enhanced computation of interscript spacing values based on TTF properties Improved wrapping of text around floating objects Improved calculation of position of floating tables and shapes Improved floater overlapping logic Improved computing of pages numbers in continuous sections which have restart attribute and conflicting oddity Fixed line justification issue when RTL span is at the end of the line Fixed issue with null dml properties Fixed issue with rendering of floating shapes in truncated headers/footers Fixed issue with rendering of lines inside of a field result when updated in truncated part of a cell Improved rendering of math operators in MathML objects Improved rendering of MathML objects with n-ary math element when n-ary character and limit location are not specified Fixed a bug with rendering of a math n-ary element if it is part of a fraction Fixed a bug when polyline with an arrow and a very small line segment at the end  was corrupted upon rendering Fixed a bug when an arrow pointer is incorrectly directed while rendering Bezier curves with arrows Fixed a bug where the end of the line was outside the &amp;ldquo;stealth arrow&amp;rdquo; when rendering LINQ Reporting Engine supports nested reports Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-1845 SetLicense throws IllegalStateException.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 18.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 18.7.
Major Features There are 90 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
New typed (generic) collections and enumerators were introduced in Aspose.Words public API Added public property HeaderFooterBookmarksExportMode in PdfSaveOptions  Added FontSourceBase.GetAvailableFonts method  Added public API for revision groups  Introduced new comparison settings  A new limo stretch algorithm for VML shapes rendering was developed, which most accurately repeats the output of MS Word (limo-stretched shapes) Public property OutlineOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 18.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 18.6.
Major Features There are 66 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Exposed Title and Description properties into Table class Added feature to insert shapes through the DocumentBuilder using ShapeType Changed public properties of AxisScaling class Implemented API allowing to set up language preferences Added IsMoveFromRevision and IsMoveToRevision properties Exposed properties for Asian typography into ParagraphFormat class Public TXT save option AddBidiMarks is added Implemented &amp;ldquo;left&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;right&amp;rdquo; alignment support for Ruby objects rendering Improved rendering of DrawingML chart data labels with percentage values and the specified format Flat shapes that are perpendicular to the projection plane are not rendered now Zero-width characters in DrawingML textboxes no longer cause an exception during rendering Fixed an issue with font fallback rendering for 1F600 - 1F64F (Emoticons) Unicode range Fixed a bug with the rendering of the chart data labels, when label text and SpPr are specified Fixed a bug with the maximum value of the chart axis when rendering DrawingML charts Fixed a problem with rendering of subscript and superscript text in DrawingML charts Fixed a bug where the shadowed shapes with compound outline lost their fill Fixed MathML alignment issue inside text boxes Fixed layout when large inline shape is attached to a paragraph with space after overflowing page Fixed issue with preferred width of vertically merged table cells accounted for during width computation Fixed exception when revision balloons are displayed in certain cases Enhanced logic which handles page breaks inside text frames LINQ Reporting Engine supports dynamic insertion of hyperlinks Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-1731 Small shadow is absent on chart diagram Bug WORDSJAVA-1757 Graph markings are not rendered in the output PDF Bug WORDSJAVA-1782 Emf fill became ugly while saving.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 18.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 18.5.
Major Features There are 75 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added public property StructuredDocumentTag.Color  Improved logic to detect the encoding of a short TXT file. Fixed line wrapping with trailing spaces at the end Fixed issue with paragraph after spacing in headers/footers Fixed issue with table width when widthAfter is specified for a jagged table Fixed issue with table width with complex column layout and default widths Fixed breaking of floating table row in compatibility mode Fixed issue with floating frame pushed from the page because of invalid wrap point Implemented support for &amp;ldquo;distribute space&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;distribute letter&amp;rdquo; types of alignment when rendering Ruby objects Improved rendering of a Doughnut DrawingML Chart with multiple series Improved rendering of DrawingML Charts data labels with the direct layout and a layout specified in the extension properties Fixed a problem with metafile rendering when glyph offsets were wrongly read for EMF_EXTTEXTOUT record with glyph indices Fixed a problem with processing of control character (U+0019) in the text when rendering Fixed a problem with Adobe “Fast Find” function (words searching) in rendered PDF documents Fixed a bug with inaccurate processing of EMR_ALPHABLEND record while rendering metafiles.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 18.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 18.4.
Major Features There are 75 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added public Ref&amp;lt;T&amp;gt; class for out/ref emulation in public API. Provide an ability to work with password-protected ODT and OTT file formats Preserve PaperTray information in PCL  Added ShapeBase.IsLayoutInCell property  Implemented optimization of metafile rendering vector output. Optimization includes applying intermediate transformations directly to the graphics and removing redundant canvases.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 18.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 18.3.
Major Features There are 71 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Public API to get Subject and Issuer names from DigitalCertificate (instead obsolete properties). Add support of CssClassNamesPrefix in HtmlSaveOptions A number of obsolete properties were removed from PdfSaveOptions class. Please refer to public API changes section for details PdfSaveOptions.EscapeUri property was added to allow the usage of custom URI strings without the automatic escape while rendering into PDF The automatic font color calculation now takes the fill of the background shape into account while rendering Added fallback rendering for Unicode range [U+1F300; U+1F5FF] - Miscellaneous Symbols and Pictographs; This range includes such symbols as Emoji and alike Implemented processing of empty EMR_EXTTEXTOUTW records in metafiles rendering Improved rendering of DML Chart plot area with a manual layout.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 18.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 18.2
Major Features There are 102 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
FontSettings.EnableFontSubstitution option added Support to insert Style Separator to put different Paragraph styles HtmlSaveOptions.MetafileFormat property added  KeepSourceFormatting logic improved Rendering of SVG graphics elements embedded into DrawingML objects (svgBlip) implemented Added option to disable the internal font substitution mechanism and use the default font instead while rendering to PDF.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 18.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-words-for-java-18-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 18.1
Major Features There are 63 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved character spacing control logic. Improved space shrinking for Verdana font. Improved &amp;ldquo;allow handing punctuation&amp;rdquo; handling when kerning is enabled. Fixed clip issue with semi-broken tables. Fixed draw order of wrapped shapes in 2013 mode. Fixed repeated header height problem during field update.</description></item></channel></rss>