<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.12.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-12-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-12-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.12.1.
Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-266 Shapefile does not display in QGIS Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.12.
Major Features TopoJSON file format support Convert GeoJSON to TopoJSON and vice versa Additional options for accessing FileGDB format Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-233 Convert GeoJSON to TopoJSON New Feature GISNET-243 Read and write features to/from TopoJSON New Feature GISNET-249 Additional options for accessing FileGDB format New Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.11.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-11-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-11-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.11.1.
Major Features Fix NullReferenceException when accessing the file from multiple threads. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-247 KML file generates Object reference not set to an instance of an object exception Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.11.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Import from WKT and WKB Export to WKT and WKB Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-234 Translate Geometries to/from WKT and WKB New Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes static Geometry.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.10.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Reading OBJECTID from FIleGDB Layers Computing distance between Geometries Computing areas and lengths of Geometries Computing convex hull of Geometries Computing centroid of Geometries Building a buffer of Geometries Fixes:
Shape writing into FileGDB. Compute Union Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-210 Geometry Buffer Operation New Feature GISNET-213 Compute Distance between Geometries New Feature GISNET-214 Geometry Convex Hull Operation New Feature GISNET-215 Geometry Area and Length Operations New Feature GISNET-216 Geometry Centroid Operation New Feature GISNET-217 A point on Surface Operation New Feature GISNET-218 Covers and CoveredBy operations New Feature GISNET-221 Read OBJECTID from FileGDB layers Improvement GISNET-222 Unable to Compute Union Bug GISNET-226 Shape distortion in GDB Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes New methods in IGeometry interface (and overloads in Geometry class):</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.9.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Determining the spatial relation between geometries (e.g. testing if geometries intersect, testing if one geometry contains another, etc.). Computing Intersection, Union, Difference and Symmetric Difference between geometries. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-206 Spatial Predicates New Feature GISNET-207 Overlay Operations (Intersection, Union, Difference, Symmetric Difference) New Feature GISNET-212 Handle Geometries Precision New Feature GISNET-211 Error while loading GDB Bug GISNET-209 CreateFromWkt fails on projected SRS Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes New methods in IGeometry interface (and overloads in Geometry class):</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.8.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Creating new layers in ESRI File Geodatabase datasets. Deleting layers from ESRI File Geodatabase datasets. Creating new ESRI File Geodatabase datasets. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-197 ESRI File Geodatabase creation and writing New Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Drivers members that were marked as obsolete at v18.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.7.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Reading data in GML format Reading data in ESRI File Geodatabase format List of Improvements Key Summary Category GISNET-174 Geography Markup Language (GML) New Feature GISNET-188 ESRI File Geodatabase (FileGDB) New Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Change in members of Drivers for working with vector layers</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information of Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.6 release.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Reading data in GPX format Support for .NET Standard 2.0 which also implies the support for: .NET Framework 4.7 or later (Windows only) .NET Core 2.0 or later (Windows and Linux) Mono 5.4 or later (Windows and Linux) Xamarin.iOS 10.14 or later Xamarin.Mac 3.8 or later Xamarin.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.5.
Major Features Support for Open Street Map XML Improvements Key Summary Category GISNET-176 OpenStreetMap XML (OSM XML) support. New Feature GISNET-183 Fix types, returned from &amp;lsquo;Clone&amp;rsquo; method of MultiLineStirng, MultiPoint and MultiPolygon. Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following Properties were added to find out whether driver supports creation of new layer and opening existing layers.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.4.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Spatial reference systems support Work with WKT - Import spatial reference systems from WKT and export spatial reference systems to WKT Create vector layers with spatial reference system Set desired spatial reference system when converting between layers Transform geometries between spatial reference systems Features and Improvements Key Summary Category GISNET-165 Spatial reference systems support New Feature GISNET-170 Convert between spatial reference systems New Feature GISNET-167 Fix IGeometry methods visibility Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes IGeometry has immutable HasZ and HasM IGeometry was designed to be immutable.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.3.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Reading and writing data in KML format. Geometry Validation Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-134 Geometry Validation New Feature GISNET-139 Streamline handling of Null values Improvement GISNET-135 Keyhole Markup Language (KML) New Feature GISTNET-157 Handle empty geometries Improvement GISNET-162 Members added to geometry collection accommodate dimension Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes This version includes certain Public API Changes that affect the existing implementations.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 18.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-gis-for-net-18-2-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.GIS for .NET has been launched Aspose.GIS for .NET has been launched. It lets you work with popular ESRI ShapeFile and GeoJSON file formats. The uniform approach of API to process these file formats allows you to work without worrying about the underlying file formats used by these geospatial file formats. Key features supported by this API are as follow.
Working with ESRI ShapeFiles and GeoJSON File Formats Single API for reading multiple Geographic file formats Create ESRI Shape and GeoJSON File Formats Read ESRI Shape File and GeoJSON files Get features count from Shape File Retrieve Attributes information from Shape File Iterate over all features of a layer Get values of feature attributes from a layer Filter features by attribute value Extract features from Shape file and export to GeoJSON format Specify attribute value length Check feature for null values Convert polygon shape file to string shape file Support for Working with Geometries Work with a number of Geometries Create Points and Multipoint geometry types Generate Line and Line Strings with specified geographic information Define Polygon and Multipolygon geometry shape Create Polygons with holes Get information of Geometry types Count geometries in a geometry shape Iterate over Points contained in Geometry Conversion Between Formats Inter-convert between ESRI shape and GeoJSON file format Control Attributes information adjustment during conversion from GeoJSON to Shape File</description></item></channel></rss>