<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 17.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 17.12
Major News Xamarin
Starting from 17.12 release, Aspose.Words for Android via Xamarin, Aspose.Words for iOS via Xamarin and Aspose.Words for Mac via Xamarin have become part of Aspose.Words for .NET. Few breaking changes have been made:
External reference to SkiaSharp has been added (in previous versions SkiaSharp was merged into Aspose.Words for Xamarin dlls) Native graphics objects (Android.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 17.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 17.11
Major Features There are 102 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
LINQ Reporting Engine supports dynamic shape background coloring. Improved optional hyphen handling and fixed related infinite loop issue. Improved floating table re-breaking in specific scenarios where content of a table used to be lost outside of a page. Improved table grid computation when cells contain tab characters.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 17.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 17.10
Major Features There are 76 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
&amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t add extra space for raised/lowered characters&amp;rdquo; compatibility option is supported. Multiple improvements in RTL and Asian text handling. LINQ Reporting Engine supports dynamic chart series removal. ‘Black and white’ images with one bit per pixel format rendering implemented. PixelFormat.Format1bppIndexed was introduced.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 17.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 17.9
Major Features There are 76 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Caching of shading patterns for PDF output implemented. The output size of PDF documents with the repeating images (e.g. in header/footer) is now significantly reduced. Precaching of printer settings implemented. Calling of AsposeWordsPrintDocument.CachePrinterSettings() reduces the time for the first call of Print() method making the sequential calls of Print() method uniform.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 17.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 17.8
Major Features There are 85 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
A significant optimization of PDF rendering engine has been carried out. Compression of document structure data and cross-reference table in PDF 1.5 output. Now the output PDF documents with the logical structure are much smaller. Image tag in Fixed HTML documents can now contain an alternative text string.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 17.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 17.7
Major Features There are 88 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Rendering into PCL format (Printer Command Language) was implemented. New saving format introduced – “SaveFormat.Pcl”. Please note that custom fonts is not yet supported. The proper algorithm for rendering of shapes with automatic size textboxes (i.e. closest to MS Word output) implemented.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 17.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 17.6
Major Features There are 82 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added feature to Automatically adjust space between Asian and Latin text, numbers. Throw warnings when an external resource in HTML could not be loaded. Track changes view settings in LibreOffice. Added ability to reference to data from parent region in child regions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 17.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 17.5
Major Features There are 84 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
MailMerge and Metafile rendering performance are improved. Support TOA, IMPORT, INCLUDE, SHAPE fields. API to bind SDT to CustomXML properties is provided. Implemented support for ShapeLayoutLikeWW8 compatibility option. Improved calculation of width of spaces in Asian text. Improved text wrapping for lines consisting of many tabs.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 17.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 17.4
Major Features There are 80 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
CompareOptions class introduced to allow customer specify comparison settings. Custom Xml Data Properties is now supported for RTF format. Implemented support for baseline alignment in asian text. Improved table split for vertically merged cells in combination with atleast height. Improved table grid calculation for horizontally merged cells.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 17.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 17.3.0
Major Features There are 67 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
new public OfficeMath properties: MathObjectType, Justification, DisplayType Full support for Word 2013 documents (roundtrip to/from DOCX) Variables support and more new features are introduced in LINQ Reporting Engine. Font substitution mechanism improved. Now Aspose.Words evaluates all related fields in FontInfo (Panose, Sig etc) and finds the closest match among the available font sources.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 17.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 17.2.0
Major Features There are 46 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Export fonts to HTML in Base64 encoding Added HtmlSaveOptions.ResourceFolder and HtmlSaveOptions.ResourceFolderAlias public properties Exposed access to Height/Width of Text Frames Improved control over BiDi text direction elements Non-bidi fields that contain hided bidi whitespaces are properly resolved Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-12975 Math equation&amp;rsquo;s alignment is changed in output Pdf Bug WORDSNET-13516 Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 17.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-words-for-net-17-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 17.1.0
Major Features There are 80 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added public API to insert online video via DocumentBuilder.InsertOnlineVideo TxtSaveOptions.ForcePageBreaks public property SaveOptions.MemoryOptimization public property New public API class FrameFormat available in Paragraph.FrameFormat Support for DOCX roundtrip of multiple MS Word 2013 native document options added Supported DOCX roundtrip of Effect Container element  DOCX Roundtrip of Extension lists suppororted for Charts and other graphics Shape texture brush with EMF image rendering implemented Shape positioning inside tables precision improved Implemented support for &amp;lsquo;FitText&amp;rsquo; attribute Improved space shrink logic for Asian text Improved Unicode normalization performance during layout Improved handling of invalid hyphenation dictionaries Improved handling of collapsed table rows Improved extracting document outline when TOC headings contain hidden entries Fixed positioning issue with Arabic list labels Fixed height issue with LTR list labels in RTL paragraphs Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-11066 TOC is built incorrectly Bug WORDSNET-11779 /hidden cell break/ Docx to Pdf conversion issue with table border Bug WORDSNET-11962 /LTR font metrics for RTL paragraph list/ A paragraph incorrectly renders at the end of previous page in PDF Bug WORDSNET-12214 /LTR font metrics for RTL paragraph list/ Extra page after DOCX to image Bug WORDSNET-12234 Document.</description></item></channel></rss>