<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.12
Long-style includes Since 23.8, Aspose.Tasks for C++ uses long-style includes to prevent header name clashing. Please refer to Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.8 release notes to learn how to switch your project to use long-style includes. We&amp;rsquo;ll continue the short-style includes support until January, 2024, inclusive.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-11060 Fix performance degradation when saving the specific project to XML Enhancement TASKSNET-11048 Add validation which checks that calendar names are unique Enhancement TASKSNET-4596 Implement writing of Task and Resource Filters for MPP14+ formats Enhancement TASKSNET-11044 Fix filters added via Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.11
Long-style includes Since 23.8, Aspose.Tasks for C++ uses long-style includes to prevent header name clashing. Please refer to Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.8 release notes to learn how to switch your project to use long-style includes. We&amp;rsquo;ll continue the short-style includes support until January, 2024, inclusive.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-11004 Add writing of Project.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.10
Long-style includes Since 23.8, Aspose.Tasks for C++ uses long-style includes to prevent header name clashing. Please refer to Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.8 release notes to learn how to switch your project to use long-style includes. We&amp;rsquo;ll continue the short-style includes support until January, 2024, inclusive.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-11003 Add validation which ensures that Project.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-9-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.9.
Long-style includes Since 23.8, Aspose.Tasks for C++ uses long-style includes to prevent header name clashing. Please refer to Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.8 release notes to learn how to switch your project to use long-style includes. We&amp;rsquo;ll continue the short-style includes support until January, 2024, inclusive.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10984 Add duplicated Task Uids validation check Enhancement TASKSNET-10970 Fix the resource unit cannot be automatically 100% when adding resources to the exported mpp file Bug TASKSNET-10982 Fix calculation of early and late dates when task has constraints Bug TASKSNET-10981 Fix exception when setting license from embedded resource Bug TASKSNET-10977 Fix writing of tasks without assignments to XML format Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.8.
Significant changes since 23.8 release - the &amp;ldquo;long-style&amp;rdquo; includes To avoid header name conflicts, since version 23.8 all library headers are moved to the separated directory. All existing projects will continue to work without changes, but you need to fix existing header references in your source files according to the new requirements. To do so:
First, make sure that the project build runs without errors.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.7.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10948 Add reading of incomplete baselines Enhancement TASKSNET-10947 Set WeekDay.DayWorking = true when working times is added Enhancement TASKSNET-10933 Add checks before saving to MPP which verify that UniqueId is not greater than max allowed UniqueIds Enhancement TASKSNET-10887 Add reading of Unit of Measure&amp;rsquo;s abbrevation from Primavera XER and P6XML formats to Resource.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.6.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10914 Fix reading of ResourceAssignment.ActualCost from XER format: OvertimeCost should be added Bug TASKSNET-10913 Fix writing of base calendars to MPP15+ formats Bug TASKSNET-10912 Fix escaping of values when exporting project to CSV format Bug TASKSNET-10909 Fix incorrect rendering of timescale when units are set to TimescaleUnit.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.5.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10892 Add Prj.AutoCalculateAssignmentCosts property to allow control of auto calculation of Asn.RemainingCost and Asn.Cost Enhancement TASKSNET-10893 Fix &amp;lsquo;TimeSpan overflowed because the duration is too long&amp;rsquo; exception when reading project with cost resource from XER format Bug TASKSNET-10891 Fix reading of Tsk.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.4.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10579 Add support of .NET 6.0 for non-Windows operating systems New Feature TASKSNET-10742 [Breaking change] Replace usages of System.Drawing.StringAlignment with Aspose.Tasks.Visualization.StringAlignment Enhancement TASKSNET-10832 Fix logic of UseProjectDefaultFont flag when project is rendered to HTML, PDF or Image formats Bug TASKSNET-10831 Fix NullReferenceException when accessing AssignmentBaseline.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.3.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10802 Add reading and writing of assignment&amp;rsquo;s hyperlink from / to MPP format Enhancement TASKSNET-10794 Add enum-typed DurationType, ActivityType and PercentCompletetype properties to PrimaveraTaskProperties Enhancement TASKSNET-10788 Add &amp;ldquo;LoadProject&amp;rdquo; method to PrimaveraXmlReader and PrimaveraXerReader Enhancement TASKSNET-10784 Add initialization of View data in projects read from non-MPP format Enhancement TASKSNET-10771 Add reading of &amp;lsquo;Calendar for Scheduling Relationship Lag&amp;rsquo; from Primavera XML and XER formats Enhancement TASKSNET-10768 Add reading of ActualExpenseCost, RemainingExpenseCost, ActualLaborCost, ActualMaterialCost, ActualNonlaborCost, ActualTotalCost for projects read from XER of Primavera P6XML formats Enhancement TASKSNET-4180 Implement consistent API for Task, Resource, Assignment notes Enhancement TASKSNET-10804 Fix reading and writing of Leveling Delay field from \ to MPP format Bug TASKSNET-10796 Fix writing of Task.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.2.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10765 Add an option which allows to control whether dates in timescale section of a view is rendered to the end of a page Enhancement TASKSNET-10773 Fix persistence of Assignment&amp;rsquo;s guid when reading and writing a project from\to XER and P6XML formats. Bug TASKSNET-10772 Fix calculation of task&amp;rsquo;s calendar when reading Task dependent activity from file in XER format Bug TASKSNET-10770 Fix reading and generation of timephased data for assignments of tasks with elapsed duration Bug TASKSNET-10766 Fix &amp;lsquo;System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/cpp/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-cpp-23-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for C++ 23.1.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10758 Add an API to access values of Labor Units for projects read from Primavera formats Enhancement TASKSNET-10756 Fix reading of task priority column for MPX files where Priority column was saved using enum values. Enhancement TASKSNET-10755 Add an API to access fractional number values of Physical Percent Complete and PercentComplete for projects read from Primavera formats.</description></item></channel></rss>