<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.12
Key Summary Category PSDNET-757 Support converting layers to Smart Object Layer Feature PSDNET-764 SmartObjectLayer.ReplaceContents method throws NullReferenceException if we try to add PSB file Bug PSDNET-773 Incorrect rendering of CMYK 8-bit and CMYK 16-bit Images, if the layer is bigger than Canvas Bug PSDNET-782 Saved PSB file can be opened with our API, but cannot with Photoshop Bug PSDNET-783 If we trying to change Smart Layer in a specific PSD with a shared data source we get an exception Bug PSDNET-172 Renaming of FileFormatVersion to PsdVersion to avoid confusion Enhancement PSDNET-620 Remove Compact framework configuration from Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.11
Key Summary Category PSDNET-713 Aspose.PSD can not convert PSD to other Color Modes/BitDepth without saving them as files Feature PSDNET-754 Add ability to copy Smart Object Layer in the PSD image Feature PSDNET-267 Exception on loading and saving the PSD file with Layer Effects Bug PSDNET-579 Method &amp;ldquo;Image.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.10 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.10
Key Summary Category PSDNET-565 Exception on saving the specific PSD file with text layers Bug PSDNET-680 Fonts are lost after round-trips with Aspose.PSD Bug PSDNET-704 Rendering of the Smart Object Layer Feature PSDNET-707 Support of the Smart Object non-destructive transforms Feature PSDNET-711 Text Layer Is Shifted After saving without any changes Bug PSDNET-720 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.9
Key Summary Category PSDNET-408 Support of SoLEResource (Smart Object Layer External resource) Feature PSDNET-614 Support of Linked Smart objects Feature PSDNET-615 Support of Embedded Smart objects Feature PSDNET-690 Updating text in given PSD file and saving it changes some layer and many text parameters Bug PSDNET-696 FillLayer are not updated after the creation and can not be rendered correctly Bug PSDNET-712 Regression: Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.8
Key Summary Category PSDNET-390 Support of PlLdResource (placed layer resource for Smart Object Layer) Feature PSDNET-400 Support of SoLdResource (Smart Object Layer Data resource) Feature PSDNET-693 Add Object Array and Unit Array structures support: ObAr / UnFl signatures Feature PSDNET-600 Fix saving modified PSD image with CMYK ColorMode 16 bit per channel Bug PSDNET-664 Underline and strikethrough lost after focusing on the text in file saved with Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.7
Key Summary Category PSDNET-673 Support of LnkE Resource Feature PSDNET-392 Support of britResource (Resource of Brightness/Contrast Adjustment Layer) Feature PSDNET-629 Change Exception Message on trying to open not supported formats as an image Enhancement PSDNET-594 Failed to save LayerMask Bug PSDNET-597 If we save PSD file after the creation of new Layer Group we get Photoshop warning on the file opening Bug PSDNET-618 Clipping mask not applying to the folder Bug PSDNET-625 Cannot open file with Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.6
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-606 Support of LnkE Resource Feature PSDNET-386 Support of britResource (Resource of Brightness/Contrast Adjustment Layer) Feature PSDNET-219 Move DefaultReplacementFont setting into ImageOptionsBase class Enhancement PSDNET-596 Layer Group with not PassThrough Blending Mode Is Not Rendered Bug PSDNET-610 NullReference Exception when trying to convert particular Psd file to image Bug PSDNET-636 Resizing PSD files works incorrect if there is a mask in the adjustment layer that has empty bounds Bug PSDNET-611 OverflowException when trying to open particular Psd file Bug PSDNET-565 Psd Image with RGB mode 16 bit/channel updates layers only on preview Bug PSDNET-652 Exception on loading specific PSD file with the compound LnkE Resource and adobeStockLicenseState property Bug PSDNET-640 PSD Layer Mask changes are discarded on save Bug PSDNET-593 Saving of AI File to Jpeg2000 Format doesn&amp;rsquo;t work Bug PSDNET-638 Incorrect Layer Order after you add Layer Group to empty Layer Group Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: P:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.5 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.5
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-595 Support of Layer Masks for Layer Groups Feature PSDNET-201 Support for document conversion progress Feature PSDNET-275 Support of Nvrt Resource (Invert Adjustment Layer Resource) Feature PSDNET-124 Support of Grayscale ColorMode PSD Image saving with 16 bit per channel Feature PSDNET-589 Refactoring of Examples on GitHub Enhancement PSDNET-587 Text Alignment through ITextPortion doesn&amp;rsquo;t work for right-to-left languages.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.4
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-567 Support of the &amp;lsquo;Vector Origination Data&amp;rsquo; resource Feature PSDNET-373 Support of lclrResource (Sheet color setting) Feature PSDNET-563 Support properties from LengthRecord data. (Path operations (boolean operations), index of the shape in the layer, count of the bezier knot records) Feature PSDNET-425 Support of Image Section Resource #1010 Background color Feature PSDNET-530 Adding of Fill Layers at runtime Feature PSDNET-424 Support of Image Section Resource #1009 Border information Feature PSDNET-592 Support of Layers in AI Format Files Feature PSDNET-256 Support Reading and Editing of Gradient Overlay Layer Effect Feature PSDNET-257 Rendering of Gradient Overlay Layer Effect Feature PSDNET-585  The GradientOverlayEffect.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.3 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.3
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-188 Support of .Net Core Feature PSDNET-523 Convert Adobe Illustrator files into PDFs Feature PSDNET-212 Add ability to render different styles in one text layer Feature PSDNET-144 Support of Black and White Adjustment Layer Feature PSDNET-233 Add support of export AI format (Version 8) to other formats Feature PSDNET-540 Support of PassThrough Blending Mode processing (Used for Layer Group Only).</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.2 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-net-20-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 20.2
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-206 Improvement of ability to render different colors text in Text Layer Feature PSDNET-369 Support of clbl resource (Layer resource contains info about Blend clipping elements) Feature PSDNET-274 Support of blwh resource (Resource contains Black &amp;amp; White Adjustment Layer Data) Feature PSDNET-230 Ability to export Layer Group to Jpeg/Png/Tiff/Gif/Bmp/Jpeg2000/Psd/Psb/Pdf Feature PSDNET-372 Support of lspf Resource (Contains settings about Layer Protected setting) Feature PSDNET-370 Support of infx resource (Contains data about Blending of interior elements) Feature PSDNET-251 Refactoring of PsdImage and Layer to change Transformation behavior (Correct resize/rotate/crop for layer masks if we transform one layer separately) Enhancement PSDNET-276 In some globalization settings, AI Image raster image can not be opened Bug PSDNET-194  After performing the FlipRotate operation on Layer, PSD Image becomes unreadable Bug PSDNET-177.</description></item></channel></rss>