<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 22.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 22.12.
Major Features There are 78 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Update links in Java ApiReferences Support Ripemd160 digital sign for PDF documents Implemented an abbility to specify the particular Margin type for the given section. The new public properties ThemeColor and TintAndShade were introduced. Implemented rendering of the linear trendline formula for DrawingML charts rendering.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 22.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 22.11.
Major Features There are 70 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Update API references for Java Implemented custom colored/grayscale printing mode. Added an ability to create the new structured document tags of Citation type. Implemented field updating progress tracking. Introduced the new property which allows to embed OLE attachments from the source document to the output PDF document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 22.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 22.10.
Major Features There are 84 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented modern style for zipped javadoc Implemented an ability to ignore StructuredDocumentTags upon FindReplace. HtmlSaveOptions.MetafileFormat now affects OLE objects and controls. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release (Reported by Java Users) Key Summary Category WORDSNET-24142 Getter for AbstractNumId New Feature WORDSJAVA-1407 Implement modern style for zipped javadoc New Feature WORDSJAVA-1176 Public Javadoc for com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 22.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 22.9.
Major Features There are 112 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Changed aspose-words-22.9.pom TxtLoadOptions was extended with new AutoNumberingDetection option. Implemented an ability to cache the header/footer shapes to reduce the size of the output PDF file. Added a new feature to get FieldEQ as OfficeMath. Allowed creation of structured document tags of Group type at Row level.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 22.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 22.8.
Major Features There are 145 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
AZW3 (also called KF8) file format is now supported for import and export. Implemented support for cell spacing in tables upon rendering. Improved font substitution for symbols. Improved the rotation algorithm of axis labels of the charts. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release (Reported by Java Users) Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-2675 Regular check&amp;amp;update of OSGI compatibility New Feature WORDSJAVA-2297 RenderedDocument example produces unwanted content and &amp;lsquo;NULLs&amp;rsquo; Bug WORDSNET-21008 PDF is losing the table cell style after DOCX to PDF conversion Bug WORDSNET-15723 Table border is lost after conversion from DOCX to PDF Bug WORDSNET-16850 DOC to PDF Number of Pages Decreased Bug WORDSNET-17448 Table layout changes during PDF conversion for a Hebrew file Bug WORDSNET-19219 TOC page number issue after Section having Landscape orientation and Section break Bug WORDSNET-21009 Incorrect rendering of Table spanning across multiple TextColumns Bug WORDSNET-21050 Spacing between Table Cells not preserved during DOCX to PDF conversion Bug WORDSNET-23630 Part of content is moved to previous page Bug WORDSNET-23360 DOCX to PDF: Table rendered incorrectly Bug WORDSNET-24088 InvalidOperationException when converting MHTML to DOC Bug WORDSNET-23705 Row is moved to previous page upon rendering Bug WORDSNET-23975 Font size is changed after rendering document Bug WORDSNET-24106 WordML to DOCX: Missing content Bug WORDSNET-24052 Line moved to the next page Bug WORDSNET-23860 NullReferenceException is thrown upon rendering document Bug WORDSNET-23861 Position of endnotes is incorrect after rendering Bug Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release (Reported by .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 22.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 22.7.
Major Features There are 87 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented support of WCAG 2.0 PDF. Implemented our own glyph outlines parsing for OpenType(CFF) fonts. Introduced new HTML import mode for block-level elements. Added support of the DATABASE fields. Provided an ability to set shadow formatting of the shape object. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release (Reported by Java Users) Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-2738 Incorrect LeftIndent value returns Bug WORDSJAVA-2689 LoadingProgressCallback does not cancels at set progress value.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 22.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 22.6.
Major Features There are 71 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented an ability to convert PDF documents to fixed page formats with high fidelity and performance. DrawingML charts public API was extended to support gradient, texture and pattern fills. Implemented a solid text fill effect inheritance exception that mimics the behavior of MS Word.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 22.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 22.5.
Major Features There are 130 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added support for loading EPUB documents. Added support for loading XML documents. Added support of &amp;ldquo;Envelope No. 10&amp;rdquo; page size for printing. Implemented rendering of a border box around the MathML formulas and the strike lines. Improved font detection when rendering characters in MathML formulas.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 22.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 22.3.
Major Features There are 91 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added saving to PDF 2.0 and several other improvements in PDF output. Improved DML chart axis scaling algorithm. Saving progress notifications were extended for TXT format. Improved table comparing algorithm. Provided comments syntax in LINQ Reporting. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release (Reported by Java Users) Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-2600 XmlDataSourceCore fails to load child Node with the same name as the table plus an attribute.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 22.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 22.4.
Major Features There are 71 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added saving to PDFA-4 and several other improvements in PDF output. Implemented reading of Photoshop metadata resolution in Jpeg images. Provided an ability to manipulate with DrawingML chart legend entries. Implemented an ability to specify the name of an xls/xlsx file the DrawingML chart is linked to.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 22.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 22.2.
Major Features There are 114 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
AZW3 format (KF8 is another name of the format) is now supported for loading. Added an ability to get custom field data which is associated with the field. Saving progress notifications were extended for HTML-based and XAML-based flow formats. Provided an ability to convert Shapes to SVG images upon export to HTML, MHTML or EPUB.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 22.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-java-22-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 22.1.
Major Features There are 76 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented rendering into PDF with PDF/UA-1 compliance. This option assumes compliance with document special accessibility requirements. Improved rendering of operators in MathML formulas. Introduced a new option to control conflicting styles behavior upon import. Added an ability to get saving progress notifications through the SaveOptions.</description></item></channel></rss>