<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.12.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Read geospatial data from SQL Server database. Support multiple SRS in one layer. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-489 Read geospatial data from SQL Server New Feature GISNET-500 Support multiple SRS in one layer Improvement GISNET-485 Support spatial index (.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.11.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Read geospatial data from PostGIS database. Write geospatial data to PostGIS database. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-474 Read geospatail data from PostGIS New Feature GISNET-484 Write geospatail data to PostGIS New Feature GISNET-481 Add GeometryGenerator symbolizer New Feature GISNET-479 Import RasterMarker from SLD Improvement GISNET-480 Add new attribute data types Improvement Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes This version includes certain Public API Changes that affect the existing implementations.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.10.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Specify raster image to be rendered on map via RasterImageMarker. Specify measurements in &amp;ldquo;MetersOnEarth&amp;rdquo; unit. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-478 Raster image marker New Feature GISNET-397 &amp;lsquo;MetersOnEarth&amp;rsquo; unit. New Feature GISNET-476 NullReferenceException in UseAttributesIndex Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes None</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.9.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Build spatial and attributes indices Use these indices to filter features in vector layer. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-348 Filtering and Indexing New Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes None</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.8.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-8-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-8-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.8.2.
Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-462 GisException is thrown while reading a GeoJson with large integers Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes None</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.8.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-8-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-8-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.8.1.
Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-458 GisException is thrown while reading a valid shapefile Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes None</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.8.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Label vector layer features on a map. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-409 Feature labeling New Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes None</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.7.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-7-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-7-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.7.1.
Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-443 ArgumentOutOfRangeException when reading a shapefile Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes None</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.7.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Import styles from SLD MarkerLine and MarkerPatternFill symbolizers Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-383 SLD styles import New Feature GISNET-391 MarkerLine symbolizer New Feature GISNET-392 MarkerPatternFill symbolizer New Feature GISNET-419 SimpleLine with offset throws OutOfMemoryException Bug GISNET-421 ArgumentException is throws when rendering SimpleLine with offset Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes None</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.6.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-6-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-6-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.6.1.
Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-420 Invalid value of a Number field error reported in some cases for NULL values Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes None</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.6.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Export maps to raster image formats Support of EPSG:3857 WGS 84 / Pseudo-Mercator Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-369 Support for EPSG:3857 WGS 84 / Pseudo-Mercator New Feature GISNET-367 Export maps to PNG New Feature GISNET-393 Export maps to JPEG New Feature GISNET-396 Export maps to BMP New Feature GISNET-339 Detect more encoding names in .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.5.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Create spatial reference system by EPSG code Add possibility to specify spatial reference system when rendering map. Add possibility to specify padding when rendering maps. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-365 Add possibility to specify spatial reference system when rendering map New Feature GISNET-359 Create spatial reference system by EPSG code New Feature GISNET-345 Add possibility to specify padding when rendering maps New Feature GISNET-364 Convert SRS WKT to ESRI format when writing Shapefile and FileGDB layer Improvement GISNET-343 Make it simpler to specify SRS for new layers Improvement GISNET-356 Error when empty LayeredSymbolizer is rendering Bug GISNET-355 Evaluation limit error during map rendering Bug GISNET-354 Exception is thrown when converting shapefile layer Bug GISNET-332 Wrong coordinates are read from MapInfo TAB Bug GISNET-330 Error when parsing a symbol shape code in a MIF file Bug GISNET-327 Error when reading a feature in KML files that contain gx prefix Bug GISNET-326 Error when no outer boundary in polygon when reading KML file Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes No backward-incompatible changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.4.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Map rendering API and support for export to SVG Convert between datums if SRS WKT definition is not complete Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-292 Map rendering API and support for export to SVG New Feature GISNET-336 Convert between datums if SRS WKT definition is not complete New Feature GISNET-342 Remove public constructor from GPX driver Bug GISNET-319 Ambiguous error message for missing files Bug GISNET-318 Extra content at the end of the document if overwriting existing file Bug GISNET-316 Error when specifying paths in the same folder as the executable Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes No backward-incompatible changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.3.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Working with GIS data located in places different from the local file system. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-299 Support for Opening Layer from Stream New Feature GISNET-246 Open KML file using a web request, byte array, and stream New Feature GISNET-298 Geometry.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.2.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Support of MapInfo TAB and MapInfo Interchange file formats. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-267 MapInfo Formats New Feature GISNET-282 Issue reading SHP file Bug GISNET-284 The tenth character in shapefile attribute name is changed Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes new MapInfoTab driver new MapInfoInterchange driver new MapInfoTabOptions class new MapInfoInterchangeOptions class</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-gis-for-net-19-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 19.1.
Major Features Major features and improvements in this release:
Support of curved geometries. Our object model now includes non-linear geometries, like CircularString and CurvePolygon. Such geometries can be read from and written to FileGDB, WKT, WKB, and GML. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-254 Curve Geometries New Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes None</description></item></channel></rss>