<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 18.12 - December 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for Java 18.12.
Improvements and Changes Summary Category Add support for standard 3d printing format AMF New Feature  Archive-based file format detection  Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Please view the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 18.11 - November 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for Java 18.11.
Improvements and Changes Summary Category Problem with UnitScaleFactor property Bug Problem with Embedded Textures Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Please view the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 18.10 - October 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for Java 18.10.
Improvements and Changes Summary Category Support for .NET Core platform New Feature Allow user to turn off compression when saving FBX binary files New Feature Improve FBX import performance Enhancement Improve FBX Binary write performance Enhancement ImportException while opening huge FBX files Bug Problem with UnitScaleFactor property Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Please view the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 18.9 - September 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for Java 18.9.
Other Improvements and Changes Summary Category CancellationToken support New Feature FBX ExportException - High Polygon Count Bug ImportException while opening huge FBX files Bug Not all properties from FBX&amp;rsquo;s global settings are loaded into the AssetInfo Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Please view the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 18.8 - August 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for Java 18.8.
Other Improvements and Changes Summary Category Export glTF files with draco compression New Feature Optimize memory consumption for mesh indices Enhancement Use Aspose.3D with Unity3D Bug Read COLLADA files referencing in same folder Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Please view the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 18.7 - July 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for Java 18.7.
Other Improvements and Changes Summary Category Add Draco 2.2 import support New Feature Add Draco 2.2 export support New Feature Import glTF files with draco compression New Feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Please view the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 18.6 - June 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for Java 18.6.
Other Improvements and Changes Summary Category Siemens JT Version 9 import support New Feature FBX to GLTF - the output GLTF loader fails in three.js Bug Input FBX - an import error occurred Bug Rendering - the wrong operand type error Bug RVM to glTF - an empty document is created Bug RVM to WavefrontOBJ - an empty document is created Bug Input FBX - Unsupported VertexElement attribute BinormalsIndex error occurred Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Please view the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 18.5 - May 2018</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-3d-for-java-18-5-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.3D for Java 18.5 Release Notes We are pleased to announce that the first version 18.5 of Aspose.3D for Java API has been released. After the release of Aspose.3D for .NET API, we have received requests from clients to build the same API for their Java applications. It is an auto-ported version from its equivalent .NET version 18.5. Aspose.3D for Java API is built to create, edit, manipulate and save 3D formats.</description></item></channel></rss>