<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 18.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 18.12.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42745 Change returned value for getting Connection points New Feature CELLSJAVA-42662 Provide ability to export range as HTML New Feature CELLSJAVA-42746 Data bars are missing when XLSX is converted to HTML New Feature CELLSJAVA-42747 Value still exists when XLSX is converted to HTML New Feature CELLSJAVA-42634 Convert left right ribbon shape to image Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42713 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 18.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-18-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-18-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 18.9.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42680 Disable Pivot Table Ribbon New Feature  CELLSJAVA-42568 Protect workbook and worksheet in ODS file New Feature  CELLSJAVA-42668 Support multiple values when using class style (Linked to: CELLSJAVA-42635) Enhancement  CELLSJAVA-42627 Unable to extract Smart Art images correctly - Shape to image conversion (CELLSJAVA-42619)  Enhancement  CELLSJAVA-42677 Interruption issue with saving XLSX file process Enhancement  CELLSJAVA-42687 Hyperlink not working when referenced from other sheet Enhancement  CELLSJAVA-42672 The output PDF document is too big  Bug  CELLSJAVA-42671 Hyperlinks issue when viewing the output Excel file in MS Excel Japanese version Bug  CELLSJAVA-42667 Getting &amp;lsquo;#NUM!</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 18.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 18.6.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42523 Use FIPS compliant version of Bouncy Castle in Aspose.Cells APIs New Feature  CELLSJAVA-42550 The concurrent conversion to PDF while each workbook has his own private (exclusive) set of fonts  New Feature  CELLSJAVA-42339 Implement custom data sorting in Pivot Table report via Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 18.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-18-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2018/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-18-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 18.3.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42493 Provide an option to decide whether exporting workbook properties New Feature  CELLSJAVA-42491 Provide an option to decide whether exporting document properties New Feature  CELLSJAVA-42498 Create a PdfBookmarkEntry for a chart sheet New Feature  CELLSJAVA-42509 Add LoadDataFilterOptions.NAMES constant to filter defined names when loading workbook New Feature  CELLSJAVA-42519 PdfSaveOptions.</description></item></channel></rss>