<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 19.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 19.12.
Major Features Elliptic Curve Digital Signature Algorithm (ECDSA) is supported now. Aspose.Words.Shaping.Harfbuzz plugin for x86 Unix-based environments. &amp;ldquo;Truncate Font Height&amp;rdquo; MS-Word compatibility option is supported now. Document(BufferedInputStream) bug is fixed. (For performance, better to use Document(String) anyway). JavaDoc bugfixes and updates. Conversion to PDF 1.7 standard is now supported. User-installed fonts are now supported upon using SystemFontSource on Windows10.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 19.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 19.11.
Major Features Harfbuzz Shaper plugin supported on Unix-based OSs. Provided an ability to work with Web Extensions, new classes allow to customize elements and attributes that extend the XML vocabulary for Office Add-ins representation. Added an ability to customize the formatting of the horizontal rule shape. Improved character spacing calculation when &amp;lsquo;use printer metrics&amp;rsquo; option is set. Macros support improved.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 19.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 19.10.
Major Features JSON data source functionality for Reporting is implemented for Java. Main Maven POM automation: choose the right JDK jar version, download plugins only if needed. Implemented DocumentDirection option that allows specifying the direction to flow the text in a document. Implemented proper scaling for shapes inside ‘graphicFrame’ container for DrawingML rendering. Improved &amp;ldquo;inline/not inline&amp;rdquo; validation for OMath objects when rendering.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 19.9.
Major Features Advanced typography based on HarfBuzz shaper. Provided API to write and modify VBA macros. Implemented ability to create repeating section structured document tags. Simplified work with XML and CSV data sources for LINQ Reporting Engine. Improved rendering of “Sitka Banner”, “Sitka Display”, “Sitka Heading”, “Sitka Small”, “Sitka Subheading”, “Sitka Text” and “Cambria Math” fonts. Implemented OpenType number spacing.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 19.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 19.8.
Major Features Option to call HarfBuzz library (on Windows only yet) for better kerning. Separate Aspose.Words jdk16.jar is publically available on Aspose Downloads site. API Examples are fully updated and improved. Aspose.Words for Java is tested on Java 12. Simplified TIFFImageWriter is used when external TIFF image libs (JAI, etc.) are not available. Implemented an option that allows specifying whether to work with the original or revised version of a document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 19.7.
Major Features Cryptographic libraries are updated to eliminate known possible security vulnerabilities. Aspose.Words.jdk16.jar compatibility with old Java 6,7 and 8 environments. Implemented basic reader and writer for Markdown format. Implemented public API for dealing with linked text boxes. Implemented feature to detect SmartArt shape. Added property Revision.Group. Supported dynamic list numbering restart for LINQ Reporting Engine. Released Advanced Typography package, kerning feature works now.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 19.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 19.6.
Major Features Improved loading license in multi-thread environment. Provided API to Extract VBA Macros from Word Document. Added a new DocSaveOptions.AlwaysCompressMetafiles option. Implemented table style public API. Improved rendering of CurvedArrow shapes with basic and custom adjustment points. Improved rendering of DrawingML charts with scaling of the vertical axis if the chart legend has a manual layout. FontInfo substitution was tuned to prefer symbolic fonts as a substitution for symbolic fonts and regular fonts as a substitution for regular fonts.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 19.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 19.5.
Major Features Jdk1.6 build option is added for customers that request it. Docx-to-Pdf Performance optimization: cold start time decreased from 20% to 3 times depending on the application. Docx-to-Pdf Performance optimization: warm tests time improved from 2 to 10 times depending on the application. Mailmerge performance is raised up to 50% for tasks of particular types. Removed obsolete properties and methods related to font substitution settings in FontSettings class.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 19.4.
Major Features MailMerge performance improved. Cold startup time improved by 10%. Added a new ImportFormatOptions class for more flexible control over importing tasks. Provide API to change how text is vertically aligned within the Text Box. Added a new ImportFormatOptions.KeepSourceNumbering option for use in import operations. Added a new ImportFormatOptions.IgnoreTextBoxes option for use in import operations. Added property PdfSaveOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 19.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 19.3.
Major Features Release JAR is upgraded to JDK 7. Added feature to preserve the representation of legacy control characters while converting to OOXML formats. Added new public properties to the ChartAxis class. Added predefined font fallback settings for Google Noto fonts. Hyphenation logic improved. Fixed trailing spaces underlines in RTL paragraphs. Fixed issue with automatic frame width updates when the field is changed.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 19.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 19.2.
Major Features Supported inlining of syntax error messages into templates instead of exception throwing for LINQ Reporting Engine. Improved font fetching and substitution mechanism with corresponding API changes. Improved warnings for image processing issues when rendering to PDF. Improved font fallback rendering for full-width character Unicode ranges. Metafiles with &amp;ldquo;HeaderPlaceable&amp;rdquo; structure is now rendering regardless of structure checksum.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 19.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-java-19-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 19.1.
Major Features There are 55 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented the directed line caps rendering for Bezier curves in metafiles. Implemented processing of the stroke properties while rendering custom line caps in metafiles. Implemented support of Unicode font names while rendering to PDF. Implemented Tiff binarization threshold control via ImageSaveOptions.</description></item></channel></rss>