<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/cpp/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/cpp/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Cpp 18.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-cpp-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-cpp-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.BarCode for C++ 18.12.
All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODENET-37024 Not able to read dotted barcodes from TIFF images Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes None</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Barcode for Cpp 18.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-cpp-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-cpp-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Barcode for C++ 18.11.
New Features List or chart of prerequisites required to generate successful barcode image of any barcode type  Implemented UpcaGs1DatabarCoupon for new barcode generation API  Implemented Interpolation AutoSize mode  Create User Control for new generation API  Implemented MaxiCode and DotCode for new barcode generation API  GS1 DataBar Expanded Stacked barcode did not pass GS1 Canda barcode verification Added new barcode subsets to DecodeType  All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36791 Prepare preview version of new barcode generation API New Feature BARCODENET-36872 List or chart of prerequisites required to generate successful barcode image of any barcode type  New Feature BARCODENET-36941 Implement UpcaGs1DatabarCoupon for new barcode generation API  New Feature BARCODENET-36930 Implement Interpolation AutoSize mode  New Feature BARCODENET-36953 Create User Control for new generation API  New Feature BARCODENET-36923 Implement MaxiCode for new barcode generation API  New Feature BARCODENET-36922 Implement DotCode for new barcode generation API  New Feature BARCODENET-36713 Investigate new architecture of barcodes recognition filters.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Barcode for Cpp 18.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-cpp-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-cpp-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Barcode for C++ 18.6.
Aspose.Barcode for C++ has been launched. It allows you to add barcode generation &amp;amp; recognition capabilities to their own C++ applications.
Aspose.BarCode for C++ not only creates barcodes but also can export the generated barcodes to a verity of image formats in high quality. Moreover, the developers can easily manipulate the appearance of the generated barcodes such as background color, bar color, image quality, rotation angle, x-dimension, captions, size, resolution and much more.</description></item></channel></rss>