<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.12
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the November release of Aspose.SVG for NET.
We have added support for rendering SVG text with stroke-dasharray, stroke-linecap parameters. The CSS serialization algorithm has been updated according to the latest SVG specification. Public API changes: No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.11
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the November release of Aspose.SVG for NET. We has fixed issue with applying of the Gaussian Blur&amp;rsquo; effect to large bitmaps with high resolution. We have changed &amp;lsquo;page sizing&amp;rsquo; algorithm for &amp;lsquo;FitContent&amp;rsquo; mode. Now the page size will be resized even if the document content is smaller than the previously specified page size.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.10
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the October release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. In this release we have expanded the class PageSetup with a new option Sizing that allows to manage the page size considering content size and scaling content in accordnace with page size.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.9
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the September release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. In this release we have added a new feature for &amp;ldquo;vectorization&amp;rdquo; of text elements inside SVG documents. By the term &amp;ldquo;vectorization&amp;rdquo; we mean converting text into a set of graphic elements such as PATH, G, USE, RECT.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.8
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the August release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. In this release we have made the number of improvements:
Added support for the comp-op property with the following list of values : hue, saturation, color, luminosity; Fixed problem with processing units in methods GetCTM and GetScreenCTM in all classes inherited from SVGGraphicsElement class; Added support for calculating bounding boxes of non-shaped elements (SVGTextElement, SVGTSpanElement) inside the method GetBBox of SVGGraphicsElement class.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.7
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the July release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. In this release we have made the number of improvements:
added support for the comp-op property with the following list of values : clear, src, dst, src-over, dst-over, src-in, dst-in, src-out, dst-out, src-atop, dst-atop, xor, plus, overlay, color-dodge, color-burn, hard-light, soft-light, difference, exclusion; the algorithm processing the type of the &amp;lsquo;discrete transfer function&amp;rsquo; has been fixed; improved precision of GetBBox method.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.6
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the June release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. In this release we have made the following improvement:
Support for rendering (X)HTML content inside of the SVG elements was added. This new feature enables correct rendering of the HTML and XHTML elements embedded into SVG document (during conversion to supported formats).</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.5
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the May release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. In this release we have made the following improvements:
updated processing of many CSS properties according to the latest documentation; made some usability improvements, like, clarified the URL parsing exceptions and added new signatures to the Document creation methods.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.4
Major Features In this release we have made the following improvements:
The issue with the calculation of the transformation matrix during pagination was fixed. The text messages in watermarks have been changed in the evaluation mode with a purpose to be more informative. Moreover, several rules have been expanded to reach more understandable product behavior in evaluation mode.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.2
Major Features In this release we have made some improvements to the quality of rendering, these improvements are:
Improved pagination algorithm. Improved element&amp;rsquo;s bounding box calculation algorithm. Public API changes: Added APIs: No change
Removed APIs: No change</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-svg-for-net-20-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 20.1
First Public Release of Aspose.SVG for .NET We are pleased to announce the first public release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. Aspose.SVG provides a wide range of features for processing and rendering of SVG documents, such as:
Document tree manipulation, which allows to create, remove and edit elements Conversion to various output formats such as PDF, PNG, JPG, XPS and more Data extraction, which includes support of XPath queries, CSS Selectors and Element Traversal Please visit the Product Features page for further details and get the chance to download the first release of Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>