<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 16.12.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-12-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-12-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 16.12.0
Major Features There are 83 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Support of Hijri/Hebrew/Japanese/ThaiBuddhist and other Lunar and non-Gregorian Calendars Save to image formats can be fine-tuned by passing RenderingHints to ImageSaveOptions.GraphicsQualityOptions Analog of .Net&amp;rsquo;s DataTableReader Support of the &amp;ldquo;people&amp;rdquo; part (Word 2013 feature) StructuredDocumentTag extensions supported (Word 2013 feature) REVNUM, INFO fields supported Improved handling of hanging punctuation and hyphens in complex script content Improved handling of &amp;ldquo;Automatically adjust space between Asian text and numbers&amp;rdquo; compatibility option Improved paragraph alignment when text contains hidden content Improved reflow of vertically merged cells for complex table grid layout Implemented combining adjacent tables on document loading Path gradient fill support while rendering SVG implemented Leader lines rendering for all DrawingML Chart types (not only for pie-charts) implemented Styles are now properly applied for DrawingML Charts while rendering Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-1320 Docx to Png conversion issue with space width Bug WORDSJAVA-1437 Can&amp;rsquo;t read Docx with DML that contains tag with undeclared namespace.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 16.11.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-11-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-11-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 16.11.0
Major Features There are 76 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
FixedPageSaveOptions.OptimizeOutput option is implemented for all fixed page formats, improving the size of output documents. Output PDF now contains a valid document ID despite the compliancy settings (with or without PDF/A compliancy) Supporting MS Word 2013 features from various DOCX extensions specs.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 16.10.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-10-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-10-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 16.10.0
Major Features There are 117 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved importing of text in DOS Arabic or Hebrew encodings. Added feature to compare document as MS Word does. Added feature to get OOXML compliance version as determined from the loaded document content. Font fallback while rendering fonts of Myanmar Unicode range improved.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 16.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 16.8.0
Major Features There are 73 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Huge Mailmerge performance optimization. NumberFormats performance optimization. Pdf performance optimization. Performance optimization of Fonts catch. Shapes with the translucent fill rendering implemented in PDF and other fixed-page formats. Opacity parameter is now taken into account. New base class FixedPageSaveOptions added for all fixed page formats e.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 16.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 16.7.0
Major Features There are 144 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
A document page can now be saved in GIF format using SaveFormat.Gif in ImageSaveOptions. Font substitution rules improved. Now embedded font is used for substitution if available. Multilevel strings rendering in DrawingML Chart axis labels improved. OfficeMath objects now can be exported (optional) to HTML,MHTML or EPUB as mathml elements.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 16.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 16.6.0
Major Features There are 113 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Fast extraction from DOC format via PlainTextDocument class is faster by a factor of ten (at a cost). Saving DOCX as ISO 29500 Strict OOXML format is available now. Added support for outer document insertion to LINQ Reporting Engine. Added feature to insert empty values in chart series.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 16.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 16.5.0
Major Features There are 83 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved reflow performance for large paragraphs. Added explicit support of multiple data sources to LINQ Reporting Engine. SVG output with IE compatibility improved. Improved widow/orphan handling for tables. Improved asian text line breaking. Improved font metrics calculation for substituted fonts. Implemented support for SuppressEndnotes option.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 16.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 16.4.0
Major Features There are 106 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved the speed of cold document creation and loading. Import MathML from HTML documents. Improved positioning of pictures inside tables. PDF A1b compliancy improved. DML Charts effects support improved. Emf, Png and MailMerge performance improved. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-1297 Odt to Pdf conversion issue with font size Bug WORDSJAVA-1314 Contents become invisible after conversion from Odt to Docx Bug WORDSJAVA-1316 Odt to Pdf conversion issue with font size Bug WORDSJAVA-1333 Inline image not displayed.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 16.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 16.3.0
Major Features There are 94 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Further improvements to the speed and public API for plain text extraction. Render OfficeMath formulas to images separately from the document. Shape and OfficeMath can now be saved to SVG. Support for RC4 encryption. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-1241 ImageData.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 16.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 16.2.0
Major Features There are 103 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
SVM format supported Heuristic detection of Encoding of text files with or without BOM Fast extraction of plain text from flow-format documents is supported PageSavingCallback was introduced for all fixed-page based save formats Ability to determine if a run or a paragraph has format changes Font substitution while rendering fixed-page formats improved to mimic MS Word Axis logarithmic scale for DML charts rendering implemented WordArt shapes fit to Bezier curves rendering implemented: ArchUp(Curve), ArchDown(Curve), Circle(Curve) DrawingML shapes with guides are now scaled correctly DML charts rendering improved Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-1191 Canvas is stretched out in output Pdf Bug WORDSJAVA-1217 Shape size and bounds retrieval issue for the shapes Bug WORDSJAVA-1259 Chinese text does not render correctly in output HtmlFixed Bug WORDSJAVA-1262 Watermark (Shape) renders incorrectly in output Pdf Bug WORDSJAVA-1265 Watermark (shape) does not render correctly in output Pdf Bug WORDSJAVA-1304 Font get bold after/before Barcode.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 16.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-java-16-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 16.1
Aspose.Words for Java 16.1 Release Notes Major Features There are 139 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
EMF format is now supported Aspose.Words for Java passes the Veracode Security Scan Performance of PNG encoding/decoding improved x 1.5 times Implemented auto-fit table grid calculation for several classes of tables EMF+ images now can be rendered without the GDI+  Comments rendering improved Word 6.</description></item></channel></rss>