<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 19.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 19.12.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-41814 Support custom data sorting for the specific area in PivotTable report New Feature CELLSJAVA-43032 Add Validation.addArea (CellArea cellArea, boolean skipArea) or Validation.setAreas() method/overloads to the APIs New Feature CELLSJAVA-42851 Get ODATA connection details New Feature CELLSJAVA-43047 Adding tooltip text to cell for export in HTML New Feature CELLSJAVA-42988 Performance issue with calculateFormula() Enhancement CELLSJAVA-43018 Export print area range to HTML without implicitly changing some state of the same workbook Enhancement CELLSJAVA-43041 Cells.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 19.9.
Key Summary Category CELLSANDROID-92 Support Product.Family license New Feature CELLSJAVA-42949 Does Aspose.Cells support ECDSA and RSA algorithms New Feature CELLSJAVA-42979 Get total page count before converting to pdf/image New Feature CELLSJAVA-42967 Insert SVG file into the worksheet New Feature CELLSJAVA-42969 Support Java 12 in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 19.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 19.6.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42914 Large conditional formats cause OOM exception Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42916 Data format issue after Workbook.save() Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42930 Excel95 load failure Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42927 Saved file opens slow in Excel after deleting columns Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42857 Wrong value displayed for shapes in the exported PDF Bug CELLSJAVA-42890 The image is opaque and not transparent after conversion - Excel to HTML rendering Bug CELLSJAVA-42893 Chart is missing in Excel to HTML rendering Bug CELLSJAVA-42899 Excel to HTML problem Bug CELLSJAVA-42903 Excel to HTML rendering issue on CentOS Bug CELLSJAVA-42882 Could not extract data from an MS Excel 95 XLS file Bug CELLSJAVA-42887 Calculation difference between MS Excel and Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 19.4.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42838 Disabling auto show task pane property. New Feature CELLSJAVA-42853 Performance issue while converting XLSX to HTML Enhancement CELLSANDROID-88 Image lost during workbook to PDF conversion Bug CELLSJAVA-42852 The label on both of the axis aren&amp;rsquo;t shown Bug CELLSJAVA-42856 Excel to HTML problem Bug CELLSJAVA-42872 Picture of the Sheet, the right and bottom lines are missing Bug CELLSJAVA-42873 The preconditioned Sheet has several cell backgrounds and text missing and is hidden.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 19.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-android-via-java-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Android via Java 19.3.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-41026 Support Excel 95/5.0 (XLS files) New Feature CELLSJAVA-42827 Insert row with InsertOptions similar to MS Excel New Feature CELLSJAVA-42845 Keep separators for empty rows when exporting an XLS file to CSV New Feature CELLSJAVA-42778 Exception &amp;ldquo;style textRotation must be between 0 and 180&amp;rdquo; while loading the XLSM Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42712 Enhance JavaDocs for Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>