<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.12.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-4520 Add support for &amp;ldquo;Clear&amp;rdquo; operation for project&amp;rsquo;s OleObjects collection Enhancement TASKSNET-4497 Refactor API for CalendarExceptions Enhancement TASKSNET-4444 Add an API for getting a count of consumed bytes \ credits when Metered license is used Enhancement TASKSNET-3896 Add API for saving more than 1 page to MemoryStream Enhancement TASKSNET-3895 Implement writing of displayed time units for assignment&amp;rsquo;s Duration* extended attributes Enhancement TASKSNET-3854 Enhance reading of dates in evaluation mode Enhancement TASKSNET-4506 Fix missing embedded OLE image in resaved project Bug TASKSNET-4499 Fix incorrect TimephasedData.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.11.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-4453 Add support for reading \ writing of cost timephased data for resource assignments. Enhancement TASKSJAVA-1197 Milestone set to TRUE after recalculate Bug TASKSNET-4438 Fix TasksException &amp;ldquo;TaskEntity.Start is DateTime.MinValue&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; when project is recalculated Bug TASKSNET-4414 Fix saving of task&amp;rsquo;s WBS code to Project Server \ Project Online Bug TASKSNET-4412 Fix &amp;ldquo;Key already exists&amp;rdquo; exception when saving and reading large file to\from ProjectServer Bug TASKSNET-4411 Fix concurrency issues when accessing Project Server Bug TASKSNET-4286 Fix reading \ writing of Task.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.10.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-4285 Implement a check that file is encrypted New Feature TASKSNET-4311 Improve resource deletion execution time Enhancement TASKSNET-4365 Add and ability to assign cost to the Resource Assignment in manual calculation mode Enhancement TASKSNET-4435 Disable recalculation of Tsk.Cost and Tsk.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.8.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-4209 Fix default columns for Task sheet in XLSX export Enhancement TASKSNET-4153 Fix &amp;ldquo;IsMilestone&amp;rdquo; flag is not reset when the duration of a task is changed to non zero value and vice versa Enhancement TASKSNET-4223 Fix InvalidCastException while converting of MPP to graphic formats Bug TASKSJAVA-1159 On saving a project the InvalidOperationException exception has been thrown Bug TASKSJAVA-1157 Milestone property wrong when writing task Bug TASKSNET-4210 Fix exception on the loading of MPP file Bug TASKSNET-4206 Fix reading of time-phased data in the case when assignment&amp;rsquo; start of finish is a non-working day Bug TASKSNET-4196 Fix inability to set assignment&amp;rsquo;s OutlineCode lookup values in a file saved by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.7.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-3988 Add support of reading of shared resource assignments New Feature TASKSNET-3981 Add support of GridlineType.MiddleTierColumn Enhancement TASKSNET-3346 Fix invalid calculation of task&amp;rsquo;s name indent when ShowProjectSummaryTask = true Enhancement TASKSNET-2237 Provide a descriptive error message when saving not supported Task property.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.6.
Major Features In this release, we are presenting improvements related to interaction with Project Online and Project Server.
You can now create or update an existing project in your Project Online account using ProjectServerManager class:
ProjectServerCredentials credentials = new ProjectServerCredentials(&amp;#34;https://xxxxxx.sharepoint.com&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;yyyyy@xxxxxxx.onmicrosoft.com&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;password&amp;#34;); Project project = new Project(&amp;#34;sample.mpp&amp;#34;); ProjectServerManager manager = new ProjectServerManager(credentials); manager.createNewProject(project); You can now create, read, and update projects in on-premise Project Server (2016 or 2019) using ProjectServerManager class:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.4.
Major Features The release Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.4supports the long-awaited feature of saving into MPP format without preloading of MPP template file. The next scenario is valid now:
Project p = new Project(); // there is no more need to load MPP template to save it into MPP // add tasks, resources, etc. ... p.save(&amp;#34;project.mpp&amp;#34;, SaveFileFormat.MPP); // !</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.2.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-3669 Fix System.ArgumentException: &amp;lsquo;Cannot set calendar with Uid &amp;lsquo;0&amp;rsquo; as a base calendar for calendar with Uid &amp;lsquo;0&amp;rsquo; &amp;rsquo; when opening non published project Bug TASKSNET-3668 Fix projects conversion to graphical formats Bug TASKSNET-3662 Fix KeyNotFoundException format during save online project to MPP and load again Bug TASKSNET-3659 Fix unrecognized GUID format during save online project to MPP Bug TASKSNET-3641 Fix calculation of cost for assignment&amp;rsquo;s resource rates Bug TASKSNET-3630 Fix NullReferenceException when the specific file is saved to XML format Bug TASKSNET-3606 Fix reading of large responses from API of Project Server Project Online Bug TASKSNET-3530 Fix rendering of newly added task Bug TASKSJAVA-1073 Resource GUID is not being saved correctly in MPP Bug TASKSJAVA-1026 Resaving to .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-tasks-for-java-20-1-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 20.1.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSJAVA-1024 ArgumentException: FontFamily ‘Segoe UI’ not found error after updating Aspose.Tasks version Bug TASKSJAVA-999 ArgumentException on saving MPP as PDF on Linux Bug TASKSJAVA-1020 The Conholdate Total license issue Bug</description></item></channel></rss>