<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for .Net 21.12.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10397 Fix resource calendars are missing in file saved by Aspose.Tasks Bug TASKSNET-4701 Fix incorrect Primavera percentage complete value Bug TASKSNET-2851 Fix incorrect updating of project work completed up to the specified date Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were deleted: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for .Net 21.11.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10377 System.OverflowException: TimeSpan overflowed because the duration is too long Bug TASKSNET-10369 Fix Exception on loading the P6 XML file Bug TASKSNET-3611 Fix formula parsing exceptions when opening the specific file Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for .Net 21.10.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10378 Fix calculation of formula results when operand is #ERROR value Enhancement TASKSNET-10376 Fix &amp;ldquo;Value was either too large or too small for a Decimal.&amp;rdquo; exception when get pages count Bug TASKSNET-10368 Fix reading of values of Actual Work&amp;rsquo;s Timephased Data Bug TASKSNET-10361 Fix &amp;ldquo;File reading error.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for .Net 21.9.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-4609 Implement feature &amp;ldquo;Fit to X pages tall and Y pages wide&amp;rdquo; New Feature TASKSNET-10333 Add support for scaling with given scale factor New Feature TASKSNET-10344 Fix &amp;lsquo;The start time should be not greater than the finish one&amp;rsquo; exception when creating project from Primavera .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for .Net 21.8.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10327 Implement reading of AutoFilters with multiple values Enhancement TASKSNET-10307 Fix &amp;ldquo;The given key &amp;lsquo;188744169&amp;rsquo; was not present in the dictionary.&amp;rdquo; exception when open MPP document Bug TASKSNET-10306 Fix &amp;ldquo;The given key &amp;lsquo;1680&amp;rsquo; was not present in the dictionary.&amp;rdquo; exception when open document Bug TASKSNET-10303 Fix StackOverflowException when creating a Project from Primavera XML Bug TASKSNET-10286 Fix Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for .Net 21.7.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10279 Fix wrong Timephased Data for the material resource in MPP Bug TASKSNET-3629 Fix disappearing of a task after an active view change Bug TASKSNET-10275 Fix Invalid Tsk.Id when blank line is inserted Bug TASKSNET-10278 Fix tasks are not shown in MS Project when opening result of &amp;ldquo;CopyTo&amp;rdquo; method Bug TASKSNET-10276 Fix task lines are shown incorrectly when blank line is inserted for MPP 2003 and 2008 Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public methods and properties were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for .Net 21.6.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-4903 Add ExecutingWebRequest event for interactions with API of ProjectOnline \ ProjectServer. Enhancement TASKSNET-4696 Add support of &amp;lsquo;Display OLE as Icon&amp;rsquo; property Enhancement TASKSNET-4908 Fix resaving of the specific MPP file throws ArgumentOutOfRangeException Bug TASKSNET-4907 Fix resaving of the specific MPP file throws &amp;lsquo;Project writing exception&amp;rsquo; Bug TASKSNET-4904 Fix OLE object frame remains even after removing ole object Bug TASKSNET-4876 Fix incorrect timephased data for assignment with zero work.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for .Net 21.5.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-4832 Add an API to specify View object to render when saving project to PDF, HTML and Image formats New Feature TASKSNET-4807 Add support for rendering Left\Top\Inside\Bottom text labels for task bars in Gantt chart Enhancement TASKSNET-4851 Fix exception when trying to get Project using ProjectServerManager Bug TASKSNET-4758 Fix non-detailed general error message when trying to retrieve nonexistent project from Project Online Bug TASKSNET-4836 Fix ArgumentException while reading XML without license Bug TASKSNET-4828 Problem with .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for .Net 21.4.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-4788 Add support for SaveOptions.TaskFilter and SaveOptions.TasksComparer options when project is saved to CSV or XLSX formats Enhancement TASKSNET-4769 Remove an ability to set Tsk.Id when using CalculationMode.Manual and CalculationMode.Automatic Enhancement TASKSNET-4793 Fix exported value of &amp;ldquo;Outline Code *&amp;rdquo; attributes when project is saved to non-MPP formats.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.3.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-4702 Add a feature to set the document name while printing New Feature TASKSNET-4705 Add writing of existing values of enterprise extended attributes Enhancement TASKSNET-4715 Fix broken page range printing Bug TASKSNET-4704 Fix missing column lines while printing to PDF Bug TASKSNET-4703 Fix printing of extra columns lines when printing to PDF Bug TASKSNET-4700 Fix wrong Resource Usage when exporting MPP - Microsoft Project 365 Bug TASKSNET-4699 Task names disappearing when saving MPP file Bug TASKSNET-4673 Fix disappearing of task names after MPP resave Bug TASKSNET-4721 Fix incorrect timephased data shown when .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.2.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-4642 Add support for user-defined page size when saving project to graphical format Enhancement TASKSNET-4636 Improve rendering of Gantt view page legend to use &amp;ldquo;adaptive&amp;rdquo; items layout Enhancement TASKSNET-4635 Add handling of &amp;ldquo;AADSTS53003: Access has been blocked by Conditional Access policies.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-tasks-for-net-21-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for .NET 21.1.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-4597 Add support for &amp;lsquo;Task Summary Name&amp;rsquo; field. Enhancement TASKSNET-4631 Fix incorrect position of not fit task labels when rendering Gantt chart view Bug TASKSNET-4628 Fix incorrect error message shown when trying to read a list of projects from empty Project Online account Bug TASKSNET-4599 Fix application of bar styles with non-default names when rendering Gantt chart view Bug TASKSNET-4588 Fix exception when trying to add a new task in XER project Bug TASKSNET-4601 Fix duplicated resources when reading XER of P6XML file Bug Pay attention, if you use Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>