<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.12.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-49680 Support converting Excel to SQL Scripts. New Feature CELLSNET-49717 Support converting Excel to xml data New Feature CELLSNET-49853 Support importing xml data New Feature CELLSNET-48190 Update priorities when adding new format condition Enhancement CELLSNET-49758 Sorting with DataSorter affects table formatting Enhancement CELLSNET-49828 FormatConditionCollection.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.11.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-48141 Support XLookup formula/function New Feature CELLSNET-49614 Support saving images with workbook.Save() method. New Feature CELLSNET-49651 Support saving as json file. New Feature CELLSNET-48499 Retrieve formatted cell values against certain cells Enhancement CELLSNET-49523 Clear defined names when clearing worksheets. Enhancement CELLSNET-48646 StackOverflow exception while Excel to PDF Conversion Performance CELLSNET-49378 Issue with Excel to HTML conversion performance and empty cells Performance CELLSNET-49453 Improve performance while converting Excel to HTML Performance CELLSNET-48095 3D, the shape of the cloud changed Bug CELLSNET-49544 Bug of saving external NamedRange which references to range of multiple sheets Bug CELLSNET-49588 Single type data saved differently than the original value Bug CELLSNET-49667 The result of ColorScale conditional formatting is incorrect Bug CELLSNET-49043 Position of drawn line is not correct in image Bug CELLSNET-49068 Wrong PDF generated from Excel file Bug CELLSNET-49179 Axis title reference is unexpectedly removed Bug CELLSNET-49294 The axis of some charts are different from those in excel files Bug CELLSNET-49495 Formula rendering overlap Bug CELLSNET-49542 The horizontal axis of the chart disappears Bug CELLSNETCORE-148 Pie chart not rendering correctly Bug CELLSNET-49193 GridDesktop not working properly Bug CELLSNET-49642 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.10.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-49192 Issue with retrieving Ranges (RefersTo) with an offset function New Feature CELLSNET-49132 Open files with HTML table inside as XLS files New Feature CELLSNET-49173 Support Range.CurrentRegion Property New Feature CELLSNET-49015 Update hyperlink(Sheet1!A1) when changing the name of the worksheet. Enhancement CELLSNET-49021 Conditional formatting of ods is lost in MS Excel if type is &amp;ldquo;Contains Text&amp;rdquo; Enhancement CELLSNET-49280 Support autofill range with fill type Enhancement CELLSNET-49413 Remove invisible shapes when?</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.9.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-48134 Support rendering Box &amp;amp; Whisker Excel 2016 Chart to image New Feature CELLSNET-48683 Delete pivot table while perserving data Enhancement CELLSNET-48624 Support named range of whole row/column for .ods files Enhancement CELLSNET-49052 Support setting Transparency of picture for xlsx files. Enhancement CELLSNETCORE-233 Enhancement for changing threaded comment&amp;rsquo;s author Enhancement CELLSNET-49011 Speed up cells iterator access for render for GridDesktop Performance CELLSNET-48915 Out Of Memory Exception when rendering worksheet to image Performance CELLSNET-47663 Excel document is not converted to html Performance CELLSNET-48506 Improve performance for writing .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.8.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-48470 Support scaling of worksheet pages when exporting files to HTML New Feature CELLSNET-41286 Support XML Maps New Feature CELLSNET-45255 Support for Apple&amp;rsquo;s .numbers? file format New Feature CELLSNET-47737 Support for reading latest Apples .numbers file format New Feature CELLSNET-48205 Add Auto-fill (pattern) handle MS Excel feature for numbers, text or Dates, etc.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.7.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-48165 Option to apply conditional formatting on PivotTable New Feature CELLSNET-48188 Create conditional formatting on PivotTable via PivotField in row area, column area and data area. New Feature CELLSNET-40399 GridWeb - runFormulas similar to GridDesktop feature New Feature CELLSNET-44065 GridWeb rows and columns grouping feature New Feature CELLSNET-48196 Preserve text formatting while converting from HTML to XLSX Enhancement CELLSNET-48213 Rich text styles are lost while converting from HTML to XLSX Enhancement CELLSNET-45625 Formula cell value is not updated automatically after changing related cell value Enhancement CELLSNET-45640 Show cell comment (rich text) exactly as in MS Excel Enhancement CELLSNET-47233 Support pattern display for GridWeb Enhancement CELLSNET-40295 Workbook rendering to Printer Enhancement CELLSNET-46642 Support WCAG 2.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.6.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-48104 Get value of SlicerCacheItem in the collection Slicer.SlicerCache.SlicerCacheItems New Feature CELLSNET-48121 Support custom style of Slicer in Xlsb New Feature CELLSNET-48053 Set user defined formulas as array-formulas and at the same time provide values as calculated results for those formulas New Feature CELLSNET-43532 Ability to embedded the fonts with ANSI encoding New Feature CELLSNET-48042 Retrieved formatted cell values are wrong in Excel worksheet Enhancement CELLSNET-48078 Deep copy of Workbook after calculation with CreateCalcChain setting Enhancement CELLSNET-48079 How to check if a worksheet is empty Enhancement CELLSNET-48135 Issue with protected workbook (with a password) generated by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.5.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-47964 Support binding Slicer Report with pivot table and pivot chart New Feature CELLSNET-48003 Support importing free html with svg image New Feature CELLSNET-47988 Reffering to spill range with # New Feature CELLSNET-47996 Support moving existing column in GridWeb New Feature CELLSNET-48002 Support exporting all worksheets to .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.4.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-47891 Support to get displaystyle with cache enable New Feature CELLSNET-47922 Render data with cell coordinates in Excel to HTML conversion Enhancement CELLSNET-47924 Implement Crypto with BouncyCastle&amp;rsquo;s API Enhancement CELLSNET-47951 Support XML maps by XSD Enhancement CELLSNET-47206 Grouping data with Horizontal Smart Markers and nested data source Enhancement CELLSNET-47888 Appropriate SmartMarkers required to achieve the desired output Enhancement CELLSNET-47918 Collapsible rows along with Smart markers Enhancement CELLSNET-47953 Support adding .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.3.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-47857 Clears all merge areas on the sheet New Feature CELLSNET-47892 Digitally sign Microsoft Signature Line in Excel spreadsheet Enhancement CELLSNET-47905 Implement Digest Algorithm by BouncyCastel’s API Enhancement CELLSNET-47838 Native chart color palette is not preserved Enhancement CELLSNET-47877 Workbook.Settings.RemovePersonalInformation is not effective Enhancement CELLSNET-47879 The generated file is corrupted when saving xls file with embedded word6.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.2.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-42427 Support percentage of column display format for PivotTable New Feature CELLSNET-44288 Using LightCells API with XLSB files New Feature CELLSNET-47817 Update data source when changing Waterfall chart to Column chart. Enhancement CELLSNETCORE-99 Support updating display icon for embedded jpg, zip, msg object.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-cells-for-net-21-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 21.1.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-47376 Release Aspose.Cells for .NET 5.0 New Feature CELLSNET-40624 How to switch row/column data series using aspose New Feature CELLSNET-42195 Convert control from xlsm to xls New Feature CELLSNET-47806 Gets the data source range of the chart. New Feature CELLSNET-47756 SmartArt shapes are not rendered fine in Excel to PDF conversion Bug CELLSNET-47391 Shapes are not positioned correctly in excel to pdf conversions Bug CELLSNET-47766 Arrow graph is incomplete Bug CELLSNET-47653 Diagram blocks are shifted when converting to HTML Bug CELLSNET-47720 Invalid CSS and HTML markup when converting XLSX to HTML Bug CELLSNET-47746 Unencoded quotes in values of HTML attributes Bug CELLSNET-47792 Images are over lapping the text when importing html to excel Bug CELLSNET-47797 Bad link when XLSM file is rendered in HTML Bug CELLSNET-47807 Invalid HTML markup with nested A elements Bug CELLSNET-47778 IRR Calculation evaluates to #NUM Bug CELLSNET-47814 GridDesktop scrollbars are not hidden Bug CELLSNET-47744 Radial plots are squished when exported to pdf Bug CELLSNET-47786 XErrorBar not displaying in the chart Bug CELLSNET-47787 XErrorBars disappears when copying chart from one workbook to another Bug CELLSNET-43907 WordArt is not rendered while converting XLS to PDF Bug CELLSNET-47780 Problem setting two ranges as data source of chart Bug CELLSNET-47781 Wrap Text not working for ODS files Bug CELLSNETCORE-94 Pivot Table Group By day is increasing when refreshed Bug CELLSNETCORE-77 Error while converting XLSX to PDF on Azure Bug CELLSNETCORE-90 Issues while inserting attachments in excel worksheet Bug CELLSNETCORE-93 H1 tag not rendered without additional tags like underline, italic or bold Bug CELLSNETCORE-97 Calling RemoveExternalLinks() raises exception Bug CELLSNET-47719 Failed to save xlsb to xlsx Exception CELLSNET-47784 Exception while importing HTML document with IStreamProvider Exception CELLSNET-47801 CalculateData on pivot table throws exception Exception CELLSNET-47809 Cell.</description></item></channel></rss>