<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.12.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36710 Support to set QR version while generating barcode image Feature BARCODENET-36279 Improve speed and quality of the new 1D recognition algorithm Enhancement BARCODENET-36733 Setting License in Aspose.BarCode throws exception Bug BARCODENET-36726 Aspose.BarCode throw exception when used in multi threading Bug BARCODENET-36690 Unable to recognize DatabarStacked barcode with big white space Bug BARCODENET-36689 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.11.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36687 Support to define settings &amp;ldquo;segments per row&amp;rdquo; Feature BARCODENET-36706 Make consistent .NET Compact and Full Framework API Enhancement BARCODENET-36705 Aspose.BarCode is detecting barcode from image that has no barcode on it Bug BARCODENET-36702 Recognized incorrect Supplement barcode Bug BARCODENET-36700 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.10 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.10.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36667 Remove Obsolete public API Enhancement BARCODENET-36694 Incorrect text in picture for DatabarStacked Bug BARCODENET-36681 Recognition result isn&amp;rsquo;t correct for DatabarExpandedStacked Bug BARCODENET-36679 Unable to recognize DatabarStacked barcode Bug BARCODENET-36688 Index was out of range exception when try to recognize barcode from PDF Bug BARCODENET-36701 Incorrect DatabarLimited generation/recognition Bug BARCODEJAVA-383 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.9.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36678 Generates incorrect barcode for DatabarLimited Bug BARCODENET-36676 Generation DatabarExpandedStacked isn&amp;rsquo;t correct Bug BARCODENET-36666 Can&amp;rsquo;t recognize Pharmacode with AllSupportedTypes Bug BARCODENET-36661 Can&amp;rsquo;t recognize second barcode (DatabarExpandedStacked) Bug BARCODENET-36660 Aspose.Barcodes 17.06 BarCodeReader does not recognize a barcode types on .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.8.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36635 Ability generate a postal barcode with specified height Enhancement BARCODENET-36651 Incorrect recognition type for GS1Code128 barcode Bug BARCODENET-36650 Generates incorrect barcode for EAN14 Bug BARCODENET-36641 Unable to get the supplement code text from EAN13 coded barcode Bug BARCODENET-36639 Incorrect recognition type for DatabarTruncated barcode Bug BARCODENET-36638 Can&amp;rsquo;t recognize DatabarStacked code Bug BARCODENET-36637 Incorrect recognition type for Code93Standard barcode Bug BARCODENET-36632 yDimension property doesn&amp;rsquo;t work Bug BARCODENET-36629 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.7.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36539 Ability to find out/get the minimum height and width required for barcode image Feature BARCODEJAVA-229 Printing the barcode on a label printer, the barcode lines are not smooth Feature BARCODENET-36622 Throws exception when using GetOnlyBarCodeImage with small size Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes This section lists public API changes that were introduced in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.6
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36540 Ability to identify the type of Code128 coded barcode type while recognition Feature BARCODENET-36572 Ability to add a picture or image inside a barcode in place of codetext Feature BARCODENET-36571 Unable to get the supplement code text from EAN13 coded barcode Bug BARCODENET-36559 Incorrect recognition UPCA of EAN13 code Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes This section lists public API changes that were introduced in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.5 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-5-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 17.5 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36531 Add support for generate DataMatrix with Text encodation scheme Feature BARCODENET-36525 Add support for generate DataMatrix with C40 encodation scheme Feature BARCODEJAVA-249 Ability to generate the QR barcode with a logo/image/picture inside it Feature BARCODENET-36557 Unable to get the supplement code text from EAN13 coded barcode (supplement barcode is bit blurred) Bug BARCODENET-36547 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.4
Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36510 Improve GS1 parsing and validation Enhancement BARCODENET-36513 Improve targets detection for QR Enhancement BARCODENET-36514 BarCodeBuilder allows to generate incorrect GS1 barcodes Bug BARCODENET-36493 Unable to recognize the barcode using Aspose.BarCode Bug BARCODENET-36491 Barcode generator accepts incorrect GS1 codetext Bug BARCODENET-36474 BarCodeBuilder.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.03 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-03-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-03-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.03
Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36497 Add checksum feature for Codabar Feature BARCODENET-36488 Barcode is not giving correct output Enhancement BARCODENET-36479 BarCode is not giving correct output when GS1DataMatrix barcode is supplied to read Enhancement BARCODENET-36475 Unable to recognize barcode of type Code39Standard from a TIFF image Enhancement BARCODENET-36386 Fake recognition of DutchKIX in MaxBarCodes mode Enhancement BARCODENET-36487 Generation GS1DataMatrix isn&amp;rsquo;t correct Enhancement</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.02 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-02-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-02-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 17.02 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODEJAVA-171 Improve Aspose.Barcode for Java for reducing memory consumption Enhancement BARCODENET-36457 Unable to successfully read code39standard barcode from PNG image Enhancement BARCODENET-36456 QR code is not recognizing Enhancement BARCODENET-36450 Restore code128 uses a bitmap spliting in the histogram algorithm Enhancement Usage examples BARCODENET-36457 Unable to successfully read code39standard barcode from PNG image</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for Java 17.01 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-01-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-barcode-for-java-17-01-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for Java has been updated to version 17.01 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Java.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36423 Reading problem of DataMatrix barcode Enhancement BARCODENET-36405 Creating barcode of 300 dpi is producing wider barcode image Enhancement BARCODENET-36352 Implement algorithm for recognizing 3D-distorted MicroQr Enhancement BARCODENET-34234 BarCodeBuilder does not generate CodeText for characters: &amp;ldquo;~B&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;~C&amp;rdquo; properly for PDF417; Enhancement BARCODENET-33257 Cannot recognize DataMatrix when image has been scanned at 200DPI Enhancement Usage examples BARCODENET-36352 Implement algorithm for recognizing 3D-distorted MicroQr</description></item></channel></rss>