<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.HTML for Java 19.9.
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the September release of Aspose.HTML for Java. This release mainly focuses on improving the quality and performance of &amp;ldquo;Font Selection and Fallback&amp;rdquo; algorithms used in the API.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 19.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-8-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.HTML for Java 19.8.
Major Features As regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are pleased to announce the second release of Aspose.HTML for Java. In this release, we have made some internal bug fixes.
Improvement and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLJAVA-251 PDFNEWNET_38773 test works too long and some times hangs Bug HTMLJAVA-267 Chaotic behavior of EPUB rendering Bug HTMLJAVA-271 The Dictionary class don&amp;rsquo;t use IEquatable interface Bug HTMLJAVA-280 Conversion hangs or throws an exception Bug HTMLJAVA-286 The font is not applied in HTML rendering Bug HTMLJAVA-285 Can&amp;rsquo;t load HTML file using stream while using path loads without any problems Bug HTMLJAVA-292 Different results for rendering the same document Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.HTML for Java 19.7
Major Features As regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are pleased to announce the second release of Aspose.HTML for Java. In this release, we have made some internal bug fixes.
Improvement and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLJAVA-241 HTML to image difference Bug HTMLJAVA-259 Performance regression, the conversion is too long Bug HTMLJAVA-277 Load HTML with dead links hang Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 19.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.HTML for Java 19.6
Major Features As regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are pleased to announce the second release of Aspose.HTML for Java. In this release, we have made some internal bug fixes.
Improvement and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLJAVA-255 No suitable constructor found for ImageDevice Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 19.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-5-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for Java 19.5.0 Release Notes Major Features As regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are pleased to announce the second release of Aspose.HTML for Java. In this release, we have made some internal bug fixes.
Improvement and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLJAVA-192 Number each page with Aspose.HTML Bug HTMLJAVA-206 The text in PDF output isn&amp;rsquo;t properly formatted Bug HTMLJAVA-220 Slow HTML to PDF rendering Bug HTMLJAVA-236 Conversion hangs Bug HTMLJAVA-240 An exception raises while processing HTML file Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for Java 19.4.0 Release Notes Major Features As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the April release of Aspose.HTML for Java. In this release, we have focused on improving quality and performance of &amp;ldquo;Font Selection and Fallback&amp;rdquo; algorithm.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 19.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-html-for-java-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for Java 19.3.0 Release Notes Major Features As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the March release of Aspose.HTML for Java. The main improvement of this release is that we created a truly parallel mechanism of processing the documents that significantly improved performance of processing the documents with lot of resources. Moreover, from this release you do not need to wait until document will be loaded, parsed and all scripts will be executed which of course is blocking the main thread of your application.</description></item></channel></rss>