<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.12.
Major Features Add more options for GeoJson format. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-1387 Add InMemory driver for InMemoryLayer Feature GISNET-1387 Add AutoIds Option for GeoJson Feature GISNET-1387 Add ArrayAsString Option for GeoJson Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.10.
Major Features Generate Map. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-1371 Generate Map Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:
T:Aspose.Gis.GeoTools.MapBuilder.MapGeneratorOptions M:Aspose.Gis.GeoTools.MapBuilder.MapGeneratorOptions.#ctor P:Aspose.Gis.GeoTools.MapBuilder.MapGeneratorOptions.Width P:Aspose.Gis.GeoTools.MapBuilder.MapGeneratorOptions.Height M:Aspose.Gis.GeoTools.MapBuilder.MapGeneratorOptions.Clone T:Aspose.Gis.GeoTools.MapBuilder.MapLayersGenerator M:Aspose.Gis.GeoTools.MapBuilder.MapLayersGenerator.#ctor M:Aspose.Gis.GeoTools.MapBuilder.MapLayersGenerator.ProduceMap(Aspose.Gis.GeoTools.MapBuilder.MapGeneratorOptions) Following members have been removed:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.9.
Major Features Support Esri Json Driver. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-997 Read data from EsriJson Feature GISNET-1370 Write data to EsriJson Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:
P:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.8.
Major Features Support GDAL Integration. This driver is similar to the database driver. The user specifies the path where GDAL is installed. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-1353 Support GDAL Integration Feature GISNET-1351 Add band mask option in Crop Feature GISNET-1367 Add N Pointed Star in Generator Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.7.
Major Features Rework Generator Algorithms Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-1337 Rework Generator Algorithms Enhancement GISNET-1357 Generate Points in Regular Mode Feature GISNET-1358 Generate Lines in Regular Mode Feature GISNET-1359 Generate Polygons in Regular Mode Feature GISNET-1350 Converting and rendering of GPX files does not work Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.6.
Major Features Add New Geometry Processing Operations (SimplifySegments, DeleteNearPoints and etc.) Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-1345 Add New Geometry Processing Operations Feature GISNET-1347 Add Option SimplifySegments for Vector Layer Feature GISNET-1346 Add Option DeleteNearPoints for Vector Layer Feature GISNET-1343 Add Option CreateMidpoints for Vector Layer Feature GISNET-1344 Add Option CloseLinearRing for Vector Layer Feature GISNET-1335 Add Symbolizer Parameter in Geometry.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.5.
Major Features Export geometry to image Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-1326 Visualize geometry Feature GISNET-1333 Add Option WritePolygonsAsLines For All Drivers Enhancement GISNET-1331 Add missed AsText methods in IGeometry Enhancement Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.3.
Major Features Support Net 6.0 Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-1329 Support Net 6.0 Enhancement GISNET-1317 Fix Aspose.Foundation Exception Bug GISNET-1328 Fix Could not load file or assembly Aspose.Foundation Bug GISNET-1302 Can&amp;rsquo;t use license in Blazor Server app Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-gis-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 22.1.
Major Features fixed couple bugs in GeoJSON and SHP formats Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-1287 Handle the &amp;ldquo;id&amp;rdquo; field of a GeoJSON Feature Bug GISNET-1249 Can&amp;rsquo;t read 3d point from SHP file Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item></channel></rss>