<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 16.12.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-16-12-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-16-12-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 16.12.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50438 Can&amp;rsquo;t group shapes second time in a Visio Drawing page. Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50445 The VBA is not being initialized due to the editing of a VSDM drawing on Linux Systems. Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50434 VSD to PDF export - the extra white space is generated on the left side of the drawing.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 16.11.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-16-11-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-16-11-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 16.11.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50356 Performance issue with exporting a VSD to PDF. Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50419 Can&amp;rsquo;t set the width and height of an ActiveX button in the VSDM. Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50257 VSD to VDX conversion, an invalid resultant file is created. Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50335 VSDX to PDF export - Solid lines of shapes are converted to dashed lines.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 16.10.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-16-10-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-16-10-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 16.10.0
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50422 Output VSDX - Can&amp;rsquo;t modify the text of shape on changing Data1, Data2, and Data3 properties. Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50423 Output PDF - Can&amp;rsquo;t modify the text of shape on changing Data1, Data2, and Data3 properties. Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50424 Output PDF - Can&amp;rsquo;t modify the text of shape from another shape text.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.8.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50347 Add support of inserting ActiveX controls in the Visio Page. New Feature DIAGRAMJAVA-50360 Add support to set color checkbox of the layer. New Feature DIAGRAMJAVA-50348 Can&amp;rsquo;t copy a Visio page in the VSDM. Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50357 The incomplete rendering of an OLE chart when converting a VSDX to PDF.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.7.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50342 Add support of detecting the file format using a stream object. New Feature DIAGRAMJAVA-50015 VSD to PDF conversion - the red cross image appears instead of the shape. Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50341 The endpoints of connectors are not connected when saving in the VDX format.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.6.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50327 Add support to import the macro enabled Drawing (.VSDM). New Feature DIAGRAMJAVA-50328 Add support to import the macro enabled template (.VSTM). New Feature DIAGRAMJAVA-50329 Add support to import the macro enabled stencil (.VSSM). New Feature DIAGRAMJAVA-50326 Diagram exception occurred while loading a VSDX file.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.5.0
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50219 Can&amp;rsquo;t retrieve connections from VSS stencil file. Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50324 The position of text items is changed on converting a VSDX to SVG. Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list for any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJava-50060 VSD to PDF conversion, incorrect layout of the text in shapes. Bug DIAGRAMJava-50070 VSD to PDF conversion, the text of shapes is not bold. Bug DIAGRAMJava-50071 VSD to PDF conversion, the text of shapes is not italicized. Bug DIAGRAMJava-50072 VSD to PDF conversion, the font-size of the text in shapes is changed.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJava-50306 Add support of detecting the Visio diagram type. New Feature DIAGRAMJava-50311 Prevent export of the hidden Visio pages in the PDF. New Feature DIAGRAMJava-50312 Prevent export of the hidden Visio pages in the HTML. New Feature DIAGRAMJava-50313 Prevent export of the hidden Visio pages in the PNG. New Feature DIAGRAMJava-50314 Prevent export of the hidden Visio pages in the JPEG.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJava-50128 Can&amp;rsquo;t get 2D shape ids when called Shape.GluedShapes method. Enhancement DIAGRAMJava-50143 VSD to VDX conversion - the text items are missing or misplaced. Bug DIAGRAMJava-50259 VSD to VDX export - the display text of the Bitmap shapes is missing. Bug DIAGRAMJava-50304 VDX to VSDX export generates a corrupt output file.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Diagram for Java.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJava-50281 ImageSaveOptions.setImageBrightness does not work Enhancement DIAGRAMJava-50293 VSD to SVG export does not preserve shape ids Enhancement DIAGRAMJava-50294 Output format VDX - Can&amp;rsquo;t connect two Visio shapes Enhancement DIAGRAMJava-50300 Can&amp;rsquo;t change page orientation by setting PrintPageOrientation property Enhancement DIAGRAMJava-50067 VSD to PDF conversion, the word &amp;ldquo;text&amp;rdquo; is added in the shape&amp;rsquo;s text Bug DIAGRAMJava-50124 Incorrect setting of connector text location Bug DIAGRAMJava-50288 Warning of the missing attribute when opened the resultant VDX diagram Bug DIAGRAMJava-50289 Shape.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 6.0.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-0-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-diagram-for-java-6-0-0-release-notes/</guid><description>The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Diagram for Java.
Other Improvements and Changes New Feature DIAGRAMJAVA-50216) -Add support of loading VSSX format file in the Diagram class DIAGRAMJAVA-50225)-Add support to determine two shapes are glued or connected Bugs DIAGRAMJAVA-50196) -VSD to VDX conversion, curve dynamic connectors turn into stright DIAGRAMJAVA-50229)-Geometry of the connector shapes is incorrect DIAGRAMJAVA-50230) -Geometry of the connector shapes is incorrect DIAGRAMJAVA-50241) -VSDX to EMF conversion - a zero bytes EMF file is generated DIAGRAMJAVA-50242) -Copying a Visio diagram page operation does not preserve style of the shapes DIAGRAMJAVA-50243) -Output format PDF Copying Shape from the VSDX - an empty PDF is generated DIAGRAMJAVA-50244) -Output format EMF Copying Shape from the VSDX - an empty EMF is generated DIAGRAMJAVA-50245) -Output format JPEG Copying Shape from the VSDX - an empty JPEG is generated DIAGRAMJAVA-50246) -Output format PNG Copying Shape from the VSDX - an empty PNG is generated DIAGRAMJAVA-50247) -Output format GIF Copying Shape from the VSDX - an empty GIF is generated DIAGRAMJAVA-50248) -Output format SVG Copying Shape from the VSDX - an empty SVG is generated DIAGRAMJAVA-50249) -Output format TIFF Copying Shape from the VSDX - an error occurred DIAGRAMJAVA-50250) -Output format XPS Copying Shape from the VSDX - an empty XPS is generated DIAGRAMJAVA-50251) -Output format XAML Copying Shape from the VSDX - an empty XAML is generated DIAGRAMJAVA-50252) -Output format HTML Copying Shape from the VSDX - an empty HTML is generated DIAGRAMJAVA-50253) -Copying a Visio diagram page does not preserve shapes completely DIAGRAMJAVA-50254) -Copying a Visio diagram page does not preserve shapes completely DIAGRAMJAVA-50255) -VSDX to TIFF conversion - an error occurred while saving into the Tiff format DIAGRAMJAVA-50258) -VDX to VDX export, shape&amp;rsquo;s text is not bold DIAGRAMJAVA-50260) -VSD to VDX export, missing shadow of the shapes DIAGRAMJAVA-50268) -Source VSD - ConnectCollection class returns additional connect and incorrect shape ids DIAGRAMJAVA-50270) -Shape.</description></item></channel></rss>