<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 21.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 21.12
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-40230 Zimbra calendars backup to PST Feature EMAILNET-40267 Ability to skip exceptions while enumerating messages from OLM file Feature EMAILNET-40481 Contacts API is being deprecated. Migrate to People API to retain programmatic access to Google Contacts Enhancement EMAILJAVA-35001 MailQueryBuilder.From.OrderBy throws KeyNotFoundException Bug EMAILJAVA-34971 Adding message to PST infinite loop Bug New Features OLM file traversal API The traversal API allows extracting all items as far as possible, without throwing out exceptions, even if some data of the original file is corrupted.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 21.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 21.11
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-40470 Load MapiMessage from file without changing values for fields Enhancement EMAILNET-40462 GraphMessageInfo.getSize() method always returns -1 Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34964 Contacts API is being deprecated. Migrate to People API to retain programmatic access to Google Contacts. Enhancement EMAILNET-40412 &amp;ldquo;Reply All&amp;rdquo; in Outlook doesn&amp;rsquo;t work after adding EML to PST Bug EMAILNET-40425 Event appears only in one day, but should repeat every year Bug EMAILNET-40454 NullReferenceException when trying to send a email via strato.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 21.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 21.10
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-40441 Add support for saving appointments to MSG format Feature EMAILNET-40449 MSG file body with emoji is changed after Load/Save Enhancement EMAILNET-40440 Optional attendees are not displayed in the mht header output Enhancement EMAILNET-40446 Incorrect ClientSubmitTime when converting EML to MSG Bug EMAILNET-40455 EmlLoadOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 21.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 21.9
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILJAVA-34947 PST to MSG: Some messages extraction slow Enhancement EMAILNET-40303 Custom flags generated with ImapMessageFlag.Keyword function contains extra flags Bug EMAILNET-40397 Loading MAPI message from stream throws InvalidOperationException Bug EMAILNET-40411 Inline attachments in EML file are not showing Bug EMAILNET-40383 Ignoring SMTP address check throws SmtpException Bug EMAILNET-40220 Loading Appointment throws AsposeArgumentOutOfRangeException Bug EMAILJAVA-34941 Calendar event does not repeat with UNTIL property in recurrence rule Bug EMAILJAVA-34943 deepClone losing the multipart/alternative Bug EMAILJAVA-34945 Date from EML is not shown properly Bug EMAILNET-40347 ImapMessageInfo.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 21.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 21.8
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-40359 When converting MSG to PDF atendees are missing Bug EMAILJAVA-34924 NullPointerException is thrown when adding MSG files to PST file Bug EMAILNET-40348 ImapClient contructor throws ArgumentNullException for single file app Bug EMAILNET-40265 SmtpClient.Send throws OperationCancelledException Bug EMAILNET-40333 Filter messages containing attachments through ImapClient Feature EMAILNET-40205 PST traversal API implementation Feature EMAILJAVA-34929 Add com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 21.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 21.7
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-40250 Using CRAM-MD5 authentification with ImapClient Feature EMAILNET-40256 Newest API for SmtpClient Feature EMAILNET-40326 Encoding options for MboxrdStorageReader class Enhancement EMAILNET-40310 Appointment Sub Type is missing when load modified occurrences(embedded message) Enhancement EMAILNET-40328 HTML default header formating options Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34916 Spacing in headers lost after converting to PDF Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34898 Reading Importance and Class properties from ICS file Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34868 AsposeException is thrown when importing a calendar event into a PST file Enhancement EMAILNET-40306 Embedded message does not get updated Bug EMAILNET-40309 Body text is missing in exported MHT Bug EMAILJAVA-34919 Regressions: NullPointerException when calling MailMessage Bug EMAILNET-40293 EML attachments lost while saving mails to Office 365 folder Bug EMAILNET-40291 Messages differ after saving and loading Tnef Bug EMAILNET-40279 MapiCalendar cannot get some event&amp;rsquo;s recurrence period Bug EMAILNET-40304 Unable to investigate all contacts Bug EMAILJAVA-34915 MapiCalendar recurrence pattern process is stuck Bug EMAILNET-40316 Exception on removing the signature from email Bug EMAILJAVA-34912 Exception on removing the signature from email Bug EMAILJAVA-34926 Headers are squashed when converting EML to HTML Bug New Features Added CRAM-MD5 authentication The ability to authenticate using the CRAM-MD5 mechanism in IMAP, POP3, and SMTP clients has been added.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 21.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 21.6
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILJAVA-34890 Email text missing content Bug EMAILNET-40252 AppointmentStateFlags missing when saving calendar to MSG file Bug EMAILNET-40228 Enumerating MAPI messages throws InvalidOperationException Bug EMAILJAVA-34891 Possible regression: mailMessage.getHtmlBodyText(true) returns different content Bug EMAILNET-40271 Exception was thrown when getting multiple EWS clients at the same time Bug EMAILNET-40269 Connection with Exchange 2013 SP1 fails using EWSClient Enhancement EMAILNET-40215 ImapClient.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 21.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 21.5
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-40231 &amp;ldquo;header doesn&amp;rsquo;t correspond to vCard format&amp;rdquo; exception when loading VCF file Bug EMAILNET-40232 Retrieving appointments from Google calendar throws exceptions Bug EMAILNET-40223 Attachments appear after saving EML message Bug EMAILNET-40209 Message header is incorrect if the subject ends with backslash Bug EMAILNET-40225 Task attached to the meeting request gets converted to embedded message Bug EMAILNET-40218 Unable to retrieve content from EML file Bug EMAILNET-40210 &amp;ldquo;Object reference not set to an instance of an object.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 21.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 21.4
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-40147 Exception on changing the category of email using Graph Client Bug EMAILNET-40199 Duplicate attachments after saving EML message Bug EMAILNET-40169 Alternate view is deleted when message is sent or saved, when message also contains linked resources Bug EMAILNET-40187 Recurrence issue when writing ICS to PST Bug EMAILNET-40174 Enumerating MAPI messages throws NullReferenceException Bug EMAILNET-40123 &amp;ldquo;Operation has been canceled&amp;rdquo; when sending SMTP mail Bug EMAILNET-40186 Support Adding custom flags does not work anymore Bug EMAILNET-40182 Search for RFC message id in PST file doesn&amp;rsquo;t work Bug EMAILNET-40038 ImapClient.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 21.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 21.3
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-40117 Issue while sending Bulk emails Enhancement EMAILNET-40157 Implementation of FindPeople Method to find all persona objects that match a specified query string Enhancement EMAILNET-40143 Add LinkedResource.ContentDisposition property Enhancement EMAILNET-40139 PersonalStorageQueryBuilder.Text property doesn&amp;rsquo;t work for pst Enhancement EMAILNET-40131 Improve error handling for ImapClient.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 21.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 21.2
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-40088 Improve Imap.ThreadGrCommand to get threads list for GMail Enhancement EMAILNET-40084 Error loading folder by its EntryIdString Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34783 Getting modified date OPFMessageCopyModDate for message in OLM Enhancement EMAILNET-40107 Body Text of MSG File looks different from how it looks in Outlook Bug EMAILNET-40115 The ContentID cannot contain a ‘&amp;lt;’ or ‘&amp;gt;’ character Bug EMAILNET-39978 Aspose email gives an error on using Bug EMAILJAVA-34779 Outlook Task / TaskRequest in EML format shows MessageClass as &amp;ldquo;IPM.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 21.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-email-for-java-21-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 21.1
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-40027 Email client authentication customization Feature EMAILJAVA-34778 EWSClient, support for CalendarView Feature EMAILJAVA-34777 Support to validate SMTP connection credentials Feature EMAILNET-40010 MSG extraction from PST: Object reference not set to an instance of an object Bug EMAILNET-40030 Use TFM file naming conventions to simplify project files Bug EMAILNET-40019 Special characters breaking in appointments Bug EMAILNET-40023 Pictures inserted (AttachMethod = 6) in MapiJournal cannot be displayed normally Bug EMAILNET-40020 The body (BodyContentType.</description></item></channel></rss>