<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 17.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-java-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.Tasks for Java 17.11 version.
Major Features Option to set Image quality while saving project data to JPEG Improvements Key Summary Category TASKSNET-2140 Add option to set image quality when saving as JPEG New Feature TASKSNET-2147 Enum GanttBarFillPattern should have value 11 corresponding to fill pattern in MSP 2016 Enhancement TASKSNET-2109 Exception raised while loading the mpp file Bug TASKSNET-2105 ArgumentOutOfRangeException exception if 24 Hours Calendar is set Bug TASKSNET-2104 Program hangs while setting Tsk.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 17.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-java-17-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-java-17-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 17.8.
Major Features Support for JDK 1.6 has been discontinued. Improvements Key Summary Category TASKSJAVA-418 Migrate from JDK 1.6 to JDK 7 Enhancement TASKSNET-1818 Add support for text style information Enhancement TASKSNET-1965 TasksReadingException while using MspDbSettings Enhancement TASKSNET-2046 Add support of RateScale reading/writing for MSP 2013+ New Feature TASKSNET-1963 Finish date is incorrect for zero duration task using Recalculate Bug TASKSNET-1941 Empty project with one task has incorrectly filled ActualStart, ActualFinish dates Bug TASKSNET-1916 HtmlSaveOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 17.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-java-17-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-java-17-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.Tasks for Java 17.5.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category TASKSJAVA-326 Tasks with custom timephased data has Percent Complete &amp;gt; 100% and MSP in XML format cannot be imported. Bug TASKSNET-1917 Formulas get corrupted after file save Bug TASKSNET-1905 Loading a MPP file using Aspose.Tasks throw exception An item with the same key has already been added Bug TASKSNET-1899 Recalculation of project sets percent complete to zero on milestone tasks Bug TASKSNET-1867 Saving Project raises TaskWritingException Bug TASKSNET-1814 Erroneous calendar entry added in XML while converting MSP 2016 MPP Bug TASKSNET-1740 Out of Memory error while saving MPP to PNG Bug TASKSJAVA-266 Task duration shown wrong in MSP 2016 as compared to MSP 2010 Bug TASKSNET-1705 Saving MPP file hangs and never returns Bug TASKSJAVA-246 Timephased data entries are repeated for AssignmentActualWork in the XML file Bug TASKSJAVA-245 Timephased data not copied while saving project as MPP Bug TASKSJAVA-236 Wrong Actual Start, % Complete and Actual duration calculated while saving MPP Bug TASKSJAVA-215 The value of actual start of parent node set to NA while loading and saving the project Bug TASKSNET-1565 TimephasedData written to MPP File shows wrong Work Values for the Last two days Bug TASKSJAVA-332 Project.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 17.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-java-17-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-java-17-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Tasks for Java 17.3.0 version.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category TASKSNET-1796 Inconsistent behavior of %Complete in MPP Bug TASKSNET-1792 WBS Codes written to MPP file are not same as Microsoft Project Bug TASKSNET-1769 ArgumentOutOfRangeException is raised when setting task Finish date Bug TASKSJAVA-247 Empty timephased data added in XML for type AssignmentWork Bug TASKSNET-1684 Formula values not calculated properly for DateAdd, DateDiff and DatePart Bug TASKSJAVA-243 Project reading exception while loading MPP file Bug TASKSNET-1577 Project Reading Exception while Loading MPP file Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Methods and Properties added Description com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 17.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-java-17-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-java-17-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Tasks for Java API enables application developers to write code for manipulating Microsoft Project documents without it being installed on the systems. It provides support for Microsoft Project (MPP/XML) as well as Primavera File Formats. Project data can be exported to a number of formats including PDF, PNG, BMP and others.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category TASKSNET-1729 Improve public API to simplifyworking with Custom Fields.</description></item></channel></rss>