<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 19.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-note-for-java-19-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-note-for-java-19-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Note for Java 19.11.
Major Features Extended public API to work with AttachedFile, Image and Title elements. Optimized saving using HTML format Features and Improvements Key Summary Category NOTEJAVA-594 Extract alternative text (title and description) set in the attached file Feature NOTEJAVA-593 Extract alternative text (title and description) set in the image Feature NOTENET-2550 Unable to set a prefix for nested HTML resources Enhancement NOTEJAVA-250 Information can&amp;rsquo;t be read from OneNote online file format Bug NOTENET-2786 &amp;ldquo;Img&amp;rdquo; tag required instead of &amp;ldquo;Image&amp;rdquo; while converting .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-note-for-java-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-note-for-java-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Note for Java 19.9.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category NOTENET-2675 FileCorruptedException when opening OneNote files Bug NOTENET-2710 Investigate bug: Outline incorrect measurement Bug NOTENET-2714 Unknown Binary Data Marker in OneNote Online File Format. Bug NOTEJAVA-585 Fonts subsystem setting does not have any effect on the result Bug NOTEJAVA-641 Exception raised while converting .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-note-for-java-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-note-for-java-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Note for Java 19.7.
Major Features Improved support for processing files in OneNote Online format Features and Improvements Key Summary Category NOTEJAVA-247 The index was out of range. Exception raised while loading note file Bug NOTEJAVA-248 Unknown binary data compression exception raised while loading Note file Bug NOTEJAVA-317 Note document has negative zoom so there is extra space on the left and incorrect number of pages (after saving as pdf) Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes The following public properties are marked as obsolete: Description com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 19.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-note-for-java-19-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-note-for-java-19-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Note for Java 19.5.
Major Features Switching to use of FIPS compliant version of BouncyCastle Features and Improvements Key Summary Category NOTEJAVA-581 Is Aspose.Note FIPS 186-4 compliant New Feature NOTEJAVA-425 FIPs Compliant version of Bouncy Castle usage in APIs New Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes No Change</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-note-for-java-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-note-for-java-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Note for Java 19.4.
Major Features Management of Locale used by Aspose.Note Features and Improvements Key Summary Category NOTEJAVA-465 Provision to set locales New Feature NOTEJAVA-584 Missing styles when export fonts set to NoExport Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 19.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-note-for-java-19-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-note-for-java-19-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Note for Java 19.1.
Major Features Support for JDK 11 Features and Improvements Key Summary Category NOTEJAVA-519 Aspose.Note compatibility with JDK 11 New Feature NOTEJAVA-562 JpegQuality does not make any effect on output document Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes None</description></item></channel></rss>