<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Java 19.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Java 19.12.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-43047 Adding tooltip text to cell for export in HTML New Feature CELLSJAVA-43002 Unexpected CPU hot spot in ZipOutputStream when opening XSLB Enhancement CELLSJAVA-43008 Option to disable loading OLE object while opening a workbook Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42793 Fontwork SmartArt object lost during ODS to XLSX conversion Bug CELLSJAVA-43020 Radial graph distorted after calling Chart.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Java 19.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Java 19.11.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-43032 Add Validation.addArea (CellArea cellArea, boolean skipArea) or Validation.setAreas() method/overloads to the APIs New Feature CELLSJAVA-42851 Get ODATA connection details New Feature CELLSJAVA-43018 Export print area range to HTML without implicitly changing some state of the same workbook Enhancement CELLSJAVA-43041 Cells.importCSV throws exception &amp;ldquo;string value cannot exceed 255 characters&amp;rdquo; Enhancement CELLSJAVA-43043 Cells.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Java 19.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Java 19.10.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-41814 Support custom data sorting for the specific area in PivotTable report New Feature CELLSJAVA-42988 Performance issue with calculateFormula() Enhancement CELLSJAVA-41103 Pivot table data coloring and formatting is not rendering properly Bug CELLSJAVA-43007 PDF is not generated as expected Bug CELLSJAVA-43025 Cell.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Java 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Java 19.9.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42990 Hidden rows are displayed while converting Excel file to HTML when AutoFilter exists Bug CELLSJAVA-42997 CalculateFormula() fails with large formula strings Bug CELLSJAVA-43000 CalculateFormula() corrupts the Excel file Bug CELLSJAVA-42987 Formatting issues while converting Excel file to PDF Bug CELLSJAVA-42986 Text overlapping after converting Chinese XLSX file to PDF Bug CELLSJAVA-43012 Workbook.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Java 19.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Java 19.8.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42949 Support for ECDSA and RSA algorithms New Feature CELLSJAVA-42979 Get total page count before converting to PDF/image New Feature CELLSJAVA-42967 Insert SVG file into the worksheet New Feature CELLSJAVA-42969 Support Java 12 in Aspose.Cells for Java Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42977 High CPU and memory consumption during Excel to PDF conversion Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42902 Waterfall chart style is not copied properly while copying workbook Bug CELLSJAVA-42944 Error converting XLSX to HTML Bug CELLSJAVA-42966 Refreshing PivotTable and PivotCharts corrupts the Excel file Bug CELLSJAVA-42975 Differences in HTML conversion Bug CELLSJAVA-42971 #N/A is shown in the rendered PDF Bug CELLSJAVA-42970 Unwanted extended borderline in Excel to PDF rendering Bug CELLSJAVA-42976 Image position mismatch when rendering Excel file to PDF Bug CELLSJAVA-42961 Table properties not copied properly while copying data using copyColumns Bug CELLSJAVA-42980 Transparent image changes to opaque during picture copy Bug CELLSJAVA-42959 Exception &amp;ldquo;Shape to image Error&amp;rdquo; when rendering an XLSX file to PDF Exception Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Java 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Java 19.7.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42861 Could not get the alternative text of the shape in ODS file format Bug CELLSJAVA-42929 Graph title changes on XLSX to PDF conversion Bug CELLSJAVA-42933 Graphics color changes while converting Excel file to PDF Bug CELLSJAVA-42946 Wrong rendering of Stacked bar chart with series to PDF Bug CELLSJAVA-42942 Pages printed on worksheet level and not on workbook level Bug CELLSJAVA-42952 Wrong indentation from the top of the cell in some words Bug CELLSJAVA-42902 Waterfall chart style is not copied properly while copying workbook Bug CELLSJAVA-42939 Warning raised by Excel if we only call Workbook.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Java 19.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Java 19.6.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42914 Large conditional formats cause OOM exception Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42916 Data format issue after Workbook.save() Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42930 Excel95 load failure Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42927 The saved file opens slow in Excel after deleting columns Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42932 Conditional formatting error with Style.getDisplayStyle method Bug CELLSJAVA-42928 Some lines are not reflected in XLSX to PDF conversion Bug CELLSJAVA-42904 Header image seemingly corrupts the file Bug CELLSJAVA-42907 Filter lost after saving the workbook Bug CELLSJAVA-42915 Filters are changed after adding a sheet to the workbook Bug CELLSJAVA-42918 Converted file&amp;rsquo;s chart flattened (XLS to XLSX conversion)  Bug CELLSJAVA-42938 Loading XLSX file halts the application Bug CELLSJAVA-42859 CellsException for loading Name from ODS file Exception CELLSJAVA-42908 Exception while calling Name.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Java 19.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Java 19.5.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42857 Wrong value displayed for shapes in the exported PDF Bug CELLSJAVA-42890 The image is opaque and not transparent after conversion - Excel to HTML rendering Bug CELLSJAVA-42893 The chart is missing in Excel to HTML rendering Bug CELLSJAVA-42899 Excel to HTML problem Bug CELLSJAVA-42903 Excel to HTML rendering issue on CentOS Bug CELLSJAVA-42882 Could not extract data from an MS Excel 95 XLS file Bug CELLSJAVA-42887 Calculation difference between MS Excel and Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Java 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Java 19.4.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42838 Disabling auto show task pane property. New Feature CELLSJAVA-42853 Performance issue while converting XLSX to HTML Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42852 The label on both of the axis is not shown Bug CELLSJAVA-42856 Excel to HTML conversion issue Bug CELLSJAVA-42872 Picture of the Sheet, the right and bottom lines are missing Bug CELLSJAVA-42873 The preconditioned Sheet has several cell backgrounds and text missing and is hidden.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Java 19.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Java 19.3.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42845 Keep separators for empty rows when exporting an XLS file to CSV New Feature CELLSJAVA-42846 Text extraction results differ from the original Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42844 The text is not properly aligned in PDF output Bug CELLSJAVA-42834 Text color (black) is changed to red in HTML rendering Bug CELLSJAVA-42839 Scatter chart is not rendered in Excel to PDF conversion Bug CELLSJAVA-42840 Horizontal axis labels are not rendered fine for charts in Excel to PDF rendering Bug CELLSJAVA-42842 2D Bubble chart is not rendered in Excel to PDF conversion Bug CELLSJAVA-42833 Issue while embedding same PDF file in multiple sheets in a workbook Bug CELLSJAVA-42836 Workbook.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Java 19.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Java 19.2.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-42827 Insert row with InsertOptions similar to MS Excel New Feature CELLSJAVA-42712 Enhance JavaDocs for Aspose.Cells for Java Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42823 Using FontUnderlineType.WORDS throws exception Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42826 Data with conditional formatting omitted while XLSX to HTML conversion Bug CELLSJAVA-42815 Adding complex reference to defined name results in corrupt MS Excel workbook Bug CELLSJAVA-42822 Cell.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for Java 19.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-java-19-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for Java 19.1.
Key Summary Category CELLSJAVA-41026 Support Excel 95/5.0 (XLS files) New Feature CELLSJAVA-42778 Exception &amp;ldquo;style textRotation must be between 0 and 180&amp;rdquo; while loading the XLSM Enhancement CELLSJAVA-42290 Mdashes and ndashes inserted into TextBoxes in charts are not rendered properly in chart&amp;rsquo;s PDF Bug CELLSJAVA-42750 Unable to retrieve page fields&amp;rsquo; items in the PivotTable report Bug CELLSJAVA-42783 Problem with strikethrough text in generated HTML file format Bug CELLSJAVA-42784 Data in some cells (e.</description></item></channel></rss>