<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.12.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-51061 new feature for draw line with multiple points for java Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-51055 Unexpected output sent to STDOUT when loading Visio file Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-51064 Wrong shape appearance with new jar file (aspose-diagram-22.11) Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-51049 How to get connection point of a line on a shape Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-51044 .getDisplayText() to decode html entities (Aspose.Diagram Java 22.10, .vsd files) Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-51046 Shape&amp;rsquo;s name is sometimes different than names in Visio Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.10.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-51028 setTopPage not working Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-51035 wk: Geoms property for some Sheet shapes is not resolved correctly Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-51030 .getName() is sometimes different than names in Visio (Aspose.Diagram Java 22.9, .vsd files) Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-51033 .getText() is sometimes different than shape.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.9.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-51022 WK: Shape distorted after saving to PNG Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-51015 wk: Shape name in a language other then English Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-51020 wk: Name for the Sheet shape with a layer is not resolved correctly Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.8.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50226 Add support of auto size the Visio page Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-51004 Shape not properly displayed - crossed rectangle displayed instead Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-51005 When the text contains line breaks, recalculating the width of the text is incorrect Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-51006 Resizing the lateral line shape [Cont.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.7.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50991 wk: Inherit fill problem Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50446 The output image is pixelated on converting a VSD to HTML Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50996 Shape not properly displayed - crossed rectangle displayed instead Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.6.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50963 WK: Shape distorted after saving to PNG Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50967 Resizing the lateral line shape [Cont.] Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50972 API is not parsing the file correctly Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50974 Issue in adding new connection point Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.5.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50923 wk: Field Displayed values Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50924 wk: get Alignment values Enhancement DIAGRAMJAVA-50934 Investigate the feasibility to parallel processing of VSDX files Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50936 Wrong Values for Shape.getName(), Shape.getNameU() Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50941 Converting vsd to vsdx ,The converted vsdx file cannot be opened in Visio.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.4.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50898 wk: PinPos not defined Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.3.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50883 Determine missing fonts and font substitution information from the API Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.2.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50164 VST to HTML conversion, background picture of the whole diagram is missing Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-diagram-for-java-22-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Diagram for Java 22.1.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category DIAGRAMJAVA-50857 wk: EndArrow value is Bug DIAGRAMJAVA-50861 Investigate Cve-2021-42574 Vulnerability Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following is a list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>