<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.12 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.12.
All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODENET-37024 Not able to read dotted barcodes from TIFF images Bug BARCODEJAVA-623 An exception occurs for tests related to XML serialization Bug BARCODEJAVA-625 Unable to Read Complete BarCode Text Bug BARCODEJAVA-624 Restore compatibility of serialized XML code between .NET and Java Bug Usage examples: BARCODENET-37024 - Not able to read dotted barcodes from TIFF images</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.11 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.11
New Features Bring enums names into line with Java naming conventions Add new barcode subsets to DecodeType Not able to detect the barcode Improve the recognition of a 3D-distorted and rotated 2D-barcodes Improve the recognition of a 3D-distorted QR code Add minor fixes to BarCodeReader GS1 DataBar Expanded Stacked barcode did not pass GS1 Canda barcode verification All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODEJAVA-607 Bring enums names into line with Java naming conventions New Feature BARCODENET-37019 Add new barcode subsets to DecodeType New Feature BARCODENET-36945 Not able to detect the barcode New Feature BARCODENET-34367 Improve the recognition of a 3D-distorted and rotated 2D-barcodes New Feature BARCODENET-36389 Improve the recognition of a 3D-distorted QR code New Feature BARCODENET-37020 Add minor fixes to BarCodeReader New Feature BARCODEJAVA-555 GS1 DataBar Expanded Stacked barcode did not pass GS1 Canda barcode verification New Feature BARCODENET-37010 Barcode CODE39 reading problem Bug BARCODENET-37000 Barcode Detection does not constrain to the defined region.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.10.1 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-10-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-10-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.10.1.
All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODENET-37001 Using the same instance of BarcodeReader throws exceptions Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.10 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.10
New Features New architecture of barcodes recognition filters Implemented UpcaGs1Code128Coupon for new barcode generation API Implementation to read all barcodes from TIFF images  Deprecated BarCodeBuilder All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36713 Investigate new architecture of barcodes recognition filters.  New Feature BARCODENET-36940 Implement UpcaGs1Code128Coupon for new barcode generation API  New Feature BARCODENET-36973 Not able to read all barcodes from TIFF images  New Feature BARCODENET-36962 Not able to read the barcode  New Feature BARCODENET-37013 Deprecate BarCodeBuilder New Feature BARCODENET-36795 DPI settings works incorrectly with rotation  Bug BARCODENET-36956 Databars are generated incorrectly from GS1 string  Bug BARCODENET-37008 ITF14 barcode fails GS1 Verification Process  Bug BARCODENET-34141 Can&amp;rsquo;t recognize DataMatrix codes from the JPG image  Bug BARCODENET-36957 Text part isn&amp;rsquo;t correct in ENA13 when change resolution  Bug BARCODENET-36786 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.8 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.8.
New Features List or chart of prerequisites required to generate a successful BarCode image of any BarCode type Added UpcaGs1DatabarCoupon for new BarCode generation API Interpolation AutoSize mode added in new renderers MaxiCode renderer added in new BarCode generation API DotCode renderer added in new BarCode generation API All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36872 List or chart of prerequisites required to generate a successful BarCode image of any BarCode type New Feature BARCODENET-36941 Added UpcaGs1DatabarCoupon for new BarCode generation API New Feature BARCODENET-36930 Interpolation AutoSize mode added in new renderers New Feature BARCODENET-36923 MaxiCode renderer added in new BarCode generation API New Feature BARCODENET-36922 DotCode renderer added in new BarCode generation API New Feature BARCODENET-36942 Code16K BarCode drawn without above and below borders Bug BARCODENET-36952 GS1 Datamatrix BarCode wrapping issue in case of CodeLocation.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.7 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Barcode for JasperReports 18.7.
New Features New Barcode generation API with improved functionality All Changes Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36791 Prepare Preview version of new Barcode Generation API New Feature BARCODENET-36215 Unable to Read the DatabarExpandedStacked barcode from a PNG image Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.6 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>
Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports has been updated to version 18.6 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports.
Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36906 Metered license works incorrectly with some BarCodeReader constructors Bug BARCODEJAVA-8 Unable to Read the QR barcode successfully from a TIFF image Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.5 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-5-release-notes/</guid><description>
Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports has been updated to version 18.5 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports.
Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36759 Remove obsolete properties from BarCodeReader Enhancement BARCODENET-36856 GetCustomSizeBarCodeImage method is discarding check digit when generate EAN13 coded barcode Bug BARCODENET-36869 Fake recognition of MicrE13B barcodes Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.4 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-4-release-notes/</guid><description>
Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports has been updated to version 18.4 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports.
Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36843 ThrowExceptionWhenCodeTextIncorrect works incorrectly with some EncodeTypes Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.3 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-3-release-notes/</guid><description>
Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports has been updated to version 18.3 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports.
Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36820 License text is wrong just &amp;ldquo;Aspose&amp;rdquo; instead of &amp;ldquo;Aspose.BarCode Evaluation Version&amp;rdquo; Bug BARCODEJAVA-427 Barcode builder throws an exception while initialize Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.2 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-2-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports has been updated to version 18.2 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports.
Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36748 Unable to recognize the barcodes from images Bug BARCODENET-36784 License text is drawn incorrectly Bug BARCODENET-36776 Wrong codetext alignment on systems with custom scaling Bug BARCODENET-36727 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports 18.1 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/jasperreports/release-notes/2018/aspose-barcode-for-jasperreports-18-1-release-notes/</guid><description>
Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports has been updated to version 18.1 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.BarCode for JasperReports.
Key Summary Category BARCODENET-36647 Add support to save barcode in SVG Feature BARCODENET-34191 Add support to save barcode in any Vector image format Feature BARCODENET-36783 Support to generate and recognize EPC QR coded barcode Feature BARCODENET-36753 Improved drawing text when font is specified Enhancement BARCODENET-36755 Mark old useless BarCodeReader API as obsolete Enhancement BARCODENET-36760 Barcode is rendered without text Bug BARCODENET-36750 Incorrectly saving a picture to a file Bug BARCODENET-36738 Property CodeLocation works incorrectly Bug</description></item></channel></rss>