<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.12.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1298 LookupPaths does not work when export GLB with input textures saved in zip file. Task THREEDNET-1293 Allow encode and decode directional/spot light Improvement THREEDNET-1294 Cylinder defined UV but no data Bug fixing THREEDNET-1295 Convert from DXF to GLTF/GLB Bug fixing THREEDNET-1296 FBX model couldn&amp;rsquo;t convert properly Bug fixing THREEDNET-1299 Added properties not accessible in other tools Bug fixing THREEDNET-1306 Cylinder with radius top =0 will generate incorrect model Bug fixing API changes There&amp;rsquo;re no API changes in this version.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1283 Implement binary maya import support New Feature THREEDNET-1276 Improve mesh quality when converting 3D-PDF to GLTF Improvement THREEDNET-1280 Restore the support of .NET 4.5 Improvement THREEDNET-1289 Materials lost when export to USDZ with only diffuse colors Bug fix API changes Added members to class aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.10.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1241 Allow import Maya ASCII file New Feature API changes Added new type aspose.threed.Utilities.RotationOrder This is used in aspose.threed.utilities.TransformBuilder
Added new methods to class aspose.threed.utilities.TransformBuilder: # &amp;lt;summary&amp;gt; # Append rotation with specified order def rotate_degree(rot : Type[Vector3], order : Type[RotationOrder]) def rotate_radian(rot : Type[Vector3], order : Type[RotationOrder]) rotate_degree and rotate_radian allows compose a rotation matrix in specified order.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.9.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1232 Add internal temporary file system support for FBX importer Improvement THREEDNET-1111 GLTF export is not good Bug fixing THREEDNET-1215 When importing an OBJ file, one node can only read one material? Bug fixing THREEDNET-1216 Converting GLB to GLB loses textures Bug fixing THREEDNET-1225 Analyze issues found in App server - 2022 September Bug fixing THREEDNET-1227 Unsupported options in ASE files: MATERIAL_SOFTEN/PHYSIQUE/MATERIAL_SHINE Bug fixing THREEDNET-1228 Exception when importing JT files: An item with the same key has already been added Bug fixing THREEDNET-1230 STL files with quad face is not supported.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.8.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1175 Fix release package file issues. Task THREEDNET-1183 Fix default installation directory of MSI package Task THREEDNET-1176 Node with geometry translation cannot be handled properly in USDZ exporter. Bug fixing THREEDNET-1179 Aspose.3D 22.5: Exception when trying to load Vrml file Bug fixing THREEDNET-1181 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for .NET 22.7.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1166 Switch to USDZ as HTML5&amp;rsquo;s default internal format New Feature THREEDPYTHON-17 Mesh&amp;rsquo;s control points are not exposed in python version Improvement API changes The old A3DW format was used as HTML5&amp;rsquo;s internal format, now it&amp;rsquo;s obsoleted and replaced by the USDZ, which can provide more features and extensibility.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.6.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1152 Allow save 3D scene without specify the file format New Feature THREEDNET-1157 SdfValueBlock is not supported in USDZ import Improvement THREEDNET-1156 GLF Exception: Failed to import glTF, byteOffset is not defined in accessor Bug fix THREEDNET-1154 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/python-net/release-notes/2022/aspose-3d-for-python-net-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Python via .NET 22.5.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1149 Mesh triangulate does not support VertexElementUserData with mapping mode Polygon/PolygonVertex New Feature THREEDNET-1148 Add support of VertexElementUserData in TriMesh New Feature THREEDNET-1138 Allow export VertexElementUserData to glTF New Feature THREEDNET-1119 Support for GLTF Custom Vertex Attributes New Feature This is the first release of Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>