<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 18.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for Java 18.11.0 Release Notes Major Features As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are pleased to announce November release of Aspose.HTML for Java. We have made some internal changes and bug fixes as in the table below:
Improvement and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLJAVA-168 java.awt.HeadlessException Bug HTMLJAVA-177 ClassCastException in com.aspose.html.HTMLInputElement Bug HTMLJAVA-178 ArgumentOutOfRangeException in com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 18.10.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-10-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-10-2-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for Java 18.10.2 Release Notes Major Features The headless mode bug was fixed.
Improvement and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLJAVA-168 java.awt.HeadlessException Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 18.10.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-10-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-10-1-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for Java 18.10.1 Release Notes Major Features Saving intermediate debug images to disk bug was fixed.
Improvement and Changes Key Summary Category HTMLJAVA-169 Saving intermediate debug images to disk Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 18.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for Java 18.10.0 Release Notes Major Features As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are pleased to announce October release of Aspose.HTML for Java. We are honored to announce that we have increased numbers of supported platforms and the API supports Mac OS X now. In this release, we have improved rendering into output devices running under Mac OS X platform. Also, we have made some internal changes and bug fixes as in the table below:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 18.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-8-release-notes/</guid><description>Release Notes of Aspose.HTML for Java 18.8 As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are pleased to announce the August release of Aspose.HTML for Java. In this release we have refactored and increased the performance of HTML parsing module up to 40%. Also, we have made some internal bug fixes.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 18.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.HTML for Java 18.6 Release Notes As per regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the June release of Aspose.HTML for Java. In this release, we have improved SVG support and made some internal bug fixes and enhancements related to CSS parsing algorithms and document rendering. Additionally, we have improved the mechanism of the external fonts loading and introduced &amp;lsquo;Text Rendering Options&amp;rsquo; object in order to give user an ability to configure text rendering quality.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML for Java 18.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-html-for-java-18-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.HTML for Java 18.5
Release Notes of Aspose.HTML for Java 18.5 Major Features We are pleased to announce that our series of W3C formats has been extended and now we support Scale-able Vector Graphics (SVG) format. Our API offers the capabilities to manipulate SVG, both as a part of HTML document and single SVGDocument object. This API is fully compatible with the W3C SVG 2 recommendation and previously implemented HTML format, so every manipulation features: loading, saving, editing, navigation or rendering features supported exactly in the same way.</description></item></channel></rss>