<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.12
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-11 Support of Linked Layer Feature PSDNET-131 Support of SoCoResource Feature PSDNET-115 LineBreaks are added to existing LineBreaks if TextLayer is updated with a string Bug PSDNET-157 Saving PSB as PNG freezing Bug PSDNET-250 Exception on loading CMYK PSD file without layers with RLE compression Bug PSDNET-161 Exception on updating text layers Bug PSDNET-222 Resize some PSD files with layer masks works incorrect Bug PSDNET-244 Saving PSD with some Globalization.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.11
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-151 Support of Inner Shadow Layer Effect Feature PSDNET-135 Implement rendering of Fill Layer: Pattern Feature PSDNET-187 Support of Raster Images in AI Format Files Feature PSDNET-225 Get properties of inline formatting of TextLayer Feature PSDNET-214 Incorrect export of PSD to other formats if it contains Layer Effects and Adjustment Layers Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: T:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.10 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.10
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-207 Support of Color Balance Adjustment Layer Feature PSDNET-145 Support of Invert Adjustment Layer Feature PSDNET-139 Implement bicubic Resampler Feature PSDNET-169 Add support of PSD export to PDF with Clipping Mask Feature PSDNET-168 Add support of PSD export to PDF with Adjustment Layers Feature PSDNET-179 Problem Get Layer DropShadowEffect Enhancement PSDNET-203 When text is updated with / (forward slash) characters, file cannot be opened in Photoshop Bug PSDNET-199 PSD file cannot be saved when text layer contains linebreak only Bug PSDNET-185 Extracted wrong Font size Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: T:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.9
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-160 Wrong layer name extracted Feature PSDNET-175 Getting text properties from a different portion of text inside PSD TextLayer Feature PSDNET-190 Support for Add layer group Feature PSDNET-192 Support of Scale Property for Gradient Fill Layer Feature PSDNET-162 Adjusting Brightness Enhancement PSDNET-174 IndexOutOfRangeException on saving PSD image as JPEG Bug PSDNET-180 Updating text layer text throws an exception Bug PSDNET-182 Saving PSD image after RotateFlip operation produces a corrupted file which could not be open Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: M:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.8
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-184 Load JPEG,PNG and other image files to PsdImage from stream Feature PSDNET-134 Implement rendering of Fill Layer: Gradient Feature PSDNET-166 Saving PSD into PDF does not provide selectable text Feature PSDNET-158 Support saving PSB as PDF Feature PSDNET-189 High memory usage on loading of PSD with ReadOnly Mode Enhancement PSDNET-171 After the creation of new TextLayer, PSD file became unreadable for PS Bug PSDNET-156 Exception on loading PSD Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: M:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.7
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-126 Support of Layer Vector Masks processing Feature PSDNET-130 Implement correct Resize method for PSD files Feature PSDNET-165 Add support of export PSD to PDF Feature PSDNET-186 Add support of export AI format (Version 2 and 3) to other formats Feature Public API Changes Added APIs: F:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.6
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-127 Ability to convert PSD file to PSB and vice versa Feature PSDNET-154 Porting of Aspose.Imaging 19.5 sources to Aspose.PSD Enhancement PSDNET-155 Cleanup public API related to Aspose.PSD Enhancement PSDNET-159 Remove property IsLicensed Enhancement PSDNET-102 Conversion PSB to JPG hangs Bug PSDNET-150 Newly added text layer position is shifted on editing in Photoshop Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: T:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.5 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.5
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-133 Add support of Fill layers: Pattern Feature PSDNET-138 Support of PtFlResource Feature PSDNET-129 Implement correct Crop method for PSD files Feature PSDNET-140 Support of VsmsResource Feature PSDNET-121 Visible Layers in Visible SubFolder in Invisible Folder are rendered, but should not Bug PSDNET-119 PSD (RGB mode 16 bit per channel) not properly converted to JPG Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: T:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.4
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-87 Make feature to load JPEG/PNG/etc image files to PsdImage without direct loading(Which is not supported in Aspose.PSD) Feature PSDNET-120 Support of RGB Color mode with 16bits/channel (64 bits per color) Feature PSDNET-108 Support of Layer Vector Masks and Text Layer Custom FlipRotate Feature PSDNET-99 All Asian characters are not rendered properly Bug PSDNET-116 \r\n symbols are interpreted as double line break that is wrong Bug PSDNET-117 If TextLayer is updated with string which contains LineBreaks then PSD File become unreadable Bug PSDNET-118 If TextLayer is updated with string which contains Tabs symbols, processing fails with exception Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: M:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.3 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.3
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-104 Rendering of rotated by TransformMatrix Text Layers Feature PSDNET-96 Implement rendering of Stroke effect with Color Fill for export Feature PSDNET-112 InnerData Transformers corrupts some layers with vector masks Bug PSDNET-113 Updating text layer for PSD image throws error when opened in Photoshop Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: None Removed APIs: None Usage examples: PSDNET-104.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.2 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-psd-for-net-19-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for .NET 19.2
**  Key Summary Category PSDNET-97 Add support of Fill layers: Color fill Feature PSDNET-98 Add support of Fill layers: Gradient fill Feature PSDNET-105 Support of GdFlResource Feature PSDNET-106 Support of VmskResource Feature PSDNET-109 Porting of Actual Aspose.Imaging sources to Aspose.PSD Enhancement PSDNET-92 Add support of partial loading for some methods Enhancement PSDNET-110 PSD performance fell down several times Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: T:Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>