<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 16.12.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-16-12-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-16-12-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38546 List only completed tasks from Exchange server Enhancement EMAILNET-38453 EWS: Retrieve Extended Properties for Items Enhancement EMAILNET-38533 Filter mail messages by date and time when using EWS Enhancement EMAILNET-38550 Filter mail messages by date and time when using Imap Enhancement EMAILNET-38523 EML to MHTML: Output text size is different Bug EMAILJAVA-34207 Regression: EML to MSG doesn&amp;rsquo;t load images in Output Bug EMAILNET-38529 SmtpClient leaking ThreadLocal data Bug EMAILNET-38531 Subject is getting corrupted after changing its encoding Bug EMAILNET-38537 One-Off Distribution List added to PST can&amp;rsquo;t be opened in MS Outlook Bug EMAILJAVA-34212 MSG to VCF doesn&amp;rsquo;t care about the line breaks in Notes Bug EMAILNET-38539 EML to EML garbles message body Bug EMAILNET-38541 When email attachments are saved to disk, the .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 16.11.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-16-11-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-16-11-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-34611 Replace the use of the interpreter classes Enhancement EMAILNET-38510 Provision of Bcc field in ExchangeMessageInfo Enhancement EMAILNET-38497 EML to XPS Layout clipping Bug EMAILNET-38500 MSG file cannot be converted to MailMessage using MailMessageInterpretor Bug EMAILNET-38508 NamedProperties of embedded message lost while embedding message into another message and add to PST Bug EMAILNET-38513 Regression: Error in Occurrence Generation Bug EMAILNET-38514 MailMessage Attachment name turned garbage Bug EMAILNET-38522 Html body is not loaded properly Bug EMAILJAVA-34205 Using java.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 16.10.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-16-10-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-16-10-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38433 Improve GetContacts method to fetch all properties of Contact from Exchange Server Enhancement EMAILNET-38453 EWS: Retrieve Extended Properties for Items Enhancement EMAILNET-38466 Add extra parameters for UID FETCH command Enhancement EMAILNET-38469 Loading and Saving EML back loses email body Bug EMAILNET-38478 Error in recurrence generation Bug EMAILNET-38485 Images are not parsed by MailMessage Bug EMAILNET-38486 HTMLBodyText not retrieved properly from EML Bug EMAILNET-38471 MSG attachment added using MapiMessage can&amp;rsquo;t be opened in MS Outlook Bug EMAILNET-38479 Events timezone information not properly added to PST Bug EMAILNET-38460 Header with the same name removed after resaving the Plain Text email message Bug EMAILNET-38462 PDF attachment corrupted while fetching mail using Pop3Client Bug EMAILJAVA-34189 MSG to EML: Inline image converted to regular attachment Bug EMAILNET-38475 EML-&amp;gt;EML: Subject encoding lost and turned garbled Bug EMAILNET-38477 ImapClient fetches wrong message having PDF and signature info Bug EMAILNET-38480 EML body text is not parsed correctly Bug EMAILNET-38481 Garbage characters in HtmlBodyText Bug EMAILJAVA-34192 Problem with extracted Email Journal Item Bug EMAILJAVA-34196 MSG added to PST can&amp;rsquo;t be opened in MS Outlook Bug EMAILJAVA-34194 Date/Time changed when message converted from .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 6.9.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-9-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-9-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
Major Features Marking Items in-place within a PST EWS: Provision of synching folder own name Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-34970 Marking Items in-place within a PST New Feature EMAILNET-38414 EWS: Provision of synching folder own name etc New Feature EMAILNET-38448 Provision to identify embedded (nested) messages in TNEF messages Enhancement EMAILNET-35239 Implement RTF Extension Algorithm to properly display body of message after converting from eml to msg Enhancement EMAILNET-38446 Convert inline attachments from RTF body to inline images in HTML body at MSG to EML conversion Enhancement EMAILNET-38443 Improve log methods to decrease delay which depends on log operations Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34187 Move all external maven dependencies to local repo Enhancement EMAILNET-35187 Empty message Id retrieved while using ImapClient.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 6.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
Major Features Option to split PST based on time and other criterias Move Folder and Sub-folders to some other folder using ImapClient Features and Improvements EMAILNET-34829 - Option to split PST based on time and other criterias</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 6.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
Major Features Alternative for SecurityOptions.Auto, but without possibility of SecurityOptions.None Encoding detection while loading .vcs files Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-35247 Retain Content disposition and Content-Transfer-Encoding while saving and loading an Email Enhancement EMAILNET-35278 Alternative for SecurityOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 6.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
Major Features Bulk deletion and update of messages in PST Support for Gmail IMAP protocol extensions ImapClient: Delete and change message flags for set of messages Use mail server IP address for connecting the ImapClient and Pop3Client without DNS resolution Option to read X-APPLE-FILENAME for attachments in ICS from IOS Improvement of copy method.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 6.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
Major Features Ability to add event to Secondary Calendar of Office 365 Bind Smtp Client to specific IP on source having multiple IPs Provide Insert method for adding Header at specific location Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-35201 Bind Smtp Client to specific IP on source having multiple IPs New Feature EMAILNET-35192 Saving EML has date with Weekday abbreviation Enhancement EMAILNET-35198 Ability to add event to Secondary Calendar of Office 365 Enhancement EMAILNET-35222 Provide Insert method for adding Header at specific location Enhancement EMAILJAVA-33572 ImapClient: Messages fetched from Office 365 turns special characters into garbage Bug EMAILJAVA-33581 Garbage in Subject with specific encoding and Empty Body (Java) Bug EMAILJAVA-33583 Error while loading EML file Bug EMAILNET-35188 Exchange.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 6.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Java is a class library that enables applications to manipulate popular message formats including Microsoft Outlook messages. It also supports communication protocols such as IMAP, SMTP, POP3, and Microsoft Exchange Server. In addition, the API supports working with PST as well as OST file formats.
Major Features In this Release Sending Calendar invitation Moving messages using IMAP Paging Support in Email clients (IMAP, EWS List Messages List Folders List Appointments) Saving messages as Outlook Template (.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 6.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Features Detecting different file formats. This feature allows to define any supported by Aspose.Email file or stream format. Other features and improvements Support for adding message headers while converting to HTML Auto-detection of html body encoding to correct message conversion into mhtml and html Message signing with detached signature All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-35108 - Feature to detect different file formats Features EMAILNET-35110 - Include Message Headers while converting to HTML Enhancements EMAILNET-35098 - Exception thrown when setting email address with &amp;ldquo;-&amp;rdquo; right before @ Enhancements EMAILNET-35102 - Scanpst reports errors with PST generated using Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 6.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features Support for reading MS Outlook 2013/2016 OST file format.* Support for reading MS Outlook 2013/2016 OST file format.
Now Aspose.Email supports the reading of the OST file format for MS Outlook 2013/2016. You can get folders and messages using the well-known API in work with PST. Other features and improvements
EWS: Paging support for the list of appointments IMAP:Paging support for the list of messages MAPI message: Reading embedded messages from attachments MAPI message:Replacing embedded messages All Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 6.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2016/aspose-email-for-java-6-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>The following is a list of improvements and changes in this release of Aspose.Email.
Improvements and Changes
Enhancements EMAILNET-35055 - Add auto recognition for pipelining mode based on response of &amp;lsquo;capability&amp;rsquo; command .
EMAILNET-34884 - Improve support of asynchronous operations with allowance pipelining for SMTP client
EMAILNET-34853 - PersonalStorageQueryBuilder.Body.Contains NotSupportedException
EMAILNET-34968 - Provision of Creating MapiCalendarTimeZone object from a Standard Timezone
EMAILNET-35047 - Provision of adding MapiAttachment without a Name</description></item></channel></rss>