<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 18.11.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-zip-for-net-18-11-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-zip-for-net-18-11-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 18.11.1.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-232 Add self-extracted archives Enhancement ZIPNET-251 Path traversal vulnerability Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description Aspose.Zip.Saving.SelfExtractorOptions Represents an options for self extracted archive. The following public methods and properties were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 18.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-zip-for-net-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-zip-for-net-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 18.11.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-232 Add self-extracted archives Enhancement ZIPNET-251 Path traversal vulnerability Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description Aspose.Zip.Saving.SelfExtractorOptions Represents an options for self extracted archive. The following public methods and properties were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 18.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-zip-for-net-18-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2018/aspose-zip-for-net-18-9-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.ZIP for .NET API lets you work with a number of techniques for archiving files and folders. It provides several techniques for storing or compressing data that can work with popular applications. The API gives you complete control for making archives and applying protection via user defined passwords. Salient features of the API are as follow.
Compressing and Decompressing Files and Folders Compose an archive from one or multiple files Add files to existing archives Compress directories respecting its structure Decompress files and folders as per the stored structure Delete entries from existing archives Ability to store files to archives without compression Compress files of all sizes by applying parallel mode to utilize several CPU cores Support for Zip64 Archives - 4GB+ zip files with virtually unlimited number of included files Encryption of Archives Encryption of archives using Traditional Encryption Support for AES 128, 192 and 256 for encryption of archives Capability to encrypt complete archive or specific entries with password Ability to encrypt each archive entry with its own password</description></item></channel></rss>