<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 18.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1622 Implement Enhanced Metafile Format Plus Extensions (EMF+) support Feature SLIDESCPP-1623 Improve EMF/WMF format processing Feature SLIDESCPP-1624 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 18.12 features Feature Public API Changes No change</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 18.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1582 Improve thumbnails rendering quality (v18.11) Feature SLIDESNET-40224 Add support for Strict Open XML format Feature SLIDESNET-40512 Support for setting callout shape for series data label Feature SLIDESNET-40518 Support to get effects by text-box paragraphs Feature SLIDESNET-40523 Implement serialization with Strict Open XML format compliance Feature SLIDESNET-40613 ChartData SetRange on a Pivot Table Feature Public API Changes GetEffectsByParagraph() method has been added to ISequence and Sequence classes GetEffectsByParagraph() method has been added to ISequence and Sequence classes.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 18.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1485 Enhance the implementation of the System::Uri class Enhancement  SLIDESCPP-1527 Improve multi-images GIF processingNew Feature Enhancement  SLIDESNET-37354 Support for rendering shape Soft Edges (EffectFormat) effect Feature SLIDESNET-40366 Turning off update automatically option for Date time in ppt while converting to PDF Feature  SLIDESNET-40544 Connector fails to draw in straight line Enhancement  Public API Changes No change</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 18.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-9-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1380 Improve accuracy of the Graphics::MeasureString method Improvement SLIDESCPP-1445 Improve the stability of the Threading::Thread class Improvement SLIDESNET-40448 The performance issue regarding GetThumbnail method Improvement SLIDESCPP-1412 The output PPTX file is corrupted Bug Public API Changes No change</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 18.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-8-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1388 Improve rendering of joined Bezier curves Feature SLIDESNET-40224 Add support for Strict Open XML format Feature SLIDESNET-34155 Add support for Strict Open XML format Feature SLIDESNET-40189 Rendering of Metafiles ignores fonts loaded with FontsLoader Feature SLIDESNET-40304 Rendering comments from ODP format that have no author Feature SLIDESNET-39229 Support for &amp;ldquo;purl.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 18.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-7-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESNET-25055 Font size of legend, minimum &amp;amp; maximum values of axes Feature SLIDESNET-26270 Support for changing Series Color Feature SLIDESNET-30409 Getting chart image from ChartEx Feature SLIDESNET-31630 Change color of categories in a series Feature SLIDESNET-33795 Setting font related properties for chart data table Feature SLIDESNET-33828 Setting font related properties for individual legend entry Feature SLIDESNET-33909 Setting font related properties for chart data table Feature SLIDESNET-34235 Support for setting Chart Area rounded borders Feature SLIDESNET-34690 Support for Stock chart Feature SLIDESNET-39932 Setting InvertIfNegative for individual series data point Feature SLIDESNET-38920 RemoveEncryption() method removes the encryption from presentation when loaded in read only mode Feature SLIDESCPP-1336 Loading fonts from TTC files Enhancement SLIDESCPP-1352 Improve processing of 8-bit images with alpha channel transparency Enhancement Public API Changes AddDataPointForStockSeries() method has been added to IChartDataPointCollection and ChartDataPointCollection classes AddDataPointForStockSeries() method has been added to IChartDataPointCollection and ChartDataPointCollection classes.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 18.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1255 Improve accuracy of the Graphics::DrawString laying out Feature SLIDESCPP-1293 Improve overall performance of the Aspose.Slides for C++ Feature SLIDESNET-33796 Support for setting precision of data in chart data label Feature SLIDESNET-33801 Support for setting the date format for Category Axis Value Feature SLIDESNET-33974 Support for setting rotation angle for chart axis title Feature SLIDESNET-33995 Support for switch Row/Column for chart data Feature SLIDESNET-34083 Setting the chart marker options on data points level Feature SLIDESNET-34458 Support of setting Position Axis in Category or Value Axis Feature SLIDESNET-34469 Support for showing Display Unit label on Chart value axis Feature SLIDESNET-34573 Support for setting markers and its properties for particular chart series point Feature SLIDESNET-36864 Getting Series Data Point color from Theme Feature SLIDESNET-40158 Support for Bubble chart Size scaling Feature SLIDESNET-35261 Setting Series Overlap for Clustered Bar Chart Feature SLIDESNET-39685 Support for managing visibility of data labels located outside of plot area Feature SLIDESNET-40193 Improve slide graph quality Feature SLIDESCPP-1240 Surrogate pairs with hieroglyphs are not rendered properly Bug Public API Changes IChart.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 18.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-5-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESNET-39148 Support for setting custom position for child nodes in SmartArt Feature SLIDESNET-39950 Set Number of Nodes on Row level Feature SLIDESNET-40035 Rendering comments from ODP format Feature SLIDESCPP-1228 Fix the differences between drawing arrow caps in C++ and .NET Enhancement SLIDESCPP-1230 Fix graphics primitives drawing using a pen with tiny width Enhancement SLIDESCPP-1247 Fix incorrect spacing of a text containing unicode punctuation modifiers Enhancement Public API Changes Support for setting X and Y properties has been implemented in SmartArtShape class In Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 18.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-4-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-1171 Introduce new SmartPtr implementation Feature SLIDESCPP-1185 Improve TextureBrush rendering quality Feature SLIDESCPP-1192 Improve performance and reduce binaries size in Debug configuration Feature SLIDESCPP-1195 Introduce embedded resources mechanism Feature SLIDESCPP-1199 Improve CMYK color model processing when working with JPEG file format Feature SLIDESNET-36069 Make Aspose.Slides library interruptible Feature SLIDESNET-39935 Support for Picture Organization Chart SmartArt Layout Feature SLIDESNET-33471 Support for loading and using MS office theme file (*.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 18.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-3-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category SLIDESNET-38900 Option for saving fonts when converting to HTML Feature SLIDESNET-39415 Show Aspose.Slides in Add Reference dialog Feature SLIDESCPP-1142 Fix getting wrong family name when using some external fonts Bug SLIDESCPP-1143 Fix incorrect rendered text vertical position when using some external fonts Bug SLIDESCPP-1150 Fix incomplete cloning of the System::Drawing::Pen objects Bug SLIDESCPP-1151 Fix System::Drawing::Graphics::set_Clip method behavior for infinite regions Bug SLIDESCPP-1154 Fix possible &amp;ldquo;System::XmlException&amp;rdquo; exceptions when loading a presentation containing charts Bug SLIDESCPP-1160 Fix MeasureString method calculations for GenericTypographic argument Bug Public API Changes All Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 18.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-2-release-notes/</guid><description>
This release is based on Aspose.Slides for .NET 18.2. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain any API changes. All changes are related to internal improvements.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 18.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2018/aspose-slides-for-cpp-18-1-release-notes/</guid><description>
This is the first Aspose.Slides for C++ 18.1 release. Its API is completely new, and it is based on Aspose.Slides for .NET 18.1 API.
Aspose.Slides for C++ 18.1 doesn&amp;rsquo;t support GIF and TIFF image formats. There are known WMF/EMF and SVG restrictions. These features will be added soon. Slides rendered with .NET and C++ versions can have small differences because different rendering engines are used.</description></item></channel></rss>