<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 24.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-24-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-24-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 24.1.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-1112 Extract multi-volume zip archive. Feature ZIPNET-1111 Set proper encoding for some charsets. Bug ZIPNET-1106 New plugins were introduced. Feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public methods and properties were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.12.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-1062 Introduce FastLZ compression. Feature ZIPNET-1084 Encrypt existing ZIP archive without repacking. Feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description Aspose.Zip.FastLZ.FastLZStream A stream wrapper that compresses data with FastLZ.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.11.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-1094 Segment of multi-volume zip does not properly close on flush. Bug ZIPNET-1078 Fix self-extracting archive license for .NET Framework 2.0. Bug ZIPNET-1063 Proper license setting. Bug ZIPNET-1099 Extract multi-volume 7z archive. Feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public methods and properties were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-10-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.10.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-1087 Store modification time of zip entry. Feature ZIPNET-1076 Store modification time of 7z entry. Feature ZIPNET-1063 Proper license setting. Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.9.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-400 Optionally compress 7z header. Feature ZIPNET-1074 Limit the length of zip comment. Bug ZIPNET-1071 Proper license setting. Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public methods and properties were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.8.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-1037 Support tar archives compressed with Zstandard. Feature ZIPNET-1036 Extract WavPack in ZIP container. Feature ZIPNET-1051 Proper work of self-extracting archive with library nearby. Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public methods and properties were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.7.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-1031 Compose XAR archive. Feature ZIPNET-1009 Added Zstandard compression method for ZIP container. Feature ZIPNET-1038 Introduce unknown archive format instead of null. Enhancement ZIPNET-1027 Increase bzip2 parallel compression speed. Enhancement ZIPNET-1030 Compress to LZMA2 in 7z in multiple threads.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.6.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-1023 Extract 7z archives with encrypted headers. Feature ZIPNET-1022 Support conholdate plugin license. Feature - Make ExtractToDirectory and Extract methods public for some archives. Enhancement ZIPNET-1028 Release file handle on archive disposal. Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public methods and properties were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-5-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.5.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-1009 Extract plain ZIP entries compressed with Zstandard. Feature ZIPNET-1007 Do not dispose extraction stream on archvie disposal. Bug ZIPNET-1004 Check password correctness on 7z stored extraction. Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.4.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-994 Parallelize lzip composition. Feature ZIPNET-1008 Fix out of range exception while composing xz archive. Bug ZIPNET-1004 Parallelize xz composition. Feature ZIPNET-998 Provide comment for split ZIP archive. Enhancement ZIPNET-984 Introduce ExtractToDirectory method for IArchive interface. Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public methods and properties were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-3-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.3.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-990 7z archive with empty files and directories may fail to extract. Bug ZIPNET-927 Increase RAR decompression speed. Enhancement ZIPNET-987 Increase LZMA/LZMA2 compression speed. Enhancement</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.2.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-968 Make LZMA and LZMA2 compression faster. Enhancement ZIPNET-983 Make entries collection of an archive to keep stable reference. Bug ZIPNET-975 Introduce common interface for all archive types. Feature ZIPNET-531 Detect content and file names encryption. Feature ZIPNET-964 Allow to attach external cipher for 7z AES encryption.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-zip-for-net-23-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.ZIP for .NET 23.1.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type ZIPNET-937 Detect archive format without loading. Feature ZIPNET-957 Wrong filenames for subfolders in 7z archive. Bug ZIPNET-958 Compose multi-volume 7z archive. Feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>