<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2014 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2014 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 14.12.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-12-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-12-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 14.12.0
Aspose.Words for Java 14.12 Release Notes Major Features There are 103 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
WordArt rendering does not rely on GDI+ now and supported on .NET, Mono and Java New mode of handling styles during Import via public ImportFormatMode.KeepDifferentStyles Public API for specifying text effects for Revisions during rendering to fixed formats Shape connectors supported Improved tight wrapping mode for floating objects Improved rendering of overlapped and nested floating objects Enhanced inter-characters spacing calculation for Asian documents with kerning Improved text direction detection for documents with missing RTL attributes Hyperlinks on shapes and text inside textboxes are exported correctly to HTML All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-970 Dml Shadow Effects are smaller on Java.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 14.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 14.10
Aspose.Words for Java 14.10 Release Notes Major Features There are 106 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved DocumentBuilder to handle mixed LTR/RTL text Improved breaking of floating tables in layout Improved custom tab stop beyond line ending Implemented new features and effects in DrawingML rendering Added LoadOptions.WebRequestTimeout property All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-934 Inaccurate wrapping of WordArt wtih coordinates.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 14.9 Release Notes Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-9-release-notes-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-9-release-notes-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 14.9 Release Notes
Aspose.Words for Java 14.9 Release Notes Major Features There are 120 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Databinding for image SDTs is supported DrawingML is now a composite node (breaking change to the public API) DrawingML supports linked textboxes Rendering of &amp;lsquo;keep with next&amp;rsquo; paragraphs is improved Implemented &amp;lsquo;Use printer metrics to lay out document&amp;rsquo; compatibility option (Windows/GDI only) Improved tabs handling logic for Word 2013 and compatible modes in rendering Extrusion effect for DrawingML shapes rendering implemented (cold rendering) Rounding corners rendering in DrawingML charts implemented Improved 3D lighting rendering for WordArt objects Added support of Gradient background in HTML output All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-901 Thin line is missed.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 14.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 14.8.0
Aspose.Words for Java 14.8 Release Notes Major Features There are 79 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved how TOC field culture and formatting is handled Timestamping of PDF digital signature using external timestamp server implemented Improvements to advanced rendering features e.g. pre-blending semi-transparent images Horizontal rotation of characters having HorizontalRotatedFarEast orientation supported Improved page layout for additional compatibility modes Improved floater positioning in complex cases All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-913 Incorrect conversion of watermark from word document to pdf Bug WORDSJAVA-916 Svg: spare text tags for empty text.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 14.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 14.7.0
Aspose.Words for Java 14.7 Release Notes Major Features There are 114 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improvements to DrawingML shadow, extrusion and 3D rendering algorithms New public API to specify revision marks appearance for rendering Vertical text is supported in HTML, MHTML and EPUB Improvements to rendering and line wrapping for Arabic and Far East scripts Improvements to rendering of inline shapes within rotated text All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-904 Docx to Pdf conversion issue with mailto link Bug WORDSJAVA-907 Conversion of HTML to Docx issue with Img tag at Linux Bug WORDSJAVA-911 Pdf: rasterised SVG image looks highly upscaled in Acrobat.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 14.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 14.6.0
Aspose.Words for Java 14.6 Release Notes Major Features There are 115 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Support of automatic change tracking on a document Added vertical text support to HTML\Epub\MHT Footnote and endnote references now can be rendered as hyperlinks into output PDF CJK (Chinese, Japanese, Korean) text is now properly rendered in multiline DrawingML textboxes Default text AntiAliasing on Java is optimized for Chinese, Japanese and Korean fonts Font substitution feature is added to public API All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-909 Add Font Substitution feature to public API.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 14.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 14.5.0
Aspose.Words for Java 14.5 Release Notes Major Features There are 95 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Performance improvement Improved justification around inline paragraph breaks Hyphenation API updated and extended with a callback mechanism Table row wrapping around floaters in compatibility mode improved OOXML (MS Word 2010) Text effects rendering implemented Image export to HTML, MHTML and EPUB improved FitText attribute supported for all flow formats All Changes WORDSJAVA-871 Spare default font hints in DOCX document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 14.4.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-4-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-4-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 14.4.1
This is a hotfix release, use if instructed by the technical support.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 14.4 Release Notes Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-4-release-notes-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-4-release-notes-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 14.4 Release Notes
Aspose.Words for Java 14.4 Release Notes Major Features There are 83 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improvements to rendering of Arabic texts Improvements to rendering of complex document layouts Improved handling of themes, list styles and building blocks when joining documents Added support of text frames in ODT import/export Improvements in TXT import capabilities Gradient fill with transparency rendering in PDF implemented 3D rotated DrawingML shapes (and images) rendering implemented Better support of tab stops and underlines in HTML import/export All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-870 Horisontal gradient fill doesn&amp;rsquo;t work inside Smart Art.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 14.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 14.3.0
Aspose.Words for Java 14.3 Release Notes Major Features There are 95 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Public API for insertion of OLE objects both linked and embedded Outline, Shadow, Reflection, Glow and Fill text effects for rendering text inside DrawingML shapes EUDC fonts rendering partially supported “PDF Logical Structure” export reworked, significantly improving memory usage All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-867 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 14.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 14.2.0
Aspose.Words for Java 14.2 Release Notes Major Features There are 131 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved export of tabs and tab stop positions to HTML Tab leaders are preserved when exporting to HTML Move revisions are supported in RTF Hyphenation is now supported in the layout engine (with external dictionaries) Drop caps positioning improved Improved rendering of hidden text Improved rendering of Asian text, ordering of Arabic punctuation marks DrawingML &amp;ldquo;Inner Shadow&amp;rdquo; effect rendering implemented Multiline watermark rendering supports &amp;ldquo;Fit to Bezier curves&amp;rdquo; cases Digitally signing XPS documents is possible now All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-508 Table render differently, while saving in doc, png and Pdf format.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 14.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-words-for-java-14-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 14.1.0
Aspose.Words for Java 14.1 Release Notes Major Features There are 118 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Support for password-protected documents created in MS Word 2013 New public API to control rendering of tracking changes / revisions Reduced peak memory usage for large documents Performance improvements to the page layout engine Rendering of hidden text is improved Calculation of line height for Chinese characters improved Export comments to HTML as footnotes Export of drop-down fields and form fields as text into HTML Document headers and footers can now be preserved in DOC-HTML-DOC roundtrip DrawingML Soft Edge rendering effect implemented DrawingML preset shadows rendering implemented Hyperlink fragmentation in PDF resolved All Changes Key Summary Category WORDSJAVA-419 Symbol dissapiar in Embedded OLE Equation Bug WORDSJAVA-434 Shifted position for WordArts with pathInfo.</description></item></channel></rss>