<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Page for .NET 23.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for .NET 23.12.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PAGENET-73 Implement support for Separate colorspace Feature PAGENET-544 Add support for DeviceN colorspace Feature PAGENET-482 Implement ClippingByText method in PsDocument Feature PAGENET-542 Add support for XPS to PS conversion Feature PAGENET-575 Can’t convert EPS to tiff Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Added APIs T:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for .NET 23.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for .NET 23.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PAGENET-567 Converting EPS to JPG throws exception Bug PAGENET-464 Add support for text with glyph indices in PS document Feature PAGENET-509 Implement Flate encoding for alpha channel of transparent image in PS document Feature PAGENET-556 Fix text in Type0 FmapType 9 font Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Got any Query?</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for .NET 23.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for .NET 23.10.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PAGENET-552 PS to PDF: Quots defined by 2-bytes sequence are not rendered Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Got any Query? In case you have any query or need assistance in getting started with Aspose.Page for .NET, head on to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for .NET 23.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for .NET 23.9.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PAGENET-208 XPS to Multipage TIFF file Feature PAGENET-546 Add EPS resize functionality Feature PAGENET-545 Add EPS crop functionality Feature PAGENET-531 Add support for bitmap CIDFonts (FontType 32) Feature PAGENET-550 Add caching for bitmap glyphs of font FontType 32 Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Added APIs Type:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for .NET 23.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for .NET 23.8.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PAGENET-528 Optimize XPS loading and saving Enhancement PAGENET-529 Reduce image size for image masks from 32bpp to 1bpp Enhancement Got any Query? In case you have any query or need assistance in getting started with Aspose.Page for .NET, head on to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for .NET 23.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for .NET 23.7.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PAGENET-421 Fix converting multipaged document with different page sizes Bug PAGENET-521 Implement CCITTFaxDecode filter Feature PAGENET-518 XPS to PDF conversion - Keep text glyphs as text in PDF Bug PAGENET-479 If the XPS file is more then 10 MB then it will take more then 15Mins to load the file Bug Got any Query?</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for .NET 23.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for .NET 23.6.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PAGENET-462 Create Aspose.Page for .NET plugins Feature PAGENET-517 Add support for .NET7 Feature PAGENET-511 PS to PDF: gradient fill doesn&amp;rsquo;t work for the text Bug Got any Query? In case you have any query or need assistance in getting started with Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for .NET 23.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for .NET 23.5.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PAGENET-502 Add subsetting of embedded fonts Feature PAGENET-481 Text in Japan glyphs is rendered as rectangles Bug PAGENET-507 Cyrillic text is rendered as rectangles Bug PAGENET-508 PS to PDF: Unicode characters converted incorrectly Bug PAGENET-510 PS to PDF: location of text after rectangles filled with texture pattern is incorrect Bug Got any Query?</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for .NET 23.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for .NET 23.4.
Improvements and Changes Warning! In this realease we stop to continue delivering libraries for .NET Framework 2.0, 3.5 and 3.5CP, .Net Core 3.0 and .NET 5.0.
Key Summary Category PAGENET-497 SVG to EPS: Filling graphics path with Alternative FillMode is converted incorrectly Bug PAGENET-498 SVG to EPS: Graphics path with unconnected segments is converted incorrectly Bug PAGENET-499 SVG to EPS: Translucent image converted incorrectly Bug PAGENET-500 SVG to EPS: Linear gradient with zero width or height is converted incorrectly Bug PAGENET-496 Setting background color in PsDocument doesn&amp;rsquo;t work Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Added APIs Method:Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for .NET 23.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for .NET 23.3.
Improvements and Changes Warning! In the next realease we will discontinue to deliver libraries for .NET Framework 3.5, 3.5-Client, .Net Core 3.0 and .NET 5.0.
Key Summary Category PAGENET-457 Add support for unicode characters in PostScript file Feature PAGENET-459 Add support for transparent images in texture patterns in PostScript files Feature PAGENET-469 Add support for Compose Fonts (Type0) in &amp;ldquo;charpath&amp;rdquo; operators Feature PAGENET-470 PS to PDF: Incorrect paint after &amp;ldquo;initclip&amp;rdquo; operator while converting text in Composite font Bug PAGENET-471 PS to PDF: &amp;ldquo;Minus&amp;rdquo;/&amp;ldquo;hyphen&amp;rdquo; is converted incorrectly Bug PAGENET-472 PS to PDF: Fix conversion of circle symbol (0x2021) Bug PAGENET-473 PS to PDF: Fix conversion of &amp;ldquo;nbsp&amp;rdquo; symbol (0xa0) Bug Got any Query?</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for .NET 23.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for .NET 23.2.
Improvements and Changes Delivery of library for .NET Framework 2.0 is discontinued.
Key Summary Category PAGENET-420 Content are rendered outside the page after PS to PDF conversion Bug PAGENET-465 PS file with two TTF and two CMAPs throws exception Bug PAGENET-466 Convert XPS to PDF retain outline Bug Got any Query?</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for .NET 23.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-page-for-net-23-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for .NET 23.1.
Improvements and Changes Warning! In the next realease we will discontinue to deliver libraries for .NET Framework 2.0, 3.5 and 3.5CP.
Key Summary Category PAGENET-450 Implement creation and completing of PostScript document from scratch Feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Added APIs Method:Aspose.Page.Device.WritePaint(System.Drawing.Drawing2D.PathGradientBrush) Method:Aspose.Page.Device.WritePaint(Aspose.Page.EPS.GradientBrush) Type:Aspose.Page.EPS.PsDocumentException Method:Aspose.Page.EPS.PsDocumentException.#ctor(System.String) Type:Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>