<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2016/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 16.12.1 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-cad-for-net-16-12-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-cad-for-net-16-12-1-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.CAD for .Net has been updated to version 16.12.1 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.CAD.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category CADNET-202 Update Dynabic.Metered functionality New Feature CADNET-195 Implement Underlay Flags for DWG format New Feature CADNET-170 Implement drawing of DGN format as a part of DWG New Feature CADNET-185 Converting DWG to PDF is showing incorrect results Enhancement CADNET-177 Implement reading insert coordinate and rotation angle for DGN underlay.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 16.12 Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-cad-for-net-16-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-cad-for-net-16-12-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.CAD for .Net has been updated to version 16.12 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.CAD.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category CADNET-195 Implement Underlay Flags for DWG format New Feature CADNET-170 Implement drawing of DGN format as a part of DWG New Feature CADNET-185 Converting DWG to PDF is showing incorrect results Enhancement CADNET-177 Implement reading insert coordinate and rotation angle for DGN underlay Enhancement CADNET-173 Converting DWG to PNG in multithread is throwing exception Enhancement Usage Examples CADNET-195 Implement Underlay Flags for DWG format</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 16.10 Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-cad-for-net-16-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-cad-for-net-16-10-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.CAD for .Net has been updated to version 16.10 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.CAD.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category CADNET-134 Integrate metering module to promote new sales model for Aspose.CAD New Feature CADNET-164 Loading DGN file is throwing exception Enhancement CADNET-156 Converting DWG to PNG format is producing very small PNG image that is unable to view Enhancement CADNET-155 Adjust Metered module quota consumption algorythm Enhancement CADNET-154 Fix application menu URLs Enhancement CADNET-152 CAD Hatches Offsetting After Printing PDF Enhancement CADNET-149 Converting DXF to Image is working but producing shapes with very thin lines; not of proper width of lines Enhancement CADNET-147 Make Dgn exporter respects &amp;lsquo;TypeOfEntities&amp;rsquo; rasterization property Enhancement CADNET-137 Converting DWG to PDF is generating extra page at the end of PDF file Enhancement CADNET-136 Low quality of pdf files generated by GDI Pdf exporter Enhancement CADNET-133 Review and adapt architecture to CAD domain Enhancement CADNET-132 Compound objects of a DGN drawing are not displayed Enhancement CADNET-130 No GDI Pdf exporter available for DGN format Enhancement CADNET-127 Add shortcuts to online documentation and other useful aspose resources Enhancement CADNET-126 DGN exporter doesn&amp;rsquo;t respect pen color Enhancement CADNET-125 Text shifts unexpectedly during Model export Enhancement CADNET-122 AutomaticLayoutsScaling does not work correctly Enhancement CADNET-120 Some Patterns are missing while converting DXF to PDF format Enhancement CADNET-117 GC overhead limit exceeded - exception when loading DWG file Enhancement CADNET-108 Improve Image.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 1.1.0 Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-cad-for-net-1-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-cad-for-net-1-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.CAD for .Net has been updated to version 1.1.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.CAD.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category CADNET-112 Find or search text in the DWG file New Feature CADNET-111 Support to retrieve block attribute values from within a dwg and its external references New Feature CADNET-16 Support for DGN file format for possible conversion to PDF &amp;amp; raster image formats New Feature CADNET-118 Msi misses End User Agreement link Enhancement CADNET-109 Cad export to Bmp fails with out of memory exception Enhancement CADNET-88 Unable to access Face3D Objects in DXF file Enhancement Usage Examples CADNET-112 Find or search text in the DWG file</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 1.0.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-cad-for-net-1-0-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-cad-for-net-1-0-0-release-notes/</guid><description>We are pleased to announce the first release of Aspose.CAD for .NET. It allows you to convert AutoCAD DWG and DXF files to PDF and Raster images. It is a native API and does not require AutoCAD or any other software to be installed.
You can also convert the selected layers and layouts from the AutoCAD files. The conversion to PDF and Raster images is of very high quality. At the moment we support the following Cad image types for loading (please refer to the https://autodesk.</description></item></channel></rss>