<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>fundamentals on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/categories/fundamentals/</link><description>Recent content in fundamentals on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/categories/fundamentals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Cells | Excel Spreadsheet Processing Java Library</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Feb 2024 11:15:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/java/</guid><description>Java API for Excel File Formats
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.Cells for Java is an award-winning Excel Spreadsheet Processing API that allows Java developers to embed the ability to read, write and manipulate Excel® spreadsheets (XLS, XLSX, XLSM, XLSB, XLTX, SpreadsheetML, CSV, ODS), HTML, MHTML, PDF, and image file formats into their own Java applications without needing to rely on Microsoft Excel®.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email | Java Class Library to Process Outlook Formats</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 09:09:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/</guid><description>Java Email API
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.Email for Java is a complete set of Email Processing APIs to create, read and manipulate emails from within your applications. It makes it easier to work with many Outlook email message formats such as MSG, EML, EMLX and MHT files without the need of installing Microsoft Outlook.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Diagram | Java Library to Create, Export Visio Docs</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Feb 2024 08:22:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/diagram/java/</guid><description>Java API for Microsoft Visio® File Formats
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.Diagram for Java API is a solution for Microsoft Visio file manipulation requirements. It allows the Java applications to read, write, export and process Microsoft Visio diagrams while supporting all Visio objects &amp;amp; properties including shapes, pages, images, shape masters, stencils, text, layers, header, footers, user-defined cells, hyperlinks, file protection, geometries, text boxes, and comments.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging | Process &amp; Convert Images via Java Library</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 09:49:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/</guid><description>Java API for Image Processing
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
It is a standalone Imaging API consisting of Java routines that enable your Java applications to draw as well as perform basic to advanced level processing of raster &amp;amp; vector images.
Aspose.Imaging for Java offers robust image compression and high processing speed through native byte access and a range of efficient algorithms.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.ZIP | Java Library to Compress or Decompress Files &amp; Folders</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/java/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 17:30:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/zip/java/</guid><description>Process ZIP files via Java API
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.ZIP for Java is a standalone Java API to create, manipulate, extract &amp;amp; protect archives.
Aspose.ZIP for Java class library allows your Java applications to compress/decompress files and folders without getting into the complexity of coding new compression algorithms or understanding the existing ones.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Total | Java Class Libraries to Process File Formats</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/total/java/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 08:17:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/total/java/</guid><description>Java Classes for Document Format Manipulation
Product Page | Docs | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License | Policies
Aspose.Total for Java is the most complete package of all Java file format APIs offered by Aspose. It empowers developers to create, edit, render, print, and convert between a wide range of popular document formats from within any Java application.
Aspose.Words for Java Word Java library allows performing MS Word document processing operations such as document creation, processing, rendering, and conversion of Microsoft Word, OpenOffice, Markup, and eBook document formats.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D | Java Class Library to Process 3D Images, Models</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 07:41:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/</guid><description>Java API for 3D Image Processing
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.3D for Java API is built to create, edit, manipulate and save 3D formats. It empowers Java applications to connect with 3D documents without installing any software package on the computer. Aspose.3D for Java API assist developers to model and create massive worlds in games, superb scenes for design visualization, and engage virtual reality experiences.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF | Java PDF Document Processing Class Library</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/java/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 01:35:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/java/</guid><description>Java API to Process &amp;amp; Manipulate PDF Files
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.PDF for Java is a PDF document creation component that enables your Java applications to read, write and manipulate PDF documents without using Adobe Acrobat.
aspose.pdf Package Features PDF Document Featres Set basic information (e.g. author, creator) of the PDF document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks | Java Library to Ceate &amp; Manage Project Tasks</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 17:40:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/</guid><description>Microsoft Project File Manipulation API
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.Tasks a Java Project Management API to manipulate Microsoft Project files. Developers can define a project’s main and default properties as well as calendar information. API also provides the ability to specify weekdays and calendar exceptions while making it easy to add &amp;amp; recalculate tasks, resources and other data without user intervention.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides | Java Library to Process PowerPoint Formats</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/java/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 14:02:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/java/</guid><description>Java PowerPoint API
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.Slides a Java PowerPoint API for presentation manipulation and management. It allows developers to read, write, convert and manipulate PowerPoint presentations in Java applications with the ability to manipulate all document elements such as slides, tables, text, charts, shapes, images and SmartArt diagrams and more.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR | Image Character Recognition Java Class Library</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jan 2024 07:59:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java/</guid><description>Java OCR Library
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.OCR for Java is a character and optical mark recognition API that allows developers to add OCR functionality in their applications. It provides a simple set of classes for controlling character recognition.
Convert Image to Text via Java Read characters from images. Support for JPG, PNG, GIF, BMP and TIFF image file formats for OCR.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.BarCode | Process 1D, 2D &amp; Postal Barcodes via Java</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 15:41:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/barcode/java/</guid><description>Barcode Library for Java Applications
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.BarCode for Java is a robust and reliable barcode generation and recognition component, written in Java, it allows developers to quickly and easily add barcode generation and recognition functionality to their Java applications.
Demo applications Generate Barcode Recognize Barcode Embed Barcode Barcode API Features Specify different kinds of symbologies.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Drawing | Draw 2D graphics and text via Java Library</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/drawing/java/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jan 2024 15:11:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/drawing/java/</guid><description>Java API for 2D graphics drawing
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.Drawing for Java is an advanced Java 2D graphics drawing API that enables you to render vector graphics (such as lines, curves, and figures) and text (in a variety of fonts, sizes, and styles) onto raster images represented by an array of pixels in memory.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.HTML | Java Class Library to Manipulate HTML Files</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 17:12:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/html/java/</guid><description>HTML File Manipulation Java API
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
The Java HTML API assists developers to write, read, modify, navigate and convert (X)HTML documents from within Java applications.
Aspose.HTML for Java API works as a headless browser that allows you to create or open existing HTML documents from various sources in order to perform manipulation operations such as remove and replace HTML nodes, save HTML documents, extract CSS from HTML, configure a document sandbox and more.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page | Java Class Library for PostScript Processing</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 14:46:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/</guid><description>Java APIs for PS, EPS &amp;amp; XPS File Formats
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.Page for Java offers to creating &amp;amp; manipulate XPS documents. It also provides functionality to convert XPS, PS &amp;amp; EPS documents to image formats &amp;amp; PDF.
Manipulate XPS Documents via Java Create and edit XPS document. Add or remove pages of XPS document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 15:58:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/</guid><description>Java Library for Photoshop Files
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.PSD for Java is an easy to use Adobe Photoshop file format manipulation API. It can easily load and read PSD, PSB &amp;amp; AI files, making it possible for the Java developers to perform operations like updating layer properties, adding watermarks, compression, rotation, scaling or rendering one file format to another without needing to install Adobe Photoshop.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words | Java Library to Process Document Formats</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 18:48:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/</guid><description>Java API for Various Document Formats
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.Words for Java is an advanced Java Word processing API that enables you to perform a great range of document processing tasks directly within your Java applications. Aspose.Words for Java API supports processing word (DOC, DOCX, OOXML, RTF) HTML, OpenDocument, PDF, EPUB, XPS, SWF and all image formats.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Font | Java Font Processing API | TT, CFF, OT, Type1</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/java/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 03:13:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/java/</guid><description>Java API for Various Font Formats
Product Page | Docs | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.Font for Java is a font loading and drawing library. It supports multiple front formats such as TrueType (with TrueType collectons), CFF, OpenType, and Type1. The API provides rich functionality to load/save font and provide information about its data structures along with any glyph that is supported by all the font types.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OMR | Java Class Library for Digital Marks Extraction</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/omr/java/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2023 09:02:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/omr/java/</guid><description>Java API to Perform OMR
Home | Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.OMR for Java is a Java class library that provides API to recognize optical marks from OMR digitized sheet images. It can be used to recognize optical marks in a variety of image formats like BMP, JPG, TIF, TIFF, GIF. The API allows capturing human-marked data from document forms such as surveys, questionnaires, multiple-choice examination papers, and other tests.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.TeX | Java Library to Typeset &amp; Convert TeX Files</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tex/java/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 06:20:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tex/java/</guid><description>Java API to TypeSet TeX Files
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.TeX for Java is a library that provides a TeX engine extension called ObjectTeX. It can be used to typeset documents described by TeX files. Object means that intermediarytypesetting result is a specific object model which then can be uniformly converted into a number of end formats.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note | Java Library to Create/Manipulate OneNote Docs</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 07:26:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/</guid><description>Java API for OneNote Document Processing
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.Note for Java is a class library that enables applications to interact with Microsoft Office OneNote programmatically without its installation on the server. It is a pure alternate for MS OneNote Object Model provides much better performance and ease of use to manage OneNote documents.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD Java 23.8 | CAD and BIM Processing Conversion Java API SDK</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Nov 2023 13:38:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/</guid><description>CAD File Conversion API for Java
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.CAD for Java allows developers to export and convert CAD and BIM drawing files like DWG, DXF, DWT, DAE and others to PDF, Vector and Raster images. It is a native API and does not require AutoCAD or any other software to be installed.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PUB | Electronic Publishing Files Java Class Library</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/java/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 16:35:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/java/</guid><description>Process PUB files via Java API
Product Page | Docs | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.PUB for Java is a Java API that can read, manipulate and convert Microsoft Publisher (.pub) files to PDF. You can use the API in your Java applications to work with .pub files without worrying about the underlying filie format. The API can be used in Java desktop as well as web applications using JSP.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR | Image Character Recognition Java Class Library</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java-gpu/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2023 21:03:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/java-gpu/</guid><description>Java OCR Library
Product Page | Docs | Demos | API Reference | Examples | Blog | Search | Free Support | Temporary License
Aspose.OCR-GPU for Java is a character and optical mark recognition API that allows developers to add OCR functionality in their applications. It provides a simple set of classes for controlling character recognition.
Convert Image to Text via Java Read characters from images. Support for JPG, PNG, GIF, BMP and TIFF image file formats for OCR.</description></item></channel></rss>