<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Email for Android via Java 19.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Android via Java 19.10
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-39192 Provide support for the Notes Storage Facility (NSF) database file New Feature EMAILNET-39433 Add support for AMP HTML emails New Feature EMAILNET-39544 Skype Appointment/Call not supported Enhancement EMAILNET-39579 Wrongly display HtmlBodyText URL Enhancement EMAILNET-39606 Provide more accurate HTML to Text conversion.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Android via Java 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Android via Java 19.7
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-39516 Count item in OLM folder New Feature EMAILNET-39499 Support for document conversion progress New Feature EMAILNET-39524 Get emails from Zimbra New Feature EMAILNET-39453 Obtaining the list of custom folders created by user New Feature EMAILJAVA-34497 Support for getting folder path in OLM file New Feature EMAILJAVA-34528 Corrupt PST file is not throwing an error in Aspose Email Enhancement EMAILNET-39519 API hangs while converting MSG to MHTML Bug EMAILJAVA-34563 Formatting issue in MSG to MHT conversion Bug EMAILNET-39514 Message item having ICS file as attachment being incorrectly recognized as appointment Bug EMAILNET-39520 HtmlBodyText returns tag values that are not displayed in the email Bug EMAILNET-39525 Attachment ‘unavailable’ on iPhone 6, iPhone XR, and others (Mail 19.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Android via Java 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Android via Java 19.4
Major Changes Support for creating ICF and VCF version 3.0 files All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILJAVA-34491 Support for creating ICF and VCF version 3.0 files New Feature EMAILNET-35124 Option to write vCard files with S/MIME certificate in PEM format Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34522 Support for Russian Culture Name: en-RU Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34394 Provision to set locales Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34519 FormatException when passing dot-comma to “To” header Bug EMAILNET-39440 HTML body is lost when MapiMessage.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Android via Java 19.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Android via Java 19.3
Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-39295 Option to save MapiCalendar with HTML body format. Enhancement EMAILNET-39265 Working with TNEF and VCard Bug EMAILJAVA-34490 Adding EML with email addresses in other languages to PST changes those addresses to question marks Bug EMAILNET-39278 The cloned messages are not identical to the original messages Bug EMAILNET-39168 Email To PDF conversion adds styles to the top of the document Bug EMAILNET-39264 Extract and Saving Messages Directly from PST to Stream Bug EMAILNET-39267 Unable to manually create a new folder via Outlook for a PST generated by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Android via Java 19.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-19-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2019/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-19-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Android via Java 19.1
Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILJAVA-34466 Loading and saving VCF contact skips some information. Bug EMAILNET-39230 No bullets added to the output of HtmlBodyText Bug EMAILJAVA-34467 MailMessage.load throwing an exception with EML Bug EMAILNET-39245 Update date in the header using MapiMessage to display in MHTML output Bug EMAILNET-39252 MSG contact to MHT conversion issue Bug EMAILJAVA-34480 MapiMessage.</description></item></channel></rss>