<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2014 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2014 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 8.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-8-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have implemented new Aspose.Tasks for Java API. The API is more clear and easy to use. We recommend our customers to start to use the revamped version. Note, we will publish at least three releases of the existing API along side the new version. Bugs and any regression issues will be fixed in both versions but new features will be added in the revamped version only. We have supported new features for writing and reading for MPP format, importing Primavera XML file format and export to HTML format.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 7.4.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-4-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-4-1-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have fixed two bugs this release. Please, see details below.
All Changes Issue type Key Summary Bug TASKS-33893 MPP-&amp;gt;XML raises ArgumentOutOfRangeException Bug TASKS-33877 Output MPP file cannot be opened in MSP 2007 after updating the hyperlinks</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 7.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have fixed the issue &amp;ldquo;Images can not be rendered to PNG, JPG, BMP because of wrong locations in the output compared to .NET version.&amp;rdquo;
All Changes Issue Type Key Summary Bug TASKS-33833 Images cannot be rendered to PNG, JPG, BMP because of wrong locations in the output compared to .NET version.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 7.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have fixed several bugs this release. Details column in usage view was supported for 2003-2013 mpp formats. Note, our main focus is design of new Aspose.Tasks for Java API which will be available soon. The API will be more simple, clear and easy to use. Please see list of all changes below.
All Changes No changes were made in the release.
Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public classes were added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 7.2.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-2-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-2-1-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have supported WBS code fields reading and writing this release. We also have provided link arrows between tasks across the pages while MPP to PDF conversion. Bug &amp;lsquo;TASKS-33763 MPP-&amp;gt;PDF generates blank output&amp;rsquo; was fixed. About 13 bugs were fixed in total. Please see list of all changes below.
All Changes Issue type Key Summary Task TASKS-33791 TASKS-33779 Implement FF, SF links rendering across vertical pages Task TASKS-33786 TASKS-33779 Implement FS, SS links rendering across vertical pages Task TASKS-33785 TASKS-33779 Implement links rendering across horizontal pages Task TASKS-33782 TASKS-33775 Implement WBS code definition writing to mpp Task TASKS-33781 TASKS-33775 Implement WBS code definition writing to xml Task TASKS-33778 TASKS-33775 Implement WBS code definition reading from mpp and xml New Feature TASKS-33775 Support WBS code fields reading and writing.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 7.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have supported WBS code fields reading and writing this release. We also have provided link arrows between tasks across the pages while MPP to PDF conversion. About 12 bugs were fixed. Please see list of all changes below.
All Changes Issue type Key Summary New Feature TASKS-33775 Support WBS code fields reading and writing. Investigation TASKS-33808 Exception raised while loading the license if culture uses the UmAlQuraCalendar Enhancement TASKS-33779 Provide link arrows between tasks across the pages while MPP to PDF conversion Task TASKS-33791 TASKS-33779 Implement FF, SF links rendering across vertical pages Task TASKS-33786 TASKS-33779 Implement FS, SS links rendering across vertical pages Task TASKS-33785 TASKS-33779 Implement links rendering across horizontal pages Task TASKS-33782 TASKS-33775 Implement WBS code definition writing to mpp Task TASKS-33781 TASKS-33775 Implement WBS code definition writing to xml Task TASKS-33778 TASKS-33775 Implement WBS code definition reading from mpp and xml Bug TASKS-33804 MPP to PDF always renders collapsed sub tasks in expanded form Bug TASKS-33801 Image added in &amp;ldquo;i&amp;rdquo; column Bug TASKS-33800 Column text color changes from Black to Red Bug TASKS-33799 Difference in value of &amp;ldquo;Max Units&amp;rdquo; Columns Bug TASKS-33798 Images missing in &amp;ldquo;i&amp;rdquo; column Bug TASKS-33795 %W.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 7.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have significantly improved rendering into to pdf format. MPP GantChart TimeScale information is used for rendering specifically. Also, GanttChart rendering resolved for bars that are in footer section. Saving Project Data to multiple PDF files option was supported. Eight bugs were fixed. Please see list of all changes below.
All Changes Issue Type Key Summary Task TASKS-33767 Implement SF links rendering Task TASKS-33762 Implement manual column rendering as Task Mode with indicator Task TASKS-33746 Implement field aliases rendering when saving project views Task TASKS-33770 TASKS-33756 Implement original label format rendering for timescale tiers.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 7.0.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-0-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-7-0-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Major Features We have implemented FilterCriteria and GanttChart data writing to MPP formats. ResourceToColumnTextConverter methods for all resource fields and TaskToColumnTextConverter methods for all task fields have been implemented. GanttChart data writing to 2003/2007 mpp format have been supported. Please see list of all changes below.
All Changes Issue Type Key Summary Task TASKS-33721 Implement FilterCriteria writing to 2003 mpp format Task TASKS-33720 Implement GanttChart data writing to 2010-13 mpp formats Task TASKS-33713 TASKS-33705 Implement default ResourceToColumnTextConverter methods for all resource fields Task TASKS-33710 TASKS-33705 Implement default TaskToColumnTextConverter methods for all task fields Task TASKS-33701 TASKS-33693 Implement GanttChart data writing to 2007 mpp format Task TASKS-33700 TASKS-33693 Implement GanttChart data writing to 2003 mpp format Task TASKS-33697 TASKS-33661 Add Task.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 6.9.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-6-9-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-6-9-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Added Methods The following public methods were added to existing classes:
Name Description SaveOptions.getUseGradientBrush Determines whether to use gradient brush when rendering Gantt chart. SaveOptions.setUseGradientBrush Determines whether to use gradient brush when rendering Gantt chart. Resource.getGUID Returns the generated unique identification code for the resource. ProjectView.getDefaultTaskSheetView Returns project view which includes id, indicators, name, duration, start, finish, predecessors and resource names task columns.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 6.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-6-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-6-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Following changes have been made to the public API in Aspose.Tasks for Java 6.6.0.
The following public methods were added to existing classes:
Name Description ImageSaveOptions.getPixelFormat Gets the format of the color data for each pixel in the image. ImageSaveOptions.setPixelFormat Sets the format of the color data for each pixel in the image. ImageSaveOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 6.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-6-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-6-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Following changes have been made to the public API in Aspose.Tasks for Java 6.5.0.
The following public classes were added: Name Description Filter Represents a filter in Project. This class is a member of the Filters collection. FilterCriteria Defines the criteria that tasks or resources must meet to be displayed in MSP view.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 6.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-6-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-6-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Following changes have been made to the public API in Aspose.Tasks for Java 6.4.0:
The com.aspose.tasks.SaveFileFormat.PrimaveraP6XML field was added.
Used by Project.save method when saving project data to Oracle Primavera P6 xml format.
The com.aspose.tasks.SaveFileFormat.PrimaveraXER field was added.
Used by Project.save method when saving project data to Oracle Primavera P6 XER format.
The com.aspose.tasks.PrimaveraSaveOptions was class added.
It allows to specify additional options when saving project to Oracle Primavera XER format.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 6.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-6-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2014/aspose-tasks-for-java-6-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following changes have been made to the public API that may include addition/removal of new methods/enumerations, deprecation of methods and new features.
UpdateProjectWorkAsComplete(DateTime completeThrough, bool setZeroOrHundredPercentCompleteOnly) method added to Project.
It updates all work as complete through a specified date for the entire project. Set boolean parameter setZeroOrHundredPercentCompleteOnly to false if you want to calculate whether the task is not started, 100% complete or percentage complete value.</description></item></channel></rss>