<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 16.12.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-16-12-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-16-12-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 16.12.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-223 Add support of importing the DXF. New feature THREEDNET-224 Add a metered License key system. New feature THREEDNET-226 Can&amp;rsquo;t extract 3D data from a PDF. Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 16.11.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-16-11-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-16-11-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 16.11.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-219 Directional/spot light in rendering. New feature THREEDNET-218 Add a new interface to allow user to export dependencies to file system. New feature THREEDNET-217 Add support of exporting the text/binary glTF. New feature THREEDNET-215 Add support of importing the binary glTF.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 16.9.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-16-9-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-16-9-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 16.9.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-209 Generate tangent from mesh data. New feature THREEDNET-208 Normal mapping in rendering. New feature THREEDNET-182 Export 3D scene to PDF 1.6. New feature THREEDNET-205 Import 3D scenes from a PDF file. New feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list for any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 2.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-2-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-2-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 2.1.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-196 Separate import options and export options for all 3D file formats. New Feature THREEDNET-194 Export support for Collada. New Feature THREEDNET-198 Allow user to access the low-level rendering API. New Feature THREEDNET-199 Allow node to be excluded during exporting.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 2.0.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-2-0-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-2-0-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 2.0.0.
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-113 Import support for Collada New feature THREEDNET-183 Post-processing effects New feature THREEDNET-191 Use Vector4 to represent UV coordinates. Enhancement THREEDNET-189 Render may crash the application on 64bit platform Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list for any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 1.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-1-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-1-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.3D for .NET 1.7.0
Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-141 Add support of converting STL to an image format. New Feature THREEDNET-169 Render the scene to a texture. New Feature THREEDNET-170 Add support of shadow. New Feature THREEDNET-174 Generate normal data from smoothing group. New Feature THREEDNET-179 Index out of range error occurred on loading a U3D file.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 1.6.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-1-6-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-1-6-1-release-notes/</guid><description>Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-163 PolygonModifier.SplitMesh method throws a stack overflow exception for the scene. Bug THREEDNET-165 3DS to STL ASCII export - can&amp;rsquo;t load an STL ASCII file in 3D Builder. Bug THREEDNET-166 NullReferenceException occurs while loading the FBX file. Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list for any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 1.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-1-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-1-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-146 Convert geometries to per-vertex structure. New Feature THREEDNET-148 Allow user to split mesh per materials. New Feature THREEDNET-150 Create mesh for plane. New Feature THREEDNET-151 Create mesh for Box. New Feature THREEDNET-152 Create mesh for Sphere. New Feature THREEDNET-153 Create mesh for cylinder. New Feature THREEDNET-155 Create mesh for torus.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 1.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-1-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-1-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-140 Preserve vertex element data while triangulating a mesh. Enhancement THREEDNET-139 Allow users to load 3D documents by using Scene class constructors. Enhancement THREEDNET-135 Add support of exporting Universal 3D document. New Feature THREEDNET-127 Add support of importing Universal 3D document. New Feature THREEDNET-143 Add import and export options for Universal 3D formats with test cases.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for .NET 1.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-1-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-3d-for-net-1-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-127 Reading support of Universal 3D format. New Feature THREEDNET-133 Verify Aspose.3D namespaces conform to Microsoft guidelines. Enhancement THREEDNET-130 Fix Aspose license abuse issue possibly caused by Aspose Ventures. Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list for any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>