<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Email for Android via Java 17.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-17-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-17-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Android via Java 17.12 release.
Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILJAVA-34325 Task and contact attachments converted to EML Enhancement EMAILNET-38774 Processing attached encrypted messages Bug EMAILNET-38867 HTML data/links not set properly in contact body Bug EMAILNET-38875 Formatting lost while converting EML to XPS Bug EMAILNET-38877 Attachments in EML file not detected by API Bug EMAILNET-38880 MSG to MHTML removes line spaces Bug EMAILNET-38882 MSG body Text formatting different than the source HTML Bug EMAILJAVA-34324 Converting EML to MSG calendar Item shifts date by local time difference Bug EMAILNET-38876 Outlook raises exception while loading MSG file converted by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Android via Java 17.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.Email for Android via Java 17.11 release.
Major Features Support for raising events while working with sub-folders in a PST Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38855 Item moved event not fired for sub-folders Enhancement EMAILNET-38854 EMLX attachments (MSG/EML) saved as separate emails in MBOX Bug EMAILNET-38856 The (subject, to and from) disappears form converted MailMessage from MapiMessaage Bug EMAILJAVA-34315 The exception occurs while loading MapiMessage from MailMessage.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Android via Java 17.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-17-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-17-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Email for Android via Java 17.10.
Aspose.Email for Android via Java doesn&amp;rsquo;t support emailing protocols i.e. SMTP, POP3, IMAP and Exchange Server (WebDav as well as EWS).
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38823 Attachment name jibbrish on Non-Japanese Windows Bug EMAILNET-38827 MapiMessage.BodyHtml does not return correct value Bug EMAILNET-38828 Attached Word document in Outlook message is corrupted on Save Bug EMAILNET-38829 Multi-octet character split across adjacent encoded-word with UTF8 encoding Bug EMAILNET-38830 Mht empty when converting from msg with SkipInlineImages = true Bug EMAILNET-38831 Duplicated recipients when saving EML as MHTML Bug EMAILNET-38833 Content-disposition filename duplicated Bug EMAILJAVA-34309 Merging PST with sample PST loses Properties of Calendar Bug EMAILNET-38836 Creating message body from HTML includes header information in output Bug EMAILNET-38837 Converting EML to HTML resulting in incorrect HTML Bug EMAILNET-38838 After EML file is opened and re-saved, in output EML file From and Sender are null Bug EMAILJAVA-34307 Calendar added to PST doesn&amp;rsquo;t open in MS Outlook Bug EMAILNET-38842 Wrong attachment name read by API Bug EMAILJAVA-34310 Start and End Date same for full day event Bug EMAILJAVA-34314 Some characters garbled while conversion from EMLX to EML Bug None</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Android via Java 17.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-17-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-17-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Email for Android via Java 17.9.
Aspose.Email for Android via Java doesn&amp;rsquo;t support emailing protocols i.e. SMTP, POP3, IMAP and Exchange Server (WebDav as well as EWS).
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38808 PSTs generated from Aspose much bigger in size Bug EMAILNET-38806 Aspose.Email is unable to process the EML file when it has extra line breaks in the message Bug EMAILNET-38807 EML to EMLx: Resultant message body not visible in Apple Mail Bug EMAILNET-38813 MHTML: Plain text body is lost during loading Bug EMAILNET-38814 MSG with HTML body: Whitespaces between non-latin characters are lost Bug EMAILNET-38815 MSG with RTF body: Non-latin characters are replaced with question marks Bug EMAILJAVA-34304 Difference in From address with On behalf of Bug EMAILNET-38812 Reading multiple events raises exception Bug EMAILNET-38802 ToMapiMessageItem raises exception for these contacts Bug Added APIs Property MapiPropertyStream.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Android via Java 17.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-17-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-17-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Email for Android via Java 17.8.
Aspose.Email for Android via Java doesn&amp;rsquo;t support emailing protocols i.e. SMTP, POP3, IMAP and Exchange Server (WebDav as well as EWS).
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILJAVA-34292 Ability to save images inside a message (as embedded image) as separate files next to html file while converting MSG to HTML Enhancement EMAILNET-38779 EML to MSG results in malformed output Bug EMAILNET-38781 PDF attachment can&amp;rsquo;t be recognized from attachments Bug EMAILNET-38785 Attachments not recognized in MSG file Bug EMAILNET-38794 Timezone property for recurrence Bug EMAILNET-38796 Fetch PST properties PR_LAST_VERB_EXECUTED and PR_CALENDAR_MEETING_STATUS Bug Added APIs Class SaveResourceHandler Field/Enum MapiPropertyTag.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Android via Java 17.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-17-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/androidjava/release-notes/2017/aspose-email-for-android-via-java-17-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Email for Android via Java 17.4.0 has been released. We have renamed the API from Aspose.Email for Android to Aspose.Email for Java.Android and plan to bring it to the same level of functionality as that of Aspose.Email for Java API. This release doesn&amp;rsquo;t include any API changes other than renaming the API. It means that your applications don&amp;rsquo;t need to incorporate any change in implementation while using this latest release.</description></item></channel></rss>