<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/net/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/net/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.PUB for .NET 20.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-pub-for-net-20-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-pub-for-net-20-4-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.PUB for .NET 20.4.
Major Improvement This release of Aspose.PUB for .NET introduces a new feature of supporting vector graphics during conversion from PUB to PDF.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PUBNET-116 Implement vector graphics support New Feature PUBNET-155 Create static shape entities New Feature PUBNET-158 Support vector graphics in the converter New Feature PUBNET-156 Calculation for geometric parameters Enhancement PUBNET-157 Implement command interpreter for vector graphics Enhancement PUBNET-65 PUB to PDF - Images are not present in output PDF file Bug PUBNET-66 PUB to PDF - Text is overlapped in output PDF Bug PUBNET-150 PUB to PDF - Pages are duplicated in output PDF Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PUB for .NET 20.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-pub-for-net-20-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-pub-for-net-20-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PUB for .NET 20.2
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PUBNET-115 Support multi-page documents New Feature PUBNET-145 Add product version information: BuildVersionInfo class New Feature PUBNET-136 Refactor Converter classes Enhancement PUBNET-135 Refactor tests. Improve work with templates Enhancement PUBNET-52 Problem conversion multipage pub document to pdf Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Added APIs Class:Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>