<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 18.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 18.12.
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILJAVA-34454 Create folder hierarchy in PST using string notation Enhancement EMAILNET-39197 Customers solution for Inline Attachment Detection to be investigated Bug EMAILNET-39220 An exception raises while fetching messages using ImapClient Bug EMAILJAVA-34398 Message to MHTML: Numbering is disturbed Bug EMAILNET-39202 Error Reading Distribution List Bug EMAILJAVA-34464 String Format Exception While Loading ICS Bug EMAILNET-39213 VCF to MHT ignores encoding Bug EMAILNET-39215 Newly created MapiContact missing some information is VCF which is present in MSG Bug EMAILNET-39216 System Argument Exception While Loading EMLX Bug EMAILNET-39218 File format detected as Unknown Bug EMAILNET-39208 MapiMessage Attachment reading issue Bug Added APIs Method FolderInfo.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 18.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 18.11.
All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-39189 Specify created and last modified dates in ICS Enhancement EMAILNET-39190 Modification of PRODID in ICS Enhancement EMAILNET-39184 Attachments are missing in the signed email Enhancement EMAILNET-39199 Fail to save attachments for Digitally Signed emails Enhancement EMAILNET-39159 MapiMessage.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 18.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 18.10.
Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-33867 Support for Outlook for Mac Data File (.OLM) using Aspose.Email Feature EMAILNET-39121 Add ability to configure SSL/TLS ecryption type on email client instances Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34425 Implementation of FindPeople Method to find all persona objects that match a specified query string Bug EMAILJAVA-34440 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 18.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 18.9.
Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-39091 Issues with converting meeting requests to MHTML Bug EMAILNET-39081 Multiple issues with MapiContact modification Bug EMAILNET-39094 Date header returns wrong date when read from some MSG files Bug EMAILNET-39096 Loading FileStream in MailMessage is taking a long time Bug EMAILNET-39098 Setting MhtSaveOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 18.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 18.8.
Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38848 Update member in a PST distribution list (DL) and append another DL to an existing Enhancement EMAILNET-39070 EWS:Create contact in Sub-Folder of Contacts Enhancement EMAILNET-39035 Support for adding attachment to MapiCalendarExceptionInfo Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34411 Creating MapiMessage using MapiMessage.fromMailMessage gets stuck Bug EMAILNET-39053 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 18.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Email for Java 18.7.
Major Changes Provision of using http proxy in email clients Unified method for MAPI Items fetching using EWS Option to set Font in Text only emails MailMessage like MHT output for Mapi Task Ignoring error during ImapClient.ListMessagesByPage Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38952 Provision of usage of http proxy in email clients (SMTP, IMAP, POP3) New Feature EMAILNET-39044 EWS: Create unified method for MAPI items fetching Enhancement EMAILNET-39008 Option to set font in text only mails Enhancement EMAILJAVA-34385 Provide MailMessage like MHT output for MapiTask Enhancement EMAILNET-39033 ImapClient.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 18.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.Email for Java18.6.
Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38986 Memory leak in unauthenticated Smtp Client Bug EMAILJAVA-34372 Optional attendee not set in the appointment created by Aspose.Email Bug EMAILNET-38989 The email subject title is incorrectly encoded after adding to the PST file Bug EMAILJAVA-34376 EML to EML: Resultant file contains encoded body in Apple Mail Bug EMAILNET-38993 Task start date/time set to UTC instead of local time Bug EMAILNET-39000 Attachment not detected from attached EML Bug EMAILJAVA-34381 Event time not set properly while adding to PST Bug EMAILNET-39005 Embedded email corrupted when attached email is sent via SMTP Bug EMAILNET-39006 ORGANIZER calendar property is not parsed properly Bug EMAILNET-39015 HTML code when saving attachment to MSG Bug EMAILNET-39031 Data loss when license is used with Pop3 Bug EMAILJAVA-34387 Mht to MSG using MapiMessage corrupts the MSG file Bug EMAILNET-38940 MapiMessage.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 18.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information of Aspose.Email for Java 18.5.
Major Improvements
Support for Auto Discover feature for Exchange Clients Writing Multiple Events to ICS file Return Uri of Sent Mails Setting Calendar body to HTML Provision to abort PST to Exchange Server Operation All Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38891 The implementation of AutoDiscover feature on Exchange Client service New Feature EMAILNET-38789 Write multiple events to ICS file New Feature EMAILNET-38968 Return Uri of Sent Email Enhancement EMAILNET-38982 Calendar body can&amp;rsquo;t be set as HTML supported with Outlook 2016?</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 18.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains information about Aspose.Email for Java 18.4 version.
Major Changes Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38950 EML to MSG loses embedded images and digital signed information Bug EMAILNET-38958 Corrupt MHTML generated from EML Bug EMAILNET-38960 Saving to OFT wtih Embedded Images in HTML loses images Bug EMAILNET-38938 ListMessagesByPage does not fetch new messages once executed in loop Bug EMAILNET-38944 Inline attachment file name not fetched by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 18.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.Email for Java 18.3 version.
Major Changes Support for setting PARTSTAT property for ICS Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38931 Provision to set PARTSTAT property of ICS Enhancement EMAILNET-38879 ImapClient StartMonitoring consumes large processor usage Bug EMAILNET-38906 ImapClient.SelectFolder takes longer than older version of API Bug EMAILNET-38917 HTML formatting lost while setting html description of an appointment Bug EMAILJAVA-34345  Exchange events notification functionality is broken Bug EMAILNET-38923 Property attachment name cannot be set Bug EMAILNET-38924 EML to MHT generates garbled characters Bug EMAILNET-38928 ContentType.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 18.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.Email for Java 18.2 release.
Major Features Support for Metered Licensing Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38918 Metered license implementation New Feature EMAILNET-38870 Calendar organizer is not set in the appointment Bug EMAILJAVA-34328 Property can&amp;rsquo;t be set for MapiCalendar Bug EMAILNET-38885 Error while retrieving MailMessage.HtmlBodyText Bug EMAILNET-38899 Reading voting button response from MSG throws exception Bug EMAILNET-38902 Extra tab character not trimmed while reading MessageId from fetched message Bug EMAILNET-38904 url attachment in ics file is not recognized Bug EMAILNET-38907 Creating MAPI contact for Outlook is not displaying Email address in the search contact list Bug EMAILNET-38908 Bullets replaced with &amp;lsquo;?</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Email for Java 18.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/email/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-email-for-java-18-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.Email for Java 18.1.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category EMAILNET-38610 Create common queue for group and simple operations for SMTP, POP3 and IMAP clients Enhancement EMAILNET-38884 Font changed after setting the html body of email Bug EMAILNET-38885 Error while retrieving MailMessage.HtmlBodyText Bug EMAILNET-38887 Calendar EML resaved loses all data Bug EMAILNET-38889 Inline images become part of attachments collection after removing the signature Bug EMAILNET-38890 Mapi message body html has invalid namespace declarations in html tag Bug EMAILNET-38892 From/To not read properly from EML Bug EMAILNET-38893 Resaving EML to EML loses turns body content into encoding Bug EMAILNET-38894 Issue saving messages using MapiMessage Bug EMAILNET-38895 Adding EML to Mbox creates multiple emails in Mbox Bug EMAILJAVA-34337 While instancing a MailMessage object an exception raises Bug Added APIs Class AllowedConferenceSolutionTypes Class ConferenceProperties Field/Enum AllowedConferenceSolutionTypes.</description></item></channel></rss>