<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2015 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2015/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2015 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2015/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 3.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-imaging-for-java-3-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-imaging-for-java-3-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for Java has been updated to version 3.1 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of cumulative changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging:
New features IMAGING-34897 Support PSD layers loading IMAGING-34862 Add support of basic 3D entities for dxf-&amp;gt;pdf export
Enhancements IMAGING-35028 getHorizontalResolution &amp;amp; getVerticalResolution properties return invalid results
IMAGING-35026 Converting EMF to PNG format is not working properly It haults for 1 hour and do not produce output file</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 3.0.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-imaging-for-java-3-0-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-imaging-for-java-3-0-1-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for Java has been updated to version 3.0.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of cumulative changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging:
New Features IMAGING-34960 Implement the ability to add new draw operations into existing metafile with saving the result IMAGING-34492 Support for DjVu file format IMAGING-33494 Support of changing contrast/brightness setting and image quality of JPEG image
Enhancements IMAGING-33886 java.lang.NullPointerException: while loading a DXF file IMAGING-34964 FrameworkException: Incorrect access to field index, while drawing over EMF IMAGING-34935 java.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 2.9.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-imaging-for-java-2-9-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-imaging-for-java-2-9-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for Java has been updated to version 2.9.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of cumulative changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging:
New Features IMAGING-33778 Compression Schemes for PNG File Format IMAGING-33501 Add support of multiline object during Cad -&amp;gt; Pdf export IMAGING-33155 Jpeg2000 support IMAGING-34404 Auto Correct the Orientation of a JPEG Image Enhancements IMAGING-34667 TiffImageException: Cannot decode strip 0. Details: Cannot perform 2d decoding.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 2.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-imaging-for-java-2-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-imaging-for-java-2-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for Java has been updated to version 2.7.0 and we are pleased to announce it.
The following is a list of cumulative changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging:
New Features IMAGING-34566 Support the Jpeg Compression Method while creating/saving TIFF images IMAGING-34362 Java Check if a license has been properly set IMAGING-34483 Support Jpeg compression for Psd thumbnails IMAGING-34457 Support Autocad 2005 dwg format IMAGING-34454 Support Autocad 2010 dwg format IMAGING-34410 Add transparent and background color support for images IMAGING-34375 Implement Autocad 2013 dwg format IMAGING-34372 Export more than one layouts of CAD drawings to PDF &amp;amp; RasterImages IMAGING-34327 Support for PSD files having CMYK color mode IMAGING-34286 DWG to PDF: Support for text contents in the DWG drawings for rendering to PDF IMAGING-34284 Retrieve the size of DWG drawing Enhancements IMAGING-34740 Conversion process hangs while converting TIFF with Old Style Jpeg Compression to other formats IMAGING-34701 TiffImageException: Cannot decode strip 0.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 2.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-imaging-for-java-2-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2015/aspose-imaging-for-java-2-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for Java has been updated to version 2.6.0 and we are pleased to announce it.
The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging (along with all relevant tickets from corresponding .Net versions):
New Features IMAGING-34526 CAD to Raster Image Conversion IMAGING-34400 Java Resize Images Proportionally Enhancements IMAGING-34570 EmfPen incorrectly renders line width IMAGING-34564 com.aspose.imaging.internal.Exceptions.ArgumentException: Value does not fall within the expected range at Image.rotateFlip for PNG format IMAGING-34439 WmfMetafileImage throws java.</description></item></channel></rss>