<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 23.10 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-10-release-notes/</guid><description>Since Aspose.Imaging.23.10 version EpsImage class interface and behaviour changes. The main points are:
Use EpsImage.EpsType to get the file sub-type since EpsImage class is the main class for EPS file format manipulation. EpsInterchangeImage and EpsBinaryImage classes are removed. Use EpsImage.GetPreviewImage(EpsPreviewFormat) or EpsImage.PreviewImages for retrieving a specific preview image or a full list since EpsLoadOptions.PreviewExportFormat and EpsRasterizationOptions.PreviewToExport properties are removed. Use EpsImage.Save(Stream, ImageOptionsBase) to export an EPS file render since EpsPreviewFormat.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 23.11 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-11-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Implement support text styles italic/underline in CDR format Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-6435 Implement support text styles italic/underline in CDR format Feature IMAGINGNET-6464 Converting the Png to Psd issue Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5980 Failed to open CMX file Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5804 Cannot convert the CMX image to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5452 Emf file not correctly converted to png Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4348 System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 23.12 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-12-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Add RemoveBackground &amp;amp; ChangeBackground API entries for VectorImage Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-5778 Add RemoveBackground &amp;amp; ChangeBackground API entries for VectorImage Feature IMAGINGNET-6799 System.NullReferenceException while exporting a loaded PNG with 64 bpp into PNG with 32 bpp Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6741 System.NullReferenceException when DataStreamSupporter.Save Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6467 Cannot convert the EMF file to PDF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6438 Cannot resize the PNG image Enhancement IMAGINGNET-3017 Emf not converting to SVG in trial mode Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 23.9 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-9-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Implement Remove watermark filter Net5 remove notice - Please note, since 23.10 Aspose.Imaging will not support Net5 configuration.
Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-6285 Implement Remove watermark filter Feature IMAGINGNET-6558 Required palette is missing exception loading BMP Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6466 The GIF file loading issue Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6428 Exception on creating palette of large image Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6410 DICOM load issue Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5809 Error occurs when inherit custom class from Image Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 23.8 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-8-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Implement Magic Wand tool Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-6322 Implement Magic Wand tool Feature IMAGINGNET-6461 Fix bugs with fonts when Svg export Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6426 EPS -&amp;gt; SVG: InvalidOperationException Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6425 Converting EPS -&amp;gt; SVG: IndexOutOfRangeException Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6411 EPS load error Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6376 Memory leak if Image.Dispose() hasn&amp;rsquo;t been called Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6302 Saving of images with dimensions more than 65535 to Jpeg format works incorrect Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6144 Cannot conver the EPS image to SVG format Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6092 Improvement request for multi frame Gif to composite image formats export Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5803 Cannot convert the EPS image to DXF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5708 Cannot conver the EPS image to DXF format Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4907 Can&amp;rsquo;t convert EPS to PNG Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 23.7 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-7-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Add alpha blending feature for RasterImage Net2.0, Net3.5,Net3.5 client profile remove notice - Please note, since 23.7 Aspose.Imaging does not support Net2.0, Net3.5, Net3.5 client profile configurations.
Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-6017 Add alpha blending feature for RasterImage Feature IMAGINGNET-6459 UnIfy naming conventions Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6421 EMF export error Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6369 CCITT G3 1D decoder don&amp;rsquo;t work properly Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6033 Synchronize use of Pages and format specific collections for multi page images Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Field/Enum Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 23.6 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-6-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Since 23.6 release Aspose.Imaging for .NET supports Aspose.Drawing for .NET7 configuration as default graphics engine. If you work with Aspose.Imaging in Non-Windows environment you can view how to work with Aspose.Imaging .NET Core dlls in Non-Windows Environment guide.
Net2.0, Net3.5,Net3.5 client profile remove notice - Please note, in the nearest releases Net2.0, Net3.5, Net3.5 client profile configurations will not be supported. Aspose.Imaging.FileFormat.Undefined renaming notice - Please note, in the next Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 23.5 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-5-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Support of tiled Tiff writing Add NET7 configuration to Aspose.Imaging Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-5986 Support of tiled Tiff writing Feature IMAGINGNET-6191 WMF: Incorrect orientation of wmf rendering Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6181 SVG to PDF: Arrows not rendered correctly Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6102 Support of TIFF with Cmyk Alpha color mode Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6101 wk: Converting PNG to TIFF using CMYK colorspace and preserving transparency Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5802 Cannot convert the CDR image to JPG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4605 &amp;ldquo;Bit depth of 8 bits are supported for RGBA images.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 23.4 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-4-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Support of image raw data rendering from EPS Remove usings of unsafe BinaryFormatter and replace it with a better alternative. Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-6050 Support of image raw data rendering from EPS Feature IMAGINGNET-4886 Remove usings of unsafe BinaryFormatter and replace it with a better alternative. Feature IMAGINGNET-6100 DICOM loading issue under ARM64 mode Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6096 The EMF image on export to PNG has bottom-right shifted content Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6088 WMF loading issue Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6034 Issue with PNG images converted from EPS Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6001 Incorrect text offsets in Emf formulas rasterization Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5954 Cdr to png misses lines Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5862 Cannot convert the EPS image to EMF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5828 Cannot access a disposed object after conversion of ICO image Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5580 Cannot load EPS image Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5349 Can&amp;rsquo;t convert CMX to JPG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4928 Can&amp;rsquo;t convert EPS to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4376 Exception on converting CDR to PNG Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 23.3 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-3-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Add support of BigTiff Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-4684 Add support of BigTiff Feature IMAGINGNET-6077 Resultant PNG cannot be opened by Photoshop Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6064 Two conversion issues (cdr to wmf, wmf to tiff) Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6023 Cannot access a closed file when converting EMZ on Linux Enhancement IMAGINGNET-5875 Tiff image is corrupted when saved Enhancement IMAGINGNET-4986 WmfImage.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 23.2 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-imaging-for-net-23-2-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Develop plug-in licensing - Added support of Plugin licenses that allow you to get access to only specific Aspose.Imaging features and functions for .NET Standard 2.0 and higher configurations. You may order available plug-in licenses here. Also more description for available plugins available in readme of msi/nuget packages of Aspose.Imaging. Keep transparency, when indexing Png images Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-5736 Develop plug-in licensing Feature IMAGINGNET-4522 Keep transparency, when indexing Png images Feature IMAGINGNET-6035 ICO to PDF export bug Enhancement IMAGINGNET-6018 RasterImage.</description></item></channel></rss>