<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 16.12.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-12-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-12-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 16.12.0
Major Features There are 73 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Save to image formats can be fine-tuned by passing RenderingHints (TextRenderingHint, InterpolationMode etc.) to ImageSaveOptions.GraphicsQualityOptions Support of the &amp;ldquo;people&amp;rdquo; part (Word 2013 feature) StructuredDocumentTag extensions supported (Word 2013 feature) REVNUM, INFO fields supported Improved handling of hanging punctuation and hyphens in complex script content Improved handling of &amp;ldquo;Automatically adjust space between Asian text and numbers&amp;rdquo; compatibility option Improved paragraph alignment when text contains hidden content Improved reflow of vertically merged cells for complex table grid layout Implemented combining adjacent tables on document loading Path gradient fill support while rendering SVG implemented Leader lines rendering for all DrawingML Chart types (not only for pie-charts) implemented Styles are now properly applied for DrawingML Charts while rendering Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-13203 Incorrect cell width causes contents to wrap to the next line Bug WORDSNET-13350 Incorrect image size in AW pdf output Bug WORDSNET-13355 Some images not displayed correctly when converting from docx to pdf Bug WORDSNET-13398 Docx to Pdf conversion issue with Shape (image) rendering Bug WORDSNET-13413 Row deletion is not read properly.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 16.11.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-11-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-11-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 16.11.0
Major Features There are 74 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
FixedPageSaveOptions.OptimizeOutput option is implemented for all fixed page formats, improving the size of output documents. Output PDF now contains a valid document ID despite the compliancy settings (with or without PDF/A compliancy) Supporting MS Word 2013 features from various DOCX extensions specs.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 16.10.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-10-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-10-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 16.10.0
Major Features There are 109 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added feature to compare document as MS Word does. Added feature to get OOXML compliance version as determined from the loaded document content. Font fallback while rendering fonts of Myanmar Unicode range improved. DrawingML text effects rendering performance slightly improved. DrawingML text box rendering effects added.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 16.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 16.8.0
Major Features There are 68 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Huge performance optimization of UpdateFields() and ExecuteWithRegions(). Performance optimization of Fonts catch. Support loading of Mobi (Mobipocket) documents (MOBI is an eBook format used by the MobiPocket and Amazon Kindle Readers). Shapes with the translucent fill rendering implemented in PDF and other fixed-page formats.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 16.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 16.7.0
Major Features There are 132 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
A document page can now be saved in GIF format using SaveFormat.Gif in ImageSaveOptions. Font substitution rules improved. Now embedded font is used for substitution if available. Multilevel strings rendering in DrawingML Chart axis labels improved. OfficeMath objects now can be exported (optional) to HTML,MHTML or EPUB as mathml elements.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 16.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 16.6.0
Major Features There are 113 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Fast extraction from DOC format via PlainTextDocument class is faster by a factor of ten (at a cost). Saving DOCX as ISO 29500 Strict OOXML format is available now. Added support for outer document insertion to LINQ Reporting Engine. Added feature to insert empty values in chart series.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 16.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 16.5.0
Major Features There are 72 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved reflow performance for large paragraphs. Added explicit support of multiple data sources to LINQ Reporting Engine. SVG output with IE compatibility improved. Improved widow/orphan handling for tables. Improved asian text line breaking. Improved font metrics calculation for substituted fonts. Implemented support for SuppressEndnotes option.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 16.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 16.4.0
Major Features There are 94 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved the speed of cold document creation and loading. Automatic detection of encoding of a text file. Import MathML from HTML documents. Improved positioning of pictures inside tables. PDF A1b compliancy improved. DML Charts effects support improved. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10153 List numbers are incorrect after conversion from Doc to Pdf Bug WORDSNET-10321 Docx to Pdf conversion issue with chart&amp;rsquo;s border Bug WORDSNET-10374 Chart 3D bubbles have incorrect fill in output document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 16.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 16.3.0
Major Features There are 87 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Further improvements to the speed and public API for plain text extraction. Render OfficeMath formulas to images separately from the document. Shape and OfficeMath can now be saved to SVG. Support for RC4 encryption. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10709 /asian typography detection/ Chinese wraps to the next line when English and Chinese characters combined in one paragraph Bug WORDSNET-10710 /asian typography detection/ A line starts with a punctuation mark in PDF Bug WORDSNET-12471 Shape.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 16.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 16.2.0
Major Features There are 94 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Fast extraction of plain text from flow-format documents is supported PageSavingCallback was introduced for all fixed-page based save formats Ability to determine if a run or a paragraph has format changes Font substitution while rendering fixed-page formats improved to mimic MS Word Axis logarithmic scale for DML charts rendering implemented WordArt shapes fit to Bezier curves rendering implemented: ArchUp(Curve), ArchDown(Curve), Circle(Curve) DrawingML shapes with guides are now scaled correctly DML charts rendering improved Key Summary Category WORDSNET-11466 Nonbreaking spaces gets converted to squares when saving as pdf Bug WORDSNET-11905 RTF to Docx conversion issue with TOC field Bug WORDSNET-12127 /Axis logarithmic scale/Docx to Pdf conversion issue with rendering charts Bug WORDSNET-12170 digital signature is lost after conversion from Docx to Pdf Bug WORDSNET-12446 Docx to Pdf conversion issue: Creating watermark using Acrobat 9 Pro Bug WORDSNET-12488 RTF-&amp;gt;Html-&amp;gt;RTF removes the empty spaces Bug WORDSNET-12736 An empty &amp;lt;TR&amp;gt; added at the end of Table in HTML Bug WORDSNET-12751 Vertical spacing between Paragraphs is increased in PDF Bug WORDSNET-12758 Hyperlink, bold and font size returned incorrectly Bug WORDSNET-12768 Mht to png/pdf : inline image not displayed Bug WORDSNET-12776 Cell background containing logo becomes white in rendered PDF Bug WORDSNET-12814 Invalid CSS class names are exported to HTML Bug WORDSNET-12823 Docx to PNG conversion issue with textbox position Bug WORDSNET-12832 Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 16.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-words-for-net-16-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 16.1.0
Aspose.Words for .NET 16.1 Release Notes Major Features There are 133 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented auto-fit table grid calculation for several classes of tables EMF+ images now can be rendered without the GDI+  Comments rendering improved Word 6.0 binary DOC files are supported now Added public methods for inserting signature lines Added ability to configure document hyphenation options Added capability to get mail merge regions hierarchy Added more public classes and methods to work with fields in a document Font sources can now be specified for each document instance Implemented line counting (Document.</description></item></channel></rss>