<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.12.
Major Features Support namespaces for KML format Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-329 Support namespaces for KML format Improvement GISNET-594 Fix exception when checking POLYGONS intersects Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.11.
Major Features Add Records in the existing tables for Sql Server and Postgis Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-494 Append features to existing tables New Feature GISNET-588 Support &amp;lsquo;Count&amp;rsquo; in Created Layer for Databases Improvement Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.10.
Major Features Add Features in Existing Shapefile Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-577 Add Features in Existing Shapefile New Feature GISNET-581 Send credits using metered licensing Improvement GISNET-556 Write color in format &amp;ldquo;aabbggrr&amp;rdquo; in KML styles Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.09 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-09-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-09-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.09.
Major Features Add ClusterMarker symbolizer Support Metered Licensing Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-522 Add ClusterMarker symbolizer New Feature GISNET-568 Support Metered Licensing New Feature GISNET-565 Can&amp;rsquo;t draw Xyz Tile Bug GISNET-563 Can&amp;rsquo;t draw raster when Spatial Reference is missed Bug GISNET-561 Can&amp;rsquo;t read spatial reference in raster Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.08 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-08-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-08-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.08.
Major Features Client for XYZ tile servers Add single-band gray colorizer Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-548 Client for XYZ tile servers New Feature GISNET-557 Draw XYZ Tiles on Map New Feature GISNET-560 Add single-band gray colorizer New Feature GISNET-559 Add Width\Height in Raster Map Layer Improvement GISNET-554 Exception when colorizer get multi-band raster Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.07 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-07-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-07-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.07.
Major Features Warp\reproject raster layers Draw raster layers on a map Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-529 Warp\reproject raster layers New Feature GISNET-545 Draw raster layers on a map New Feature Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.06 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-06-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-06-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.06.
Major Features Udate Epsg Dataset. Update security. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-547 Udate Epsg Dataset Improvement GISNET-543, 506 Update security Improvement GISNET-541 Exception when Geometry.Null returns Dimension Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes none</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.05 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-05-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-05-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.05.
Major Features Export data to MapInfo(TAB) format. Fields preprocessing during exporting. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-527 Export data to MapInfo(TAB) format Feature GISNET-528 Add fields preprocessing during exporting Improvement GISNET-536 Can&amp;rsquo;t read long line correctly in MapInfo TAB Bug GISNET-536 Can&amp;rsquo;t read null values in MapInfo TAB Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been changeed:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.04 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-04-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-04-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.04.
Major Features Raster features:
Read EsriASCII, GeoTIFF and TIFF. Read georeference and raster sizes. Read values of numeric types (Bit, SByte, Byte, Short, UShort, Integer, UInteger, Long, Float, Double). Read raw bits for unknown data types. Read raster data by blocks. Support multy и single bands. Summary statistics (count, sum, mean, min and max) Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-520 Read GeoTIFF raster format Feature GISNET-511 Read ESRI ASCII raster format Feature GISNET-526 Add Raster Summary Statistics Improvement Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.03 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-03-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-03-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.03.
Major Features Add Easier Feature Attribute Value Access. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-514 Add Easier Feature Attribute Value Access Improvement GISNET-513 Truncated Decimals in WKT Strings Improvement GISNET-517 Can&amp;rsquo;t convert GML to SHP File Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.02 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-02-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-02-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.02.
Major Features Export style properties to KML. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-491 Export style properties to KML New Feature GISNET-510 Read BBOX members from GeoJSON Improvement GISNET-507 Generate BBOX members in created GeoJSON Improvement Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Following members have been added:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.01 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-01-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/gis/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-gis-for-net-20-01-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.GIS for .NET 20.01.
Major Features Write geospatial data to SQL Server database. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category GISNET-499 Write geospatail data to SQL Server New Feature GISNET-502 Add options of layer creation in database Improvement GISNET-504 Invalid Geometry Error when JSON to KML conversion Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes None.</description></item></channel></rss>