<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.12.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-11060 Fix performance degradation when saving the specific project to XML Enhancement TASKSNET-11048 Add validation which checks that calendar names are unique Enhancement TASKSNET-4877 Fix costs and durations rounding when reading a project from MPP and XML. Enhancement TASKSNET-11037 Fix ArgumentOutOfRangeException when trying to get Task.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.11.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-11004 Add writing of Project.Calendar.Guid to MPP Enhancement TASKSNET-10629 Add a possibility to calculate assignment&amp;rsquo;s work for the specified date time interval Enhancement TASKSNET-10626 Add read-only task Status column Enhancement TASKSNET-4829 Initialize CsvOptions.View with default view Enhancement TASKSJAVA-2130 MPP to PDF: Null Pointer exception Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public methods were added: Description com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.10.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-11003 Add validation which ensures that Project.Calendar points to calendar belonging to Project.Calendars collection Enhancement TASKSNET-11002 Add public API to allow passing of encoding when reading Primavera XER files Enhancement TASKSNET-10971 Modify hierarchy of Save Options to remove members of SaveOptions not applicable to certain formats Enhancement TASKSNET-10815 Add reading of baseline projects for Primavera XML format Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-9-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.9.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10984 Add duplicated Task Uids validation check Enhancement TASKSNET-10970 Fix the resource unit cannot be automatically 100% when adding resources to the exported mpp file Bug TASKSNET-10982 Fix calculation of early and late dates when task has constraints Bug TASKSJAVA-2080 MPP vs XML export differences Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.8.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10890 Add an API allowing to specify user&amp;rsquo;s font folder when system font folders cannot be accessed by the application Enhancement TASKSNET-4895 Optimize memory footprint of large projects Enhancement Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.7.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10948 Add reading of incomplete baselines Enhancement TASKSNET-10947 Set WeekDay.DayWorking = true when working times is added Enhancement TASKSNET-10933 Add checks before saving to MPP which verify that UniqueId is not greater than max allowed UniqueIds Enhancement TASKSNET-10887 Add reading of Unit of Measure&amp;rsquo;s abbrevation from Primavera XER and P6XML formats to Resource.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.6.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10914 Fix reading of ResourceAssignment.ActualCost from XER format: OvertimeCost should be added Bug TASKSNET-10913 Fix writing of base calendars to MPP15+ formats Bug TASKSNET-10912 Fix escaping of values when exporting project to CSV format Bug TASKSNET-10909 Fix incorrect rendering of timescale when units are set to TimescaleUnit.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.5.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10892 Add Prj.AutoCalculateAssignmentCosts property to allow control of auto calculation of Asn.RemainingCost and Asn.Cost Enhancement TASKSNET-10893 Fix &amp;lsquo;TimeSpan overflowed because the duration is too long&amp;rsquo; exception when reading project with cost resource from XER format Bug TASKSNET-10891 Fix reading of Tsk.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.4.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10742 Replace usages of System.Drawing.StringAlignment with Aspose.Tasks.Visualization.StringAlignment Enhancement TASKSJAVA-1939 Property UseProjectDefaultFont or DefaultFontName does not work Bug TASKSNET-10831 Fix NullReferenceException when accessing AssignmentBaseline.TimephasedData for new Assignment&amp;rsquo;s baseline Bug TASKSNET-10825 Fix task baseline 1-10 properties are not shown when opening a resulting MPP 2007 file using MS Project Bug TASKSNET-10824 Fix baselines&amp;rsquo;s FixedCost is not shown when output MPP file is opened using MS Project Bug TASKSNET-10823 Fix OverflowException when opening the specific file Bug TASKSJAVA-1913 Reading resource usage is not imported properly Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.3.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10802 Add reading and writing of assignment&amp;rsquo;s hyperlink from / to MPP format Enhancement TASKSNET-10794 Add enum-typed DurationType, ActivityType and PercentCompletetype properties to PrimaveraTaskProperties Enhancement TASKSNET-10788 Add &amp;ldquo;LoadProject&amp;rdquo; method to PrimaveraXmlReader and PrimaveraXerReader Enhancement TASKSNET-10784 Add initialization of View data in projects read from non-MPP format Enhancement TASKSNET-10771 Add reading of &amp;lsquo;Calendar for Scheduling Relationship Lag&amp;rsquo; from Primavera XML and XER formats Enhancement TASKSNET-10768 Add reading of ActualExpenseCost, RemainingExpenseCost, ActualLaborCost, ActualMaterialCost, ActualNonlaborCost, ActualTotalCost for projects read from XER of Primavera P6XML formats Enhancement TASKSNET-4180 Implement consistent API for Task, Resource, Assignment notes Enhancement TASKSNET-10804 Fix reading and writing of Leveling Delay field from \ to MPP format Bug TASKSNET-10796 Fix writing of Task.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.2.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSJAVA-1873 Method setEndDate does not work when rendering to single page is disabled Enhancement TASKSJAVA-1253 Primavera software not Read percentage complete as 100% Bug TASKSNET-10773 Fix persistence of Assignment&amp;rsquo;s guid when reading and writing a project from\to XER and P6XML formats.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-tasks-for-java-23-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 23.1.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10758 Add an API to access values of Labor Units for projects read from Primavera formats Enhancement TASKSNET-10756 Fix reading of task priority column for MPX files where Priority column was saved using enum values. Enhancement TASKSNET-10755 Add an API to access fractional number values of Physical Percent Complete and PercentComplete for projects read from Primavera formats.</description></item></channel></rss>