<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 23.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 23.12.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1458 Allow optimize mesh to remove duplicated control points. New Feature THREEDNET-1468 Allow specify the axis system when export model to STL/OBJ/PLY New Feature THREEDNET-222 Add support of complex boolean operations on meshes New Feature THREEDNET-1441 Allow Boolean operation can work on ordinal mesh Improvement THREEDNET-1451 OBJ exporting incorrect textures.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 23.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 23.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1432 Add support for USDA file Task THREEDNET-1435 SkiaSharp integration renders to incorrect image Support API Changes Added members to class com.aspose.threed.FileFormat: /** * Universal Scene Description in ASCII format. */ public static final FileFormat USDA; Since Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 23.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 23.10.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1424 Integrate the manifold and boolean feature into Aspose.3D Task THREEDNET-1431 Show a message to stdout when trial exception suppressed. Task THREEDNET-1435 Issues updating to latest version because of removed dependency to System.Drawing Support API Changes Added members to class com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 23.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 23.9.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1430 Prepare migration to System.Numerics Task THREEDAPP-2055 Watermark may not working for some meshes Bug fixing THREEDAPP-2065 Conversion issue Bug fixing THREEDAPP-2066 Bump texture lost when fbx is converted to obj Bug fixing THREEDNET-1429 Mesh triangulation may fail sometimes Bug fixing API Changes Added members to class com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 23.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 23.8.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1416 Use new algorithm to triangulate super complex polygons in .net product Improvement Aspose.3D for Java 23.8 is mainly a bug fixing version without any API changes.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 23.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 23.7.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1410 Watermark: InvalidDataException: Found invalid data while decoding Bug fixing THREEDNET-919 Create a FBX file from double byte character set DXF content Bug fixing THREEDNET-1235 convert from dwg file to gltf file? Bug fixing THREEDNET-1078 Mesh cannot be decoded by official draco when encoded as draco.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 23.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 23.6.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-588 IFC support request New Feature THREEDNET-1395 CascadiaCode font is not supported Bug fixing THREEDNET-1397 IFC 2x3 Transformation was incorrect Bug fixing THREEDNET-1403 Mesh save to STL and reload from it will lose polygons Bug fixing Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 23.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 23.5.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1359 Exporting to OBJ - Image/texture files not copied to OBJ directory Task THREEDNET-1361 Decouple the dependency of System.Drawing Task THREEDNET-1360 Allow export PBR material definition and normal mapping in OBJ exporter Improvement THREEDNET-1357 Missing material and texture when loading obj file Bug fixing THREEDNET-1358 When importing an obj file, ControlPoints encountered an error reading data and read it as normal vector data Bug fixing API changes Added class com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 23.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 23.4.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1359 Exporting to OBJ - Image/texture files not copied to OBJ directory Task THREEDNET-1361 Decouple the dependency of System.Drawing Task THREEDNET-1360 Allow export PBR material definition and normal mapping in OBJ exporter Improvement THREEDNET-1357 Missing material and texture when loading obj file Bug fixing THREEDNET-1358 When importing an obj file, ControlPoints encountered an error reading data and read it as normal vector data Bug fixing API changes Since 23.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 23.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 23.3.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1340 Save scene from fbx to usd may throw exception Bug fixing THREEDNET-1341 App bug - Save file to html may throw ArgumentNullException Bug fixing THREEDNET-1343 Meta data with null label saved to FBX file will fail Bug fixing THREEDNET-1350 Property with short int type is not supported in FBX exporter Bug fixing THREEDNET-1352 Unsupported maya section VEC# in binary maya file Bug fixing THREEDNET-1353 Unsupported maya section SBDS in binary maya file Bug fixing THREEDNET-1354 Unknown UV set in binary maya file format Bug fixing THREEDNET-1355 NullReferenceException in loading a GLB file Bug fixing THREEDNET-1356 Unsupported maya command: instanceable Bug fixing API changes In the 23.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 23.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 23.2.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1329 Allow import MDL-based material from USD format. Improvement THREEDNET-1288 USD load incorrect Bug fixing THREEDNET-1297 Save glTF from ASCII to binary Bug fixing THREEDNET-1325 All OBJ vertices incorrectly equal (0,0,0) (E notation Bug?) Bug fixing THREEDNET-1328 Encoded draco file have incorrect shapes.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 23.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2023/aspose-3d-for-java-23-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 23.1.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1177 Aspose.3D 22.5: Exception when trying to load Gltf file Bug fixing THREEDNET-1178 Aspose.3D 22.5: Exception when trying to load X file Bug fixing THREEDNET-1179 Aspose.3D 22.5: Exception when trying to load Vrml file Bug fixing THREEDNET-1180 Aspose.3D 22.</description></item></channel></rss>