<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.12.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-44451 Apply data Sorting for data field with respect to Row field in PivotTable - Mimic results as per user&amp;rsquo;s expected file New Feature CELLSNETCORE-45 Load data from Datasource with the option to skip some character like Apostrophe New Feature CELLSNET-47018 Calculating some combo charts can throw an exception Enhancement CELLSNET-47016 Wrap text is different in the latest version of Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.11.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-44956 Support to hide selected ranges and sort the displayed results of Pivot Table New Feature CELLSNET-46852 Support reading and writing table whose data source is a query table in the XLS file. New Feature CELLSNET-46967 Support to get indent size in unit of pixels New Feature CELLSNET-46973 Excel formula not working in generated XLS file Enhancement CELLSNET-46981 Support to read/write with memory stream for Workbook.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.10.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46926 PageSavingCallback when saving to TIFF New Feature CELLSNET-46927 IMailMergeDataSource equivalent for Cells New Feature CELLSNET-46903 Changing style on ContentTypeProperties Enhancement CELLSNET-46954 Raise Exception similar to Excel instead of hanging program Performance CELLSNET-46896 Funnel graph disappears Bug CELLSNET-46934 Delay and memory usage when converting to PDF file format  Bug CELLSNET-43416 Sorting of the Pivot Field is changed after rendering the spreadsheet to PDF Bug CELLSNET-44686 Pivot sorting not applied when extracting Chart Bug CELLSNET-46793 An issue with pivot tables Bug CELLSNET-46882 Issue when grouping pivot table by date and saving as PDF Bug CELLSNET-46935 Wrap text not rendered in HTML Bug CELLSNET-46940 Table borders are not correctly rendered in HTML Bug CELLSNET-46939 Support for TEXTJOIN() function Bug CELLSNET-46237 Cell Format does not stick Bug CELLSNET-46245 Cut/Paste does not copy the name of Cell to the new location in GridDesktop Bug CELLSNET-46910 List data validations (dropdowns) are not working with Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.9.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46864 Support reading and rendering Control of ODS files New Feature CELLSNET-46877 Add SheetRender.ToPrinter(PrinterSettings PrinterSettings) overload to the APIs New Feature CELLSNET-46907 Configure ZIP compression level for XLSX/XLSB New Feature CELLSNET-46890 Results of integer division should not be assigned to floating-point variables Bug CELLSNET-46883 PivotTables do not retain multiple select options after processing smart markers Bug CELLSNET-46874 Values not derived from formula and require pressing F2 to get values in cells Bug CELLSNET-46904 Hyperlinks are lost when importing data from DataTable Bug CELLSNET-46875 Contents overflow from the page during PDF conversion Bug CELLSNET-46865 An object is changed after open and save Bug CELLSNET-46866 Setting the font and font size of Drawing.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.8.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46823 Support Elliptic Curve Digital Signature Algorithm (ECDSA) for P-384 and P-521 New Feature CELLSNET-46813 Support for extracting OLE Embedded .MOL file New Feature CELLSNET-46822 Detecting the difference between internal and external hyperlinks New Feature CELLSNET-42334 Aspose.Cells.GridWeb compatibility with MVC Enhancement CELLSNET-46804 Improve performance for calculating large matrix with double values Performance CELLSNET-46856 The document fails to save when saved more than 10 times Performance CELLSNET-46827 Content missing in XLSX to ODS conversion Bug CELLSNET-46833 Shapes are distorted in Excel to PDF conversion Bug CELLSNET-46835 Drawing shapes are not rendered properly in Excel to PDF rendering Bug CELLSNET-46848 Issue with Arabic text in Excel to PDF rendering Bug CELLSNET-44973 Unable to set the fill color of the Pivot Table cells Bug CELLSNET-46818 Not all styles are exported when saving to HTML Bug CELLSNET-46824 Pivot table corrupted after pivot source data updated Bug CELLSNET-46820 Smart marker grouping data issues Bug CELLSNET-46840 Issue with Workbook.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.7.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-42029 Support for adding some sort of Callback event/mechanism that notifies you the progress of the conversion  New Feature CELLSNET-46791 Support more views but not custom view New Feature CELLSNET-46808 Support reading table single cells of XLS file. New Feature CELLSNET-46775 The grouped shape&amp;rsquo;s width cannot be set Enhancement CELLSNET-46785 The abbreviation case is different for the very same words: HtmlSaveOptions and HTMLLoadOptions, JsonLayoutOptions and JSONUtility, ODSLoadOptions and OdsSaveOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.6.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-41277 Comments in HTML export of XLS/XLSX files New Feature CELLSNET-45194 Support Drawing of Slicer while rendering to PDF New Feature CELLSNET-46742 Add OpenDocument Flat XML Spreadsheet (.fods) file format support New Feature CELLSNET-46744 Add StarOffice Calc Spreadsheet (.sxc) file format support New Feature CELLSNET-46714 Embedded OOXML file as a package for XLSX.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.5.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46703 The new Japanese calendar is not displayed correctly New Feature CELLSNET-46693 Support background of ODS New Feature CELLSNET-46695 Set background of ODS file New Feature CELLSNET-46706 Invalid number order when converting Arabic font to PDF. Enhancement CELLSNET-46692 Control all external data with IStreamProvider interface Enhancement CELLSNET-46711 ImportCustomObjects to merged area breaks merge Enhancement CELLSNET-46713 The method &amp;ldquo;String.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.4.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46619 Support saving Markdown format document New Feature CELLSNET-46124 Support adding WebExtension shape New Feature CELLSNET-46553 Support importing JSON files New Feature CELLSNET-46653 Support adding WebExtension task pane New Feature CELLSNET-46656 Support threaded comments New Feature CELLSNET-46657 Support cutting and pasting cells New Feature CELLSNET-46686 Support taking white space (char code 20) as the number group separator for the French language Enhancement CELLSNET-46649 Large PDF generated as compared to online tool iLovePDF Enhancement CELLSNET-46093 Charts do not honor Page Setup Black and White Enhancement CELLSNET-46677 Exporting Excel to PDF does not render Arabic texts precisely in charts Enhancement CELLSNET-46639 Support vertical page break for ODS file.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.3.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46598 Add Name.GetReferredAreas (Boolean recalculate) method to give richer data (including external references and linked data) New Feature CELLSNET-46580 Incorrect rendering of rotated shapes in Shape to image conversion Bug CELLSNET-46587 Pivot Table breaks when deleting rows and columns Bug CELLSNET-46608 Pivot table filters are cleared after load and save Bug CELLSNET-46623 Issues in embedded shared file URLs while converting Excel file to HTML Bug CELLSNET-46590 Error in a cell that calls a macro after the file is processed by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.2.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46582 Support Range.Hyperlinks property New Feature CELLSNET-46534 Int32 can be small for Cells.count attribute Enhancement CELLSNET-46552 Differentiate encrypted XLSX from encrypted PPTX and encrypted DOCX Enhancement CELLSNET-46568 Setting Box Whisker chart style Enhancement CELLSNET-46573 Replace invalid characters with suitable symbols like brackets Enhancement CELLSNET-46581 Open/save removes table alternative text Enhancement CELLSNET-46584 Performance Issue with Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-cells-for-net-19-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 19.1.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-46429 Add PivotTable with Show Report Filter Pages option New Feature CELLSNET-46014 Support handling overflowing cell content while saving as PDF and image New Feature CELLSNET-46490 Support Excel95/5.0 XLS files New Feature CELLSNET-46500 Sort by cell background color New Feature CELLSNET-46544 Detect if generated MHT file is a worksheet or not New Feature CELLSNET-46538 When XLSX is saved as PDF or TIFF, the bottom of the text is missing Bug CELLSNET-46509 R1C1 formulas are read incorrectly for certain cells Bug CELLSNET-46513 Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>