<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2010 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2010 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 9.4.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-9-4-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-9-4-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 9.4.1&amp;rsquo; INTERIM BUILD
This build is to address an issue when printing documents or rendering to graphics. Only documents that use Souvienne fonts are affected, the output appears misplaced. This build is to address a particular issue for a priority customer. If you don&amp;rsquo;t have this problem, don&amp;rsquo;t use this interim build.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 9.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-9-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-9-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 9.4.0
All DrawingML objects (shapes, pictures, charts, diagrams) are fully preserved during DOCX open/save operations. Structured Document Tags (content controls) are now fully preserved during DOCX open/save operations. Improvements to IF field update in headers/footers and other tricky scenarios. OpenType fonts with PostScript outlines are supported when rendering to PDF and XPS. More code examples added to the Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 9.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-9-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-9-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 9.3.0
Endnotes are rendered to PDF and XPS. References to API members are hyperlinked in all of the documentation. Breaking change: Legacy conversion to PDF method via Aspose.Pdf.xml has been removed. 80+ improvements and fixes. Here is the complete list of fixes and new features.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 9.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-9-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-9-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 9.2.0
Performance improvements to the layout and rendering engine. No longer relying on GDI+ for text measurements means better server-side conversion to PDF. Support for condensed and expanded text when rendering. Improvements to field update of TOC, REF, PAGEREF, NOTEREF, INCLUDETEXT fields. Ability to easily distinguish templates, documents with digital signatures or encryption before loading them. Ability to access generated list labels and numbers on paragraphs.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 9.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-9-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-9-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 9.1.0
New article and a sample project about using Nested Mail Merge. Support for Custom XML Data Storage and Properties in OOXML documents. Support for .NET 3.5 and 4.0 Client Profile. Improvements to footnotes layout and rendering. You will be happy with about 100 other fixes and improvements. Here is the complete list of fixes and new features.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 9.0.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-9-0-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-9-0-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 9.0.0
The important improvements are:
Table of Contents (TOC) fields are now updated/rebuilt. Load and save Word 2010 OOXML documents (ISO 29500 Transitional) is supported. Embedded OOXML packages are supported. TrueType fonts are subsetted and embedded into output EPUB. Footnotes are partially supported when rendering/saving to PDF. It is my big pleasure to announce Aspose.Words can finally build a complete and up-to-date table of contents in Microsoft Word documents.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 8.2.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-8-2-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-8-2-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 8.2.1
This is a maintenance release with a number of fixes that many customers will find useful.
The most important changes are:
VBA document events (On Open, On New and all others) are fully preserved (they were always lost). VBA digital signature is always preserved (it was lost under some circumstances in DOC). Names of VBA macros are preserved in the Macros Window (they were sometimes lost).</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 8.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-8-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-for-net-8-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 8.2.0
The important changes are:
Comment ranges are now supported. Assemblies with and without the Authenticode signature are supplied. About 50 other fixes and improvements. A comment in a Word document can be anchored to a position or to a range of text. Earlier versions of Aspose.Words supported comments anchoring to a position of text only. If a comment was anchored to a range of text (and that is the most common scenario), Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words 8.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-8-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2010/aspose-words-8-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words 8.1.0
Many document layout and rendering to PDF and XPS improvements. Important improvements to the field update engine. About 80 other fixes. In this release we have managed to address some of the hot issues and improve the accuracy of Word documents to PDF and XPS conversion.
Some of the layout and rendering improvements are:
Added PdfOptions.IsPreserveFormFields that controls whether to export Word document form fields as PDF form fields or as text.</description></item></channel></rss>