<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 21.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 21.12.
Major Features There are 83 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented ability to get OOXML of content control. Implemented loading previously saved font search cache to speed up the font cache initialization process upon rendering. Added recognition of non-standard footnotes in PDF documents during the import workflow. Implemented support for &amp;lsquo;Allow Latin text to wrap in the middle of a word&amp;rsquo; feature Implemented workaround for SkiaSharp bug, which causes application crash on Linux when new SkiaSharp 2.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 21.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 21.11.
Major Features There are 67 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented a ProgressCallback to be able to show the document loading progress. New UseAttachments option has been implemented to display the attachments panel in the output PDF documents. Added a new ChmLoadOptions to get more control over CHM loading. Added new option to ignore field codes during find-replace operation.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 21.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 21.10.
Major Features There are 77 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added an ability to get ParentRegion through the MailMergeRegionInfo. Added new public methods and properties to work with gradient fills and gradient stops. Introduced an intuitive capability to change the appearance of a structured document tag. Added new option to ignore footnotes during find-replace operation.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 21.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 21.9.
Major Features There are 87 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
License checking is updated to tolerate &amp;ldquo;suspicious&amp;rdquo; complex environments. Added an ability to get CustomNumberStyleFormat of ListLevel. Make it possible to get the string representation of the ListLevel object for the specified index. Implemented export of triangular gradients into PDF in native (vector) form.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 21.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 21.8.
Major Features There are 82 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added an ability to insert GIF images into the document. Added new Pdf save option - ExportLanguageToSpanTag. Implemented field updating public callback. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-20059 Provide API to move cursor to any position (character etc) inside a Paragraph New Feature WORDSNET-19311 Add support for HSL colors in HTML documents New Feature WORDSNET-19381 Add context to exceptions thrown while evaluating expressions for LINQ Reporting Engine New Feature WORDSNET-21015 Request to Remove Generator or Producer Name New Feature WORDSNET-22449 Calculate storeItemChecksum attribute on Save New Feature WORDSNET-22345 Export language in Tag tab of object properties New Feature WORDSNET-1786 Allow inserting GIF images into the document New Feature WORDSNET-22408 Implement field updating public callback New Feature WORDSJAVA-2623 Add feature to get certificate valid &amp;lsquo;from&amp;rsquo; and &amp;rsquo;to&amp;rsquo; Dates New Feature WORDSNET-22539 Opening a document using the Document class is significantly slower in version 21.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 21.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 21.7.
Major Features There are 94 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented rendering to PDF/A-2 format. Added an ability to work with Framesets. Introduced a new overload of DocumentBuilder.InsertHtml and a new enumeration HtmlInsertOptions. Provided new API for working with Fill patterns. Supported several exact date-time parse formats while loading JSON for LINQ Reporting Engine.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 21.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 21.6.
Major Features There are 105 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented an ability to set fill and stroke formatting for chart series, data points and markers. Introduced a new API for working with textures. Implemented rendering of OOXML Ink (InkML subset). TxtSaveOptions.MaxCharactersPerLine property was introduced. A new Document.LayoutOption is added to control page numbering in a continuous section.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 21.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 21.5.
Major Features There are 112 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
EQ field export to all HTML based formats was implemented. Added new methods to set checked and unchecked symbol for StructuredDocumentTag. Implemented an ability to use PDF annotations to display user comments. Added MailMerge.RestartListsAtEachSection property to control list numbering restart. Provided a way to customize restrictions on dynamic cell merging for LINQ Reporting Engine.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 21.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 21.4.
Major Features There are 102 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added an ability to remove unused BuiltIn Styles. The Fill class was extended with a functionality for processing solid fills. Public API of Structured Document Tag range was extended. Document.getRange().replace() bulk bug fixing and improvement. JavaDoc documentation update and bug fixes.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 21.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 21.3.
Major Features There are 94 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
ClearQuickStyleGallery method of StyleCollection class was introduced. Extended font API to set Fill properties of text. Added an ability to work with child nodes of StructuredDocumentTag range. Fixed issue with nested PDF bookmarks due to merged hidden paragraphs. Supported Select and SelectMany extension methods for LINQ Reporting Engine.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 21.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 21.2.
Major Features There are 97 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Optimized &amp;ldquo;throws Exception&amp;rdquo; clauses in public API. Harfbazz improvements, XmlDataSource fixes. Make it possible to load documents from IStream object in COM applications. Added an option to update CreatedTime property upon saving. Implemented API to manipulate themed properties of Font object.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 21.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-words-for-java-21-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 21.1.
Major Features There are 84 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
StartColumnBookmark and EndColumnBookmark methods were introduced in DocumentBuilder class. MarkdownSaveOptions.ImageSavingCallback has been added to control how images are saved upon converting to Markdown format. Added an ability to ignore &amp;lt;noscript&amp;gt; HTML elements upon loading HTML. TableStyle.VerticalAlignment was exposed publicly. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-4987 Support &amp;ldquo;cold&amp;rdquo; rendering of OOXML SmartArt (Diagrams) New Feature WORDSNET-20666 Add feature to create Move revision New Feature WORDSNET-21389 Add IImageSavingCallback into MarkdownSaveOptions New Feature WORDSNET-17026 LINQ Reporting Engine - Support section breaks inside data bands and conditional blocks New Feature WORDSNET-20367 Add a field to the Node class so a User can store some custom meta-data in Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>