<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Font for .NET 20.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-font-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-font-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Font for .NET 20.12
WOFF format has been added. TTF and WOFF conversion option has been implemented. .NET 5 target framework has been supported. Some bugs have been fixed.
Key Summary Category FONTNET-147 Public API for conversion functionality has been expanded New Feature FONTNET-152 TTF converter has been developed New Feature FONTNET-159 Conversion for Type1 format has been developed New Feature FONTNET-161 Support WOFF format reading New Feature FONTNET-162 .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Font for .NET 20.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-font-for-net-20-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-font-for-net-20-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Font for .NET 20.10
This release of Aspose.Font for .NET API provides the capability to edit font names for TTF/OTF fonts. In addition, you can now save TTF fonts after editing. Several issues have been fixed, resulting in a more stable font processing functionality.
Key Summary Category FONTNET-107 Saving functionality for fonts of TTF format New Feature FONTNET-124 Ability editing font names New Feature FONTNET-105 Improvement API reference documentation Enhancement FONTNET-115 Basic structures for TTF font editing Enhancement FONTNET-76 Problem with font replacement Bug FONTNET-99 Recovering saving functionality for Type 1 and CFF fonts Bug FONTNET-108 Incorrect encodings are used for font names when TTF font is saves Bug FONTNET-119 Fixing the font saving functionality Bug Got Queries?</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Font for .NET 20.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-font-for-net-20-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/font/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-font-for-net-20-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Font for .NET 20.9
Aspose.Font for .NET has been launched! We are pleased to announce the launch of Aspose.Font for .NET - a .NET font loading and drawing library. The API provides rich functionality to load/save font and provide information about its data structures along with any glyph that is supported by all the font types.
Aspose.Font for .NET also provides encoding information for all the font types which represents a mapping between character codes and glyph identifiers.</description></item></channel></rss>