<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.11.
Major Features In this release we added support for JDK 11, now you can use either -jdk17 or -jdk18 library versions on JRE 11 environment. Please also note about breaking changes in this release. We are going to put our Java port in order to minimize differences from the .NET version of the library. One of that changes is marking non-virtual methods of .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.10.
Breaking Changes We are going to put our Java port in order to minimize differences from the .NET version of the library. One of that changes is marking non-virtual methods of .NET version, as &amp;ldquo;final&amp;rdquo; in Java. In a case when such methods was overridden, compilation errors may appear in customer&amp;rsquo;s code. All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-2434 Implement reading of activity codes for XER files New Feature TASKSNET-2697 Add recurring task parameters validation when creating recurring task Enhancement TASKSNET-2692 Incorrect scheduling of recurring daily task Bug TASKSNET-2659 Wrong timephased data for material resource Bug TASKSNET-2649 Fix issues with formula calculation Bug TASKSNET-2643 Loading MPP file raises Exception Bug TASKSNET-2590 Custom fields&amp;rsquo; values are not formatted properly when saving a project to PDF Bug TASKSNET-2735 Incorrect start of recurring task Bug TASKSJAVA-677 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.8.
Breaking Changes We are going to put our Java port in order to minimize differences from the .NET version of the library. One of that changes is marking non-virtual methods of .NET version, as &amp;ldquo;final&amp;rdquo; in Java. In a case when such methods was overridden, compilation errors may appear in customer&amp;rsquo;s code. All Changes Key Summary Category TASKSNET-1720 Add an ability to create a new recurring task in MPP New Feature TASKSNET-709 Support calculation custom fields by rollup option New Feature TASKSNET-2570 Extend support for saving HTML resources using MemoryStream Enhancement TASKSNET-2599 Improve ExtendedAttribute public API for Date, Duration, decimal values.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.7.
Major Improvements Support for saving fonts/images/css styles separately when saving as HTML Support for OnlyTableValuesAllowed in Extended Attribute Breaking Changes Methods save and saveAsTemplate in Project class can now throw java.io.IOException. All Changes Key Summary Category TASKSNET-1915 Add an option for saving fonts/images/css styles separately when saving as html New Feature TASKSNET-2465 Remove obsolete members in ExtendedAttributeDefinition and OutlineValue Enhancement TASKSNET-1790 Add support for OnlyTableValuesAllowed field in new Extended Attributes API Enhancement TASKSNET-2537 Differences in XML output after resave Bug TASKSNET-2509 Incorrect timephased data for tasks with splits Bug TASKSNET-2508 Incorrect finish dates for tasks with splits Bug TASKSNET-2506 Timephased data displayed incorrectly after a resave Bug TASKSNET-2504 Fix duplicated &amp;ldquo;OutlineCode&amp;rdquo; elements in project&amp;rsquo;s xml Bug TASKSNET-2503 AT brakes MPP file when tasks has splits Bug TASKSNET-2494 Incorrect duration in XML with custom timephased data Bug TASKSNET-2480 Duration changed due to update the percentage complete Bug TASKSJAVA-590 LinkType changes after saving data to MPX Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Added Public Types Description com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information of Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.6.
Major Improvements Support for reading/writing of extended attributes to resource assignment. Validation of work contour type for manual tasks and assignments without resource. All Changes Key Summary Category TASKSNET-2457 Forbid a changing of the work contour type for manual task and assignment without resource Enhancement TASKSNET-730 Implement extended attribute writing for resource assignments New Feature TASKSNET-2468 Fix calculation of Stop/Resume dates when assignment percent work complete equals 100 Bug TASKSNET-2467 Fix calculation of Start/Finish dates when duration is set after them Bug TASKSNET-2466 Fix calculation of Stop/Resume dates of tasks during recalculation Bug TASKSNET-2461 AT writes contoured timephased data in wrong way - work is different Bug TASKSNET-2456 A HyperlinkBase project property value is truncated up to 15 characters Bug TASKSNET-2453 Duration is zeroed when material resource is being used Bug TASKSNET-2452 No links on tasks after an export to PDF/HTML/Images Bug TASKSNET-2450 Resource usage distribution is not correct in the resultant MPP file Bug TASKSNET-2449 Wrong elapsed duration for a summary task Bug TASKSNET-2435 Partial baselines are skipped when reading assignments&amp;rsquo; baselines Bug TASKSNET-2433 XER to MPP raises TaskWritingException Bug TASKSNET-2428 Baseline* extended attribute values for assignments are lost in AT-resaved file.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information of Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.5.
All Changes Key Summary Category TASKSNET-2362 Add a support of setting a default font when a project is rendering into JPG, BMP, PNG and HTML New Feature TASKSJAVA-569 Integrate Metered license into Aspose.Tasks for Java New Feature TASKSNET-2381 Newly created calendar could not be assigned to a task Bug TASKSNET-2360 StartDate and EndDate properties of SaveOptions are not working properly Bug TASKSNET-2344 Fix unnecessary thrown and caught exceptions on .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information of Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.4 release.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category TASKSJAVA-526 Add support of a Conholdate.Total license New Feature TASKSJAVA-476 Ignore milliseconds while setting the task times Enhancement TASKSJAVA-505 Exception while recalculating the XML project Bug TASKSNET-2318 Incorrect calculation of Tsk.ManualStart while Tsk.ActualStart is set Bug TASKSNET-2310 MPP to PDF raises System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-tasks-for-java-18-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.Tasks for Java 18.3.
Major Features Renumbering of WBS Code Eliminating the gap between Tasks list and page footer Get page count depending upon start and end date time All Changes Key Summary Category TASKSNET-1566 Add a support for setting a default font when a project is rendering into PDF New Feature TASKSNET-1994 Implement a feature &amp;ldquo;Renumber&amp;hellip;&amp;rdquo; WBS codes New Feature TASKSNET-2217 Setting for eliminating the gap between the list of tasks and footer New Feature TASKSNET-2199 Implement GetPageCount overload depending on Start and EndDate dates Enhancement TASKSJAVA-335 Provide descriptive error messages when opening corrupted MPP files.</description></item></channel></rss>