<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 22.12 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Speed up create method in Aspose.Imaging Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8293 Speed up create method in Aspose.Imaging Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8325 Dynamic loading not works for conversion to dicom Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8314 Fix memory leak when save tiffframes to MemoryStream Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8313 Incorrect convertion from svg to png Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8312 Specific cdr image to pdf conversion Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8308 Cannot load the CDR image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8304 SVG to PNG, output image distorted Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8302 Incorrect export Tiff -&amp;gt; Pdf with compression PdfImageCompressionOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 22.11 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Integration Aspose.Fonts into Aspose.Imaging Reworked memory allocation management - the shared memory approach was replaced by a buffered file cache and it resolves the issue of abandoned temporary files Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8291 Integration Aspose.Fonts into Aspose.Imaging Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8290 Emf to PNG not properly converted Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8289 Cannot load WEBP image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8284 Cannot convert the DICOM image to APNG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8280 Fix Emf formulas rasterization Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8267 Cannot convert EMF to SVG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8266 CDR to JPG conversion error Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 22.10 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Support of 16-bit/Channel 64 bit PNG images Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8250 Support of 16-bit/Channel 64 bit PNG images Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8256 &amp;ldquo;Unknown character - &amp;quot; exception when open ODG file Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8248 PSD exporter saves CMYK colors as RGB Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8245 DNG to JPG changes image color Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8240 Exception while load the particular tiff Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8236 Exception on conversion Gif and Dicom images to Bmp Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8235 Cannot export particular SVG image Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 22.9 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Add support for Icon File (.ico) file format Add Apple MakerNote tags parsing Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8231 Add support for Icon File (.ico) file format Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8209 Add Apple MakerNote tags parsing Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8213 Cannot compress particular SVG image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8212 Cannot save particular SVG image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8210 BMP loading bug Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8208 Exception on reading EPS image size Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8207 CDR to PDF conversion issue Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 22.8 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Review error messages in the entire library Implement Jpeg saved quality estimation Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8192 Review error messages in the entire library Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8191 Implement Jpeg saved quality estimation Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8194 Incorrect extracting embedded bmp from Cdr image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8193 Incorrect saving Dicom image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8187 Can&amp;rsquo;t load PNG image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8186 SVG image Load method throws an exception Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8184 Can&amp;rsquo;t convert WMZ to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8182 Problem in EMF to SVG conversion Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8181 Artifacts appear when load tiff file and save to tiff with parameters Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8180 Incorrect export BMP -&amp;gt; JPG -&amp;gt; PNG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8178 Cannot export particular EPS image Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 22.7 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8175 Exception in Java 17 (&amp;ldquo;opens java.util.regex&amp;rdquo;) Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8173 Incorrect export from EMF to PNG on Linux Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8164 Svg to Dxf export failed Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8163 System.NullReferenceException while rotating or flipping particular GIF animation Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8162 Can&amp;rsquo;t convert SVG to BMP Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8161 &amp;ldquo;There is no active frame selected.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 22.6 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Fix issue with rounded corners in rectangle generated in emf file Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8131 Fix issue with rounded corners in rectangle generated in emf file Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8152 Cannot load particular ODG image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8151 Can&amp;rsquo;t load DCM image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8141 Fix bug with exception in CDR file Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8134 Can&amp;rsquo;t load DCM image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8129 Cannot read DICOM image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8124 AdjustContrast and AdjustGamma operations are not properly applies on Gif multiframe image Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 22.5 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Unify extraction of raster images, embedded in vector formats. Improve DIB processing implementation Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8108 Unify extraction of raster images, embedded in vector formats. Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8106 Improve DIB processing implementation Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8116 Exception on converting EMF to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8115 Duplicate tiff frame results in a wrong colors (almost completly dark) Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8112 Incorrect export from SVGZ to PNG on Linux Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8111 Incorrect output after WEBP image is resized Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8110 Exception on converting EPS to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8109 Can&amp;rsquo;t convert WMZ to JPG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8107 Can&amp;rsquo;t convert CMX to PNG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8105 Fix bug of a text formatting in the attached image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8104 Dicom export and consequent save then export produce different results Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8103 Exception on loading a CDR image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8102 DrawString with extra distance between symbols or lines Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8101 Support reading of a 16bit Dicom image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8097 Emf file not correctly converted to png Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8096 ImageSaveException while exporting particular GIF image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-1573 Exception on saving DICOM image Enhancement Public API changes: Added APIs: Please see corresponding cumulative API changes for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 22.4 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-4-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Texture brushes support for export to vectorized Psd format Improve resampling quality (transparency handling and color intensity on borders) Implement support storing Xmp tags in Dicom format Fix bug with SVG tspan elements aligment Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8087 Texture brushes support for export to vectorized Psd format Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8076 Improve resampling quality (transparency handling and color intensity on borders) Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8070 Implement support storing Xmp tags in Dicom format Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8058 Fix bug with SVG tspan elements aligment Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8090 Exception when exporting TIFF to TIFF Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8089 Fix bugs with rendering in Cdr file Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8088 Export Png to Svg not work in trial mode Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8086 Exception when loading a DICOM image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8079 Incorrect export from GIF to APNG Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8078 Emf to png export failed Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8077 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 22.3 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Implement export from Aps to Vectorized PSD Original Dicom tags should be kept on export Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8056 Implement export from Aps to Vectorized PSD Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8045 Original Dicom tags should be kept on export Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8055 Resolve unsupported options combination for tiff Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8053 Type of profile ColorSpaceClass is not supported Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8047 Not all pages visible in specific DCM file Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8046 Loosing transparency during the export from PNG to the BMP 32bits Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8040 Exception occur when save tiff image to stream Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-7905 Add com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for Java 22.2 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-imaging-for-java-22-2-release-notes/</guid><description>Competitive features: Speed up resize method in Aspose.Imaging Support pixel perfect text alignment Key Summary Category IMAGINGJAVA-8028 Speed up resize method in Aspose.Imaging Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8021 Support pixel perfect text alignment Feature IMAGINGJAVA-8037 Display the correct exception instead of: &amp;ldquo;Object reference not set to an instance of an object.&amp;rdquo; exception. Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8025 Improve YCbCr to RGb subsampling test coverage for Jpeg2000 Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8023 Fix bug in EMF with CacheData Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8022 Can&amp;rsquo;t load CDR Image Enhancement IMAGINGJAVA-8019 &amp;ldquo;Specified color model &amp;lsquo;Invalid&amp;rsquo; is not supported.</description></item></channel></rss>