<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 19.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 19.12.
Major Features Conversion to PDF 1.7 standard is now supported. User-installed fonts are now supported upon using SystemFontSource on Windows10. New public properties of Bookmark are exposed. OLE object data is exposed to public API. Access to related DataTable is provided in LINQ Reporting Engine through relation name. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-18367 Medieval fonts: support for inline number forms New Feature WORDSNET-17731 Support converting word documents to the PDF 1.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 19.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 19.11.
Major Features Provided an ability to work with Web Extensions, new classes allow to customize elements and attributes that extend the XML vocabulary for Office Add-ins representation. Added an ability to customize the formatting of the horizontal rule shape. Improved character spacing calculation when &amp;lsquo;use printer metrics&amp;rsquo; option is set. Macros support improved. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-18890 Consider support ECSDA New Feature WORDSNET-18182 Add feature to set properties of horizontal rule New Feature WORDSNET-19023 Throw warnings about the presence of JavaScript (or any other unsupported Scripts) in HTML New Feature WORDSNET-19152 Support of .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 19.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 19.10.
Major Features Implemented DocumentDirection option that allows specifying the direction to flow the text in a document. Implemented proper scaling for shapes inside &amp;lsquo;graphicFrame&amp;rsquo; container for DrawingML rendering. Improved &amp;ldquo;inline/not inline&amp;rdquo; validation for OMath objects when rendering. Supported dynamic insertion of links to document bookmarks for LINQ Reporting Engine. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-11772 Image is misplaced in generated PDF New Feature WORDSNET-19103 Add feature to link CustomDocumentProperty to Bookmark New Feature WORDSNET-18920 Add feature to insert hyperlink to bookmark using LINQ Reporting New Feature WORDSNET-19263 Some content render at the bottom of previous page in PDF New Feature WORDSNET-18596 DOCX to PDF - text is not on right page New Feature WORDSNET-19067 Add feature to detect text direction (RTL / LTR) while import TXT document New Feature WORDSNET-8253 Images are overlapping and rendering to previous pages in PDF New Feature WORDSNET-14273 Content renders on previous page in output PDF New Feature WORDSNET-7534 SmartArt graphic is not preserved during DOCX to RTF conversion New Feature WORDSNET-19054 Add the ability to set the NumberFormat for an individual data label New Feature WORDSNET-19216 OMath should be rendered as &amp;ldquo;Not inline&amp;rdquo; (currently OMath is always &amp;ldquo;inline&amp;rdquo;) Bug WORDSNET-4631 IMailMergeDataSource has no code sample for the GetValue member Bug WORDSNET-18984 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 19.9.
Major Features Provided API to write and modify VBA macros. Implemented ability to create repeating section structured document tags. Simplified work with XML, JSON, and CSV data sources for LINQ Reporting Engine. Improved rendering of “Sitka Banner”, “Sitka Display”, “Sitka Heading”, “Sitka Small”, “Sitka Subheading”, “Sitka Text” and “Cambria Math” fonts. Implemented OpenType number spacing. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-19120 Add support for the Truncate Font Height compatibility option New Feature WORDSNET-18722 Simplify working with XML, JSON, and CSV data sources for LINQ Reporting Engine New Feature WORDSNET-12480 Provide ability to manipulate VBA macro code (string changes) New Feature WORDSNET-12655 Provide code to programmatically create RepeatingSection SDT using Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 19.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 19.8.
Major Features Implemented an option that allows to specify whether to work with the original or revised version of a document. Implemented API to define default options for data labels of chart series. Fixed rendering of diagonal borders is vertically merged cells. Fixed issue when &amp;ldquo;keep with next&amp;rdquo; is applied to the last paragraph in a table cell.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 19.7.
Major Features Implemented basic reader and writer for Markdown format. Implemented public API for dealing with linked text boxes. Implemented feature to detect SmartArt shape. Added property Revision.Group. Supported dynamic list numbering restart for LINQ Reporting Engine. Released Advanced Typography package, kerning feature works now. Improved handling of whitespace shrinking in a presence of an option &amp;ldquo;Balance SBCS characters and DBCS character&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 19.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 19.6.
Major Features Provided API to Extract VBA Macros from Word Document. Added a new DocSaveOptions.AlwaysCompressMetafiles option. Implemented table style public API. Improved rendering of CurvedArrow shapes with basic and custom adjustment points. Improved rendering of DrawingML charts with scaling of the vertical axis if the chart legend has a manual layout. FontInfo substitution was tuned to prefer symbolic fonts as a substitution for symbolic fonts and regular fonts as a substitution for regular fonts.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 19.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 19.5.
Major Features Added a new overloaded AppendDocument() method with additional ImportFormatOptions parameter. Added a new public property Paragraph.BreakIsStyleSeparator. Added feature to get font leading (line spacing). Added Field.DisplayResult property to obtain a fake result.  Provide a method to check if a particular DML text effect is applied. Implemented StreamFontSource class which allows loading fonts from the stream.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 19.4.
Major Features Added a new ImportFormatOptions class for more flexible control over importing tasks. Provide API to change how text is vertically aligned within the Text Box. Added a new ImportFormatOptions.KeepSourceNumbering option for use in import operations. Added a new ImportFormatOptions.IgnoreTextBoxes option for use in import operations. Added property PdfSaveOptions.AdditionalTextPositioning to control writing of additional text positioning operators in PDF.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 19.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 19.3.
Major Features Added feature to preserve the representation of legacy control characters while converting to OOXML formats. Added new public properties to the ChartAxis class. Added predefined font fallback settings for Google Noto fonts. Hyphenation logic improved. Fixed trailing spaces underlines in RTL paragraphs. Fixed issue with automatic frame width updates when the field is changed. Implemented invalid parameters filtering for shadow effect rendering.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 19.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 19.2
Major Features Supported inlining of syntax error messages into templates instead of exception throwing for LINQ Reporting Engine. Improved font fetching and substitution mechanism with corresponding API changes. Improved warnings for image processing issues when rendering to PDF. Improved font fallback rendering for full-width character Unicode ranges. Metafiles with &amp;ldquo;HeaderPlaceable&amp;rdquo; structure is now rendering regardless of structure checksum.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 19.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-words-for-net-19-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 19.1
Major Features There are 48 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented the directed line caps rendering for Bezier curves in metafiles. Implemented processing of the stroke properties while rendering custom line caps in metafiles. Implemented support of Unicode font names while rendering to PDF. Implemented Tiff binarization threshold control via ImageSaveOptions.</description></item></channel></rss>