<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.12.
Major Features There are 74 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented an abbility to specify the particular Margin type for the given section. The new public properties ThemeColor and TintAndShade were introduced. Implemented rendering of the linear trendline formula for DrawingML charts rendering. Implemented optimization that significantly reduces the depth of graphics state nesting when rendering to PDF to maintain specification compliance.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.11.0.
Major Features There are 67 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added an ability to create the new structured document tags of Citation type. Introduced the new property which allows to embed OLE attachments from the source document to the output PDF document. Changed default behavior when opening document of unknown format.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.10.0.
Major Features There are 78 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented an ability to ignore StructuredDocumentTags upon FindReplace. HtmlSaveOptions.metafile_format now affects OLE objects and controls. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release (Reported by .NET Users) Key Summary Category WORDSNET-19205 Add feature to export Shape into SVG and DIV tag in output HTML New Feature WORDSNET-19780 Render correct indentation in Text format against HTML blockquote Tags New Feature WORDSNET-23920 Consider providing a way to move DocumentBuilder cursor inside SDT New Feature WORDSNET-23530 Check Boxes (Content Control) are checked after UpdatingFields Enhancement WORDSNET-24237 Redundant revisions are rendered in PDF Enhancement WORDSNET-24393 The document appears to be corrupted and cannot be loaded message on loading a doc file Enhancement WORDSNET-11419 Issue with table border when saving as PDF Bug WORDSNET-12476 Shape&amp;rsquo;s hyperlink is removed after saving to HTML Bug WORDSNET-18387 Incorrect conversion to PDF page numbers Bug WORDSNET-19584 Page numbering is off when converting to PDF Bug WORDSNET-19698 Page numbering in footer gets corrupted in PDF Bug WORDSNET-20416 Use DML shapes instead VML for DOCX to HTML conversion Bug WORDSNET-20600 DOCX to PDF conversion issue with chart&amp;rsquo;s Y-Axis Bug WORDSNET-20723 Conversion issue with page numbers Bug WORDSNET-20724 Conversion issue with page number upon DOCX to PDF Bug WORDSNET-20725 Incorrect page numbers Bug WORDSNET-20726 Issue with page numbers when DOCX to PDF Bug WORDSNET-21887 Node is internally removed from the DOM tree after table serialization Bug WORDSNET-21964 Nested content control not deleted from document Bug WORDSNET-22706 Issue when converting a Word Cell to text Bug WORDSNET-23435 Revisions changed after adding CustomXmlPart Bug WORDSNET-23629 PAGE field is updated improperly upon rendering Bug WORDSNET-23638 HtmlSaveOptionsMetafileFormat does not work as expected Bug WORDSNET-23647 Alpha list is reset to numbered list after conversion from HTML to DOCX Bug WORDSNET-23679 Table layout is broken after rendering document Bug WORDSNET-23850 Incorrect cell margins on html to docx conversion Bug WORDSNET-23923 Incorrect table indent on rtf to docx conversion Bug WORDSNET-24004 Gradient fill is rendered improperly Bug WORDSNET-24012 Built in styles are written as custom styles after open/save DOCX Bug WORDSNET-24138 Text is truncated when rendering metafile to PDF Bug WORDSNET-24148 Encoding of a HTML document is incorrectly detected as UTF-7 Bug WORDSNET-24149 Garbage text is loaded from a EPUB document Bug WORDSNET-24150 Document title is incorrectly imported from EPUB Bug WORDSNET-24172 Set correct values for UseFELayout and DefaultFontLocalIdFarEast when Chinese is specified in LoadOptions Bug WORDSNET-24238 Strikethrough text format is changed to underline on PDF import Bug WORDSNET-24250 SystemArgumentOutOfRangeException: &amp;ldquo;Length cannot be less than zero&amp;rdquo; unhandled exception Bug WORDSNET-24267 Legend gradient fill is not rendered Bug WORDSNET-24269 DOCX to PDF: Chart rendered incorrectly Bug WORDSNET-24272 Reflection effect is not rendered in Html Fixed Bug WORDSNET-24286 Shape flip is not taken into account when rendering a gradient fill Bug WORDSNET-24291 Resaving the document changes checkbox state Bug WORDSNET-24298 DOCX to PDF: Border around objects does not retain after conversion Bug WORDSNET-24299 InvalidOperationException: Operator should take n operands: Incorrect stream content Bug WORDSNET-24300 InvalidOperationException: Operator should take n operands: too big integer value Bug WORDSNET-24301 ExtractPages throws NullReferenceException Bug WORDSNET-24308 Invalid DOCX document Bug WORDSNET-24319 NullReferenceException on saving to PDF Bug WORDSNET-24331 Incorrect reflection direction when rendering 3D effects Bug WORDSNET-24344 Date format of SDT is ignored when FindReplaceOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.9.0.
Major Features There are 102 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
TxtLoadOptions was extended with new auto_numbering_detection option. Implemented an ability to cache the header/footer shapes to reduce the size of the output PDF file. Added a new feature to get FieldEQ as OfficeMath. Allowed creation of structured document tags of Group type at Row level.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.8.0.
Major Features There are 143 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Published API Reference AZW3 (also called KF8) file format is now supported for import and export. Implemented support for cell spacing in tables upon rendering. Improved font substitution for symbols. Improved the rotation algorithm of axis labels of the charts.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.7.0.
Major Features There are 85 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented an ability to convert PDF documents to fixed page formats with high fidelity and performance. Implemented support of WCAG 2.0 PDF. Implemented our own glyph outlines parsing for OpenType(CFF) fonts. Introduced new HTML import mode for block-level elements.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.6.0.
Major Features There are 69 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
DrawingML charts public API was extended to support gradient, texture and pattern fills. Implemented a solid text fill effect inheritance exception that mimics the behavior of MS Word. Saving progress notifications were extended for ODT format. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release (Reported by .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.5.0.
Major Features There are 126 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added support for loading EPUB documents. Added support for loading XML documents. Added support of &amp;ldquo;Envelope No. 10&amp;rdquo; page size for printing. Implemented rendering of a border box around the MathML formulas and the strike lines. Improved font detection when rendering characters in MathML formulas.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.4.0.
Major Features There are 66 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added support for Python 3.10. Added saving to PDFA-4 and several other improvements in PDF output. Implemented reading of Photoshop metadata resolution in Jpeg images. Provided an ability to manipulate with DrawingML chart legend entries. Implemented an ability to specify the name of an xls/xlsx file the DrawingML chart is linked to.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Python via .NET 22.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/python/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-python-via-dotnet-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Python via .NET.
Major Features There are 355 improvements and fixes in this release. The most notable are:
Added saving to PDF 2.0 and several other improvements in PDF output. Improved DML chart axis scaling algorithm. Improved table comparing algorithm. Provided comments syntax in LINQ Reporting. AZW3 format (KF8 is another name of the format) is now supported for loading.</description></item></channel></rss>