<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 17.12.1 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cad-for-net-17-12-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cad-for-net-17-12-1-release-notes/</guid><description> Key Summary Category CADNET-506 Extra margins when DXF saved as PDF Enhancement</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 17.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cad-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cad-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category CADNET-457 Set compliance after converting CAD to PDF Feature CADNET-450 Support for rounded hidden lines when exporting DWG/DXF to BMP and PDF Feature CADNET-415 Support for reading XREF metadata for DWG file Feature CADNET-420 Wrong page size when exporting DWG to PDF (.NET) Feature CADNET-376 3D entities support for DGN v7 Feature CADNET-371 Support for setting print area for DWG image in exported PDF Feature CADNET-355 DWG to PDF convert gives blank page Feature CADNET-343 Support for DWT file format in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 17.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cad-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cad-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category CADNET-186 Support for IFC format Feature CADNET-380 Implement support for STL format Feature CADNET-292 When DXF is converted to PDF, output files has 3 pages instead of 1 Enhancement CADNET-294 Converting DXF to PDF is splitting image on multiple pages in PDF Enhancement CADNET-338 Incorrect image size for DWF Enhancement CADNET-381 Difference between rendered PDF and Image Enhancement CADNET-382 ImageException on exporting DWG to PDF Enhancement CADNET-336 Text missing when DWG is exported to PDF Enhancement CADNET-301 Layer not visible when saving dwg as jpg Enhancement CADNET-293 DXF to PDF conversion is producing very small shapes in resultant PDF Enhancement CADNET-288 Blank area when saving dwg as image and pdf Enhancement CADNET-272 Converting DXF to PDF is generating incorrect PDF file (text missing and multiple pages) Enhancement CADNET-199 Converting DWG to PDF format is producing incorrect PDF file of empty pages Enhancement CADNET-178 Support export option which automatically excludes empty layouts Enhancement CADNET-296 Fix bug with shift of drawing on layouts Enhancement CADNET-175 Converting DXF to PDF is not producing correct results: Incorrect color and orientation of text Enhancement Added APIs: Class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 17.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cad-for-net-17-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cad-for-net-17-4-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category CADNET-240 Support DWF Format Feature CADNET-68 Support MLeader Entity for DWG format Feature CADNET-200 Converting DWG to PDF format is producing error Enhancement CADNET-197 Add support for DXF and DWG file formats in FileFormat enumeration Enhancement CADNET-245 Converting DWG layers to PDF is producing incomplete text in the resultant PDF Enhancement CADNET-196 Converting DWG to PNG is producing incomplete image Enhancement Added APIs: Class Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for .NET 17.02.0 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cad-for-net-17-02-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cad-for-net-17-02-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.CAD for .Net has been updated to version 17.02.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category CADNET-179 Normalize drawing size to absolute metrics Feature CADNET-201 Add support for clipping of raster images Feature CADNET-110 Determine the external references for a dwg and their filepaths Feature CADNET-15 Support for DWG 2007(AC1021) Format Feature CADNET-255 Implement right entity order for dwg format Enhancement CADNET-198 Converting DWG to PDF format is producing incorrect PDF file of 1kb size Enhancement CADNET-184 Converting DWG to PDF file is throwing exception Enhancement CADNET-183 Converting DWG to PDF is not exporting external raster images linked with DWG file Enhancement Usage examples CADNET-179 Normalize drawing size to absolute metrics Automatic shrink (Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>