<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.12
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the December release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
we have fixed the issue with masks which having the type of coordinate units userspaceonuse and applying to images and graphics;
the opacity processing code that is used for graphics and bitmaps was changed to address issues with ignoring transformation matrix inside nested SVG elements;</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.11
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the November release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
We have improved processing of unit types for CSS media query parsing algorithm.
Fixed issue with disposing node iterators.
Public API changes: Added APIs: No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.10
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the October release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
We have added a new &amp;ldquo;Image Vectorization&amp;rdquo; feature that allows to vectorize raster images such as PNG, JPEG, BMP, TIFF, GIF, ICO into an SVG document. Under vectorization we mean the process of reducing bitmaps to geometric shapes made up from path elements and stored as SVG.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.9
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the September release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
Enhanced the accuracy of the glyph vectorization algorithm. Updated the user agent style sheets according to the latest documentation. Public API changes: Added APIs: A new method was added to DOMObject class:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.8
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the August release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
added the ability to manage pdf document metadata when converting SVG; fixed algorithm of calculation styles with &amp;lsquo;important&amp;rsquo; derective according to latest CSS specifications. Public API changes: Added APIs: A new option was added to PdfRenderingOptions class:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.7
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the July release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
improved handling of large images; introduced the new resource handling option, which allows to ignore certain resources; fixed issue SVG-128. Public API changes: Added APIs: A new field &amp;lsquo;Ignore&amp;rsquo; was added to ResourceHandling enumeration.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.6
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the June release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
fixed an issue with calculating bounding boxes for rotated objects; added support for applaing restrictions to URLs of handled pages and resources such as css, js, images etc&amp;hellip;; removed absolete properties.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.5
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the May release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
fixed issue in the method GetBBox for SVG tspan elements; improved the gradients serialization algorithm. Public API changes: Added APIs: No Changes
Changed APIs: No Changes
Removed APIs: No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.4
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the April release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
we have added support for caching operation of SVGGeometry elements which seriously increased performance. Public API changes: Added APIs: No Changes
Changed APIs: No Changes
Removed APIs: No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.3
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the March release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
we have added support of rtl (right to left languages) to conversion and rendering of SVG documents; updated the SVG serialization algorithms according to the latest documentation. Public API changes: Added APIs: No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.2
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the February release of Aspose.SVG for .NET:
we have added escaping control characters (&amp;rsquo;&amp;lt;&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;&amp;gt;&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;&amp;rsquo;&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;&amp;quot;&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;&amp;amp;&amp;rsquo;) into SVGDocument save methods; the URL parsing algorithm was modified according to the latest documentation; we have improved the path resolution algorithm to encode special characters correctly.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-svg-for-net-21-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 21.1
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are honored to announce the January release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. We have added support for saving SVGDocument with new IOutputStorage interface. This interface allows save SVG document content and resources to streams and manage them.
Public API changes: Added APIs: Next interface and classes were added to namespace Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>