<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Android via Java 22.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-22.12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-22.12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Android via Java 22.12.
Major Features There are 232 improvements and fixes in this release. The most notable are:
Implemented an ability to ignore StructuredDocumentTags upon FindReplace. HtmlSaveOptions.MetafileFormat now affects OLE objects and controls. Implemented custom colored/grayscale printing mode. Added an ability to create the new structured document tags of Citation type. Implemented field updating progress tracking. Introduced the new property which allows to embed OLE attachments from the source document to the output PDF document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Android via Java 22.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-22.9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-22.9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Android via Java 22.9.
Major Features There are 344 improvements and fixes in this release. The most notable are:
Implemented support of WCAG 2.0 PDF. Implemented our own glyph outlines parsing for OpenType(CFF) fonts. Introduced new HTML import mode for block-level elements. Added support of the DATABASE fields. Provided an ability to set shadow formatting of the shape object. AZW3 (also called KF8) file format is now supported for import and export.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Android via Java 22.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-22.6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-22.6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Android via Java 22.6.
Major Features There are 272 improvements and fixes in this release. The most notable are:
Added saving to PDFA-4 and several other improvements in PDF output. Implemented reading of Photoshop metadata resolution in Jpeg images. Provided an ability to manipulate with DrawingML chart legend entries. Implemented ability to specify the name of an xls/xlsx file the DrawingML chart is linked to.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Android via Java 22.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-22.3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/androidjava/release-notes/2022/aspose-words-for-android-via-java-22.3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Android via Java 22.3.
Major Features There are 281 improvements and fixes in this release. The most notable are:
Implemented rendering into PDF with PDF/UA-1 compliance. This option assumes compliance with document special accessibility requirements. Improved rendering of operators in MathML formulas. Introduced a new option to control conflicting styles behavior upon import. Added an ability to get saving progress notifications through the SaveOptions.</description></item></channel></rss>