<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.12.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10724 Fix escaping of text values when writing project to XER format. Enhancement TASKSNET-10717 Add LinkLagTimeSpan property to TaskLink. Enhancement TASKSNET-3704 Fix cost calculations for case when multiple rates are effective on a day. Enhancement TASKSNET-10723 Fix System.FormatException when reading a project from XER file Bug TASKSNET-10722 Fix creation of external task links Bug TASKSNET-10721 Fix addition of new table for a project saved without a template file Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public methods were added: Description com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.11.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-3855 Implement the API to access entities&amp;rsquo; fields using .NET properties. New Feature TASKSNET-10664 Add an setting that allows to specify that Primavera UIDs should be preserved when importing project from XER or P6XML formats Enhancement TASKSNET-10657 Fix &amp;lsquo;TimephasedData value is not in correct format&amp;rsquo; exception when reading the specific file Bug TASKSNET-10652 Fix reading of filter criteria when value is fractional number Bug TASKSNET-10614 Fix Percent and Duration differences for Milestone and Summary tasks read from Primavera XER format Bug TASKSNET-10699 Add an API for read-only access to Primavera-specific task&amp;rsquo;s properties for projects read from XER\P6XML formats Enhancement TASKSNET-10696 Change sort order of summary tasks for a project read from XER format Enhancement TASKSNET-10693 Fix reading of rates from XER format Bug TASKSNET-10692 Fix incorrect values of Work and Cost fields for assignments with Units count not equal to 1 in project read from XER file.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.10.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSJAVA-1742 Fix handling of environment variables with newlines Bug TASKSNET-10648 Fix ArgumentOutOfRangeException when recalculating project read from XML file Bug TASKSNET-10638 Fix exception when saving the specific XML file to MPP Bug TASKSNET-10637 Fix addition of new view. Bug TASKSNET-10633 Fix recalculation error for the specific project Bug TASKSNET-10631 Fix tasks Ids when reading the specific project with null tasks Bug TASKSNET-10628 Fix ArgumentOutOfRangeException when recalculating Project read from specific file Bug TASKSNET-10606 Fix reading of resource rates from XER file Bug TASKSNET-10583 Fix errors when saving specific files to MPP format Bug TASKSNET-10634 Fix NullReferenceException when saving project with added View Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public enumerations were added: Description com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.9.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10612 Throw user-friendly exception when a view cannot be rendered with the specified &amp;ldquo;Fit X to Y pages&amp;rdquo; options Enhancement TASKSNET-10610 Change the default value of SaveOptions.Timescale to SaveOptions.DefinedInView Enhancement TASKSNET-10603 Fix reading of LinkLag for XER and PrimaveraXML formats Bug TASKSNET-10615 Fix reading of task&amp;rsquo;s calendars from Primavera XML format Bug TASKSNET-10607 Fix reading of project&amp;rsquo;s currency for XER format Bug Examples and additional notes Related issue: TASKSNET-10610 - Change the default value of SaveOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.8.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10589 Add an ability to map member of Tsk class to MS Project&amp;rsquo;s default field title Enhancement TASKSNET-10558 Add support of reading of Activity Codes and its values for Primavera P6 XML format Enhancement TASKSNET-3635 Reduce load time when reading a project from Project Server DB Enhancement TASKSNET-10601 Fix &amp;lsquo;Arithmetic operation resulted in an overflow&amp;rsquo; error when opening files saved by MS Project ver 16.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.7.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10556 Add IsRoot property to Resource object Enhancement TASKSNET-10553 Add properties to access ResourceAssignment&amp;rsquo;s Task and Resource Enhancement TASKSNET-10469 Add support of reading of User Defined Types for Primavera P6 XML format Enhancement TASKSNET-10554 Fix incorrect calculation of Asn.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.6.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10547 Add an ability to turn off export of tasks/resources/assignments sheets when exporting to XLSX format Enhancement TASKSNET-10535 Add support of PrimaveraReadOptions.UndefinedConstraintHandlingBehavior for Primavera P6 Xml format Enhancement TASKSNET-10536 Fix each call to project.Recalculate decreases work of task with &amp;lsquo;FixedDuration&amp;rsquo; Type and non-flat WorkContour Bug TASKSNET-10524 Fix infinite loop in recalculations when task calendar is set to 24h Bug TASKSNET-10505 Fix incorrect timephased data generation for tasks with non flat WorkContour Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.5.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-4602 Extend XER import to support XER files with more than 1 projects Feature TASKSNET-10500 Add a way to specify behavior of task constraints import for XER format Enhancement TASKSNET-10468 Add support of reading User Defined Fields for Primavera XER format Enhancement TASKSNET-10520 Fix reading \ writing of PreleveledStart and PreleveledFinish fields Bug TASKSNET-10519 Fix task &amp;lsquo;Notes&amp;rsquo; icon is incorrectly shown when MPP saved by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.4.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSJAVA-1130 Support for thread interruption for Project loading operation New Feature TASKSNET-10310 Add cancellation token support for Project loading operation New Feature TASKSNET-10498 Add reading/writing of Status date from/to XER file. Enhancement TASKSNET-10496 Make WorkingTime immutable Enhancement TASKSNET-10480 Add an API to set user-specified callback which allows to substitute absent fonts when a project is rendered to a graphical format Enhancement TASKSNET-10471 Remove unnecessary memory allocations when reading Task, Assignment, Resource properties.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.3.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10362 Rename CalculationType.Calculation to CalculationType.Formula Enhancement TASKSNET-10470 Reduce number of memory allocations when reading View data from MPP file Enhancement TASKSNET-10458 Fix project&amp;rsquo;s timescale start \ finish is not shown properly by MS Project Bug TASKSNET-10394 Fix file in MPP12 format saved by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.2.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10433 Fix ShowProjectSummaryTask public API Enhancement TASKSNET-10309 Change return type of *Slack properties to System.TimeSpan Enhancement TASKSNET-4835 Rename members of SaveFileFormat enum to camel case Enhancement TASKSNET-10431 Fix rendering of timescale to fit it to page&amp;rsquo;s width Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public methods and properties were deleted: com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2022/aspose-tasks-for-java-22-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 22.1.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-10397 Fix resource calendars are missing in file saved by Aspose.Tasks Bug TASKSNET-2851 Fix incorrect updating of project work completed up to the specified date Bug TASKSJAVA-1679 Fix StackOverflow exception during project loading in a case of neutral culture used Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were deleted: Description com.</description></item></channel></rss>