<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2022 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.12.0 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-12-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-12-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This article contains a summary of recent changes, enhancements and bug fixes in Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.12.0 (December 2022) release.
GPU version: 21.6.0
What was changed Key Summary Category OCRNET-608 Added ID card recognition. New feature OCRNET-609 Added passport recognition. New feature OCRNET-606 Added vehicle license plate recognition. New feature OCRNET-610 Added invoice recognition. New feature OCRNET-617 Added methods for comparing image texts.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.11.1 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-11-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-11-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This article contains a summary of recent changes, enhancements and bug fixes in Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.11.1 (November 2022) release.
GPU version: 21.6.0
What was changed Key Summary Category OCRNET-603 Improved curved lines recognition algorithm. Enhancement OCRNET-613 Fixed an issue with recognition of blank pages that caused the automatic skew correction algorithm to detect page boundaries incorrectly. Fix Public API changes and backwards compatibility This section lists all public API changes introduced in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.11.0 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-11-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-11-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This article contains a summary of recent changes, enhancements and bug fixes in Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.11.0 (November 2022) release.
GPU version: 21.6.0
What was changed Key Summary Category OCRNET-582 Added a new document areas detection mode that auto-straightens curved lines and finds text blocks inside the resulting image. New feature OCRNET-604 Fixed handling of images with different horizontal and vertical resolutions (non-square pixels).</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.10 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This article contains a summary of recent changes, enhancements and bug fixes in Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.10 (October 2022) release.
GPU version: 21.6.0
What was changed Key Summary Category OCRNET-584 Extracting text from a TIFF image provided as a memory stream. New feature OCRNET-584 Extracting text from a DjVu file provided as a memory stream. New feature OCRNET-592 Fixed conversion of TIFF images with specific resolution to searchable PDF documents.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This article contains a summary of recent changes, enhancements and bug fixes in Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.9 (September 2022) release.
GPU version: 21.6.0
What was changed Key Summary Category OCRNET-569 Extracting text from receipts. New feature OCRNET-572 Added a recognition setting that improves the recognition of small fonts and detection of dense lines. New feature OCRNET-573 Improved handling of images rotated by 90 degrees.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This article contains a summary of recent changes, enhancements and bug fixes in Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.8 (August 2022) release.
GPU version: 21.6.0
What was changed Key Summary Category OCRNET-567 Added support for text recognition from images provided as an array of Aspose.Drawing.Color objects. New feature OCRNET-565 Added support for text recognition from images provided as an array of bytes.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This article contains a summary of recent changes, enhancements and bug fixes in Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.7 (July 2022) release.
GPU version: 21.6.0
What was changed Key Summary Category n/a Fixed incompatibility between Aspose.OCR and Aspose.OMR installers. Fix OCRNET-551 Added image noise reduction filter. New feature OCRNET-551 Added image skew correction filter. New feature Public API changes and backwards compatibility This section lists all public API changes introduced in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This article contains a summary of recent changes, enhancements and bug fixes in Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.6 (June 2022) release.
GPU version: 21.6.0
What was changed Key Summary Category OCRNET-465 Replaced System.Drawing with Aspose.Drawing to improve performance and cross-platform support. Enhancement OCRNET-513 Added a new detection mode for better identification and recognition of tabular structures. Enhancement OCRNET-517</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.5 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.5
GPU version: 21.6.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRNET-506 Extend the languages enum Enhancement OCRNET-504 Integrate the Cyrillic model Enhancement OCRNET-508 Extend fields for Json ouput format Enhancement OCRNET-503 Add xml output format Enhancement OCRNET-499 Fast recognition method Enhancement Enhancements added support for cyrillic alphabet and belorussian, bulgarian, ukrainian, kazakh, russian, serbian languages added ability to get result in XML or JSON file format added fast recognition method Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API added method string RecognizeImageFast(string fullPath) to the AsposeOcr class added method string GetJson(bool isReadable = false) to the RecognitionResult class added method string GetXml() to the RecognitionResult class Removed APIs All methods of the previous release are supported.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.4
GPU version: 21.6.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRNET-493 Implement algorithm for improved .xlsx file creation (placement of result by cells) Enhancement OCRNET-494 Implement algorithm for improved .txt file creation (placement of result by position) Enhancement OCRNET-486 Extend the enum AreasType with value WORDS and add the ability to get words coordinates as a result Enhancement OCRNET-491 Implement the ability to save recognition result as a PDF in MemoryStream Enhancement OCRNET-490 Implement the ability to load PDF from MemoryStream Enhancement OCRNET-495 Test ONNX runtime library new releases Enhancement Enhancements improved algorithm for XLSX files creation improved algorithm for TXT files creation added ability to recognize PDF from stream added ability to save result as the file stream added AreasType.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.3 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.3
GPU version: 21.6.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRNET-457 Add multipage DJVU input support Enhancement OCRNET-480 Improve the logic of the COMBINE mode for areas recognition Enhancement OCRNET-481 Error converting an PDF to a searchable PDF Bugfix Enhancements added support for multipage DJVU files fixed PDF creation improved text area detection algorithm Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API added new method List RecognizeDjvu(string fullPath, DocumentRecognitionSettings settings) in public API Removed APIs All methods of the previous release are supported.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.2 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.2
GPU version: 21.6.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRNET-385 Craft text detector integration Enhancement OCRNET-474 Create the combine mode for DSR/CRAFT areas recognition Enhancement OCRNET-471 Test opimized models Enhancement OCRNET-470 Fix image extraction from PDF Bug Enhancements reduced package size added ability to choose mode of areas detection increased recognition speed Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API added new enum DetectAreasMode with fields: DOCUMENT, PHOTO, COMBINED, NONE added property DetectAreasMode to the RecognitionSettings class Removed APIs All methods of the previous release are supported.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.1 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/ocr/net/release-notes/2022/aspose-ocr-for-net-22-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.OCR for .NET 22.1
GPU version: 21.6.0
All Features Key Summary Category OCRNET-456 Add multipage TIFF input support Enhancement Enhancements added ability torecognize multi-page TIFF images Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes New API added method List RecognizeTiff(string fullPath, DocumentRecognitionSettings settings) to the AsposeOcr class Removed APIs All methods of the previous release are supported.</description></item></channel></rss>