<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.PSD for Java 20.9 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for Java 20.9
Key Summary Category PSDJAVA-272 In a specific PSD file, resizing TextLayer breaks the location value Bug PSDJAVA-273 Updating text in given PSD file and saving it changes some layer and many text parameters Bug PSDJAVA-276 Support of Linked Smart objects Feature PSDJAVA-278 Regression: Aspose.PSD 20.8.0 can’t open file Bug PSDJAVA-279 FillLayer are not updated after the creation and can not be rendered correctly Bug PSDJAVA-280 Support of Embedded Smart objects Feature PSDJAVA-282 Support of SoLEResource (Smart Object Layer External resource) Feature Public API Changes Added APIs: F:com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for Java 20.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for Java 20.8
Key Summary Category PSDJAVA-264 Support of SoLdResource (Smart Object Layer Data resource) Feature PSDJAVA-263 Support of PlLdResource (placed layer resource for Smart Object Layer) Feature PSDJAVA-262 Add Object Array and Unit Array structures support: ObAr / UnFl signatures Feature PSDJAVA-265 Underline and strikethrough lost after focusing on the text in file saved with Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for Java 20.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for Java 20.7
Key Summary Category PSDJAVA-231 Support of the adding of Stroke Effect at runtime Feature PSDJAVA-249 Support of lnk2 / lnk3 Resources (Resources of Smart Object Layer) Feature PSDJAVA-247 Change Exception Message on trying to open not supported formats as an image Enhancement PSDJAVA-235 If we save PSD file after the creation of new Layer Group we get Photoshop warning on the file opening.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for Java 20.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for Java 20.6
Key Summary Category PSDJAVA-216 Support of LnkEResource (Resource of Smart Object Layer) Feature PSDJAVA-219 Support of britResource (Resource of Brightness/Contrast Adjustment Layer) Feature PSDJAVA-222 Move DefaultReplacementFont setting into ImageOptionsBase class Enhancement PSDJAVA-217 Resizing PSD files works incorrect if there is a mask in the adjustment layer that has empty bounds Bug PSDJAVA-218 Psd Image with RGB mode 16 bit/channel updates layers only on preview Bug PSDJAVA-220 PSD Layer Mask changes are discarded on save Bug PSDJAVA-221 Incorrect Layer Order after you add Layer Group to empty Layer Group Bug PSDJAVA-223 Exception on loading specific PSD file with the compound LnkE Resource and adobeStockLicenseState property Bug PSDJAVA-224 Saving of AI File to Jpeg2000 Format doesn&amp;rsquo;t work Bug PSDJAVA-225 Layer Group with not PassThrough Blending Mode Is Not Rendered Bug PSDJAVA-226 NullReference Exception when trying to convert particular Psd file to image Bug PSDJAVA-227 OverflowException when trying to open particular Psd file Bug Public API Changes Added APIs: M:com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for Java 20.5 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for Java 20.5
Key Summary Category PSDJAVA-188 Support for document conversion progress Feature PSDJAVA-197 Support of Grayscale ColorMode PSD Image saving with 16 bit per channel Feature PSDJAVA-198 Support of Nvrt Resource (Invert Adjustment Layer Resource) Feature PSDJAVA-200  Support of Layer Masks for Layer Groups Feature PSDJAVA-195 Fix saving PSD image with Grayscale ColorMode 16 bit per channel to 16bit per channel RGB PSD format Bug PSDJAVA-196 Fix saving PSD image with Grayscale ColorMode 16 bit per channel to 8 bit per channel Grayscale PSD format Bug PSDJAVA-199 Text Alignment through ITextPortion doesn&amp;rsquo;t work for right-to-left languages.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for Java 20.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for Java 20.4
Key Summary Category PSDJAVA-156 Support of the &amp;lsquo;Vector Origination Data&amp;rsquo; resource Feature PSDJAVA-171 Support of lclrResource (Sheet color setting) Feature PSDJAVA-157 Support properties from LengthRecord data. (Path operations (boolean operations), index of the shape in the layer, count of the bezier knot records) Feature PSDJAVA-158  Support of Image Section Resource #1010 Background color Feature PSDJAVA-161 Adding of Fill Layers at runtime Feature PSDJAVA-168 Support of Image Section Resource #1009 Border information.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for Java 20.3 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for Java 20.3
Key Summary Category PSDJAVA-133 Convert Adobe Illustrator files into PDFs Feature PSDJAVA-134 Add ability to render different styles in one text layer Feature PSDJAVA-135 Support of Black and White Adjustment Layer Feature PSDJAVA-137 Add support of export AI format (Version 8) to other formats Feature PSDJAVA-138 Support of PassThrough Blending Mode processing (Used for Layer Group Only).</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PSD for Java 20.2 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/psd/java/release-notes/2020/aspose-psd-for-java-20-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PSD for Java 20.2
Key Summary Category PSDJAVA-96 Improvement of ability to render different colors text in Text Layer Feature PSDJAVA-97 Support of clbl resource (Layer resource contains info about Blend clipping elements) Feature PSDJAVA-100 Support of blwh resource (Resource contains Black &amp;amp; White Adjustment Layer Data) Feature PSDJAVA-101 Ability to export Layer Group to Jpeg/Png/Tiff/Gif/Bmp/Jpeg2000/Psd/Psb/Pdf Feature PSDJAVA-105 Support of lspf Resource (Contains settings about Layer Protected setting) Feature PSDJAVA-106 Support of infx resource (Contains data about Blending of interior elements) Feature PSDJAVA-99 Refactoring of PsdImage and Layer to change Transformation behavior (Correct resize/rotate/crop for layer masks if we transform one layer separately) Enhancement PSDJAVA-98 In some globalization settings AI Image raster image can not be opened Bug PSDJAVA-102 After performing the FlipRotate operation on Layer, PSD Image becomes unreadable Bug PSDJAVA-103 System.</description></item></channel></rss>