<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2012 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2012 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 11.10.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-10-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-10-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 11.10.0
Aspose.Words for Java 11.10 Release Notes What&amp;rsquo;s New There are 171 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Gradient fills are exported to PDF now. TOC (Table Of Contents) field update performance dramatically improved. Supported the Object.Attr syntax for both merge fields and tags. Shape handling improved. Text wrapping polygon info read/written. SvgSaveOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 11.9.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-9-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-9-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 11.9.0
Aspose.Words for Java 11.9 Release Notes What&amp;rsquo;s New There are 152 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Many more features supported when rendering DrawingML charts. Borders for &amp;ldquo;conforming&amp;rdquo; paragraphs are exported to HTML correctly. It is possible to specify image size now when inserting images during mail merge. Significant improvements to layout of floating tables when converting to PDF and XPS.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 11.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 11.8.0
There are 164 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Improved EMF+ rendering (Embedded Metafiles, Curve Drawing Records); Metafile rendering speed optimized;Supported RTL text during mail merge; Supported rendering OOXML Charts. For a list of changes to the public API in this release refer to the following article in the documentation.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 11.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 11.7.0
There are 212 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Page BorderArt rendering implemented;Supported rendering of EMF metafiles embedded in WMF metafiles (special metafiles format);Improved printing speed; Improved font substitution according to default registry values; Fixed a problem with incorrect image rotation in PDF export;Fixed page size detection while printing; Fixed problem with CMYK images being not rendered; Fixed rendering problem with gradient &amp;ldquo;from center&amp;rdquo; fill in WordArt shapes; Fixed rendering problem with super-scripted underlined text.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 11.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 11.6.0
There are 120 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. Most notable are:
Revision public API ready; Support for Hidden table rows;Improved handling of Alternate content; Different default style templates for 2003/2007 documents; Significant improvement of table width handling; Numerous improvements in TOC update; TOC now looks identical to MS Word in almost all test cases; Child fields (including SET) located in the false argument of the IF field are not updated anymore (like MS Word does); Nearly 30 improvements and bug fixes across AW model and flow formats.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 11.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 11.5.0
There are 143 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. Most notable are:
Added plaintext import format (TXT). Formatting of paragraphs and lists is supported; Support for reading and importing of AltChunk content (DOCX) into document model; Support for reading/writing MailMerge settings in RTF; Better validation of AW generated DOCX documents through OpenXML SDK 2.0; Office Math formulas are preserved during DOCX&amp;gt;DOC&amp;gt;DOCX and DOCX&amp;gt;WML&amp;gt;DOCX roundtrip scenarios; Table/row revisions are supported in DOCX; Improvements in table width handling for HTML and PDF; Added option to specify zoom factor and fit type in rendered PDF documents (see PdfSaveOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 11.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 11.4.0
What&amp;rsquo;s new There are 133 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. Most notable are: Implemented embedded EMF+ metafiles rendering;Implemented font style simulation while rendering to fixed page formats;Improved rendering of gray colors to PDF for proper printing;Improved PDF A1/B compatibility;Improved EMF rendering.
New features WORDSJAVA-451
WORDSJAVA-499 Open password protected documents.
WORDSNET-1770 Image inserted by Aspose.Words appears with border in OpenOffice.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 11.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 11.3.0
What&amp;rsquo;s new
There are 133 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. Most notable changes are:
OfficeMath is rendered and supported in almost all formats; MathML import in ODT is supported; Floating tables rendering improvements; Table formatting revisions are supported in DOCX and WML; Performance improvements for the PAGE field update; Support for some EMF+ rendering; Signature line shapes are supported.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 11.2.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 11.2.0
There are 152 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. Most notable changes are:
Math equations can be imported/exported to RTF; Move revisions are supported; New “mustache” templating engine syntax is supported; Performance improvements for large documents; Detailed documentation about what features are supported in each document format; Linked textboxes are supported in layout and rendering; Subsetting of OpenType fonts with PostScript outlines in rendering.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 11.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 11.1.0
Aspose.Words for Java 11.1 Release Notes
What&amp;rsquo;s New There are 118 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. Most notable changes are:</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for Java 11.0.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-0-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/java/release-notes/2012/aspose-words-for-java-11-0-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for Java 11.0.0
Aspose.Words for Java 11.0 Release Notes
What&amp;rsquo;s New There are 80 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. Most notable changes are:
New public element in the Model: AbsolutePositionTab (WORDSNET-2932) support for DOCX and RTF provided. Linked textboxes (WORDSNET-616) supported in DOC, DOCX, WML. A number of improvements in handling of RTF control words. Around two dozen of fixes and resiliency code improvements across flow formats.</description></item></channel></rss>