<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 20.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 20.12.
Supported Platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows x64 (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows x86 (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). New Features and Enhancements Key Summary Category SLIDESNET-33574 Creating presentation from PDF Feature SLIDESNET-33808 Support for converting PDF to PPT/PPTX Feature SLIDESNET-42160 Reduce fonts size when converting to HTML with embedded resources Enhancement Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-2413 Use Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 20.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 20.11.
Supported Platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows x64 (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows x86 (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). New Features and Enhancements Key Summary Category SLIDESNET-36008 Support to verify the presentation password Feature SLIDESNET-42201 Ability to test presentation password to open Feature SLIDESNET-38917 Ability to test presentation password to modify Feature SLIDESNET-42020 Support for Map type chart in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 20.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 20.10.
Supported Platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). New Features and Enhancements Key Summary Category SLIDESNET-41409 Support for representing Autoshape text as curve Feature SLIDESNET-42099 Make IChartData.SetRange() method workable for all chart types Enhancement SLIDESNET-41960 Add DefaultRegularFont property to NotesCommentsLayoutingOptions Feature SLIDESNET-35920 WordArt effects editing API Feature Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-2411 Use Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 20.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 20.9.
Supported Platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). New Features and Enhancements Key Summary Category SLIDESNET-42081 Id attribute generating support for the individual tspan in SVG Enhancement Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-2409 Use Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 20.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 20.8.
Supported platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). New Features and Enhancements Key Summary Category SLIDESNET-41864 SketchStyle property support Feature SLIDESNET-42091 Support to Redact text in Aspose.Slides Feature SLIDESNET-42044 Support for GetRange() method for chart data Feature Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-2410 Use Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 20.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 20.7.
Supported platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). New Features and Enhancements Key Summary Category SLIDESNET-41954 Convert Mathematival Text to MathML Format Feature SLIDESNET-38137 Extract equation from ppt to LaTeX Feature SLIDESNET-34154 Support for rotation options for line shape Feature SLIDESNET-41947 SVG image rendered as PNG image in generated PDF Feature SLIDESNET-41591 Automatic wrapped text exported with line breaks in PDF Enhancement Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-2483 Improve thumbnails rendering quality (v20.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 20.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 20.6.
Supported platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). New Features and Enhancements SLIDESNET-33764 Support for Open Type Font (OTF) in Aspose.Slides Feature SLIDESNET-41930 Pptx to Html: Slide converted to PNG image when NotesPosition is set Enhancement SLIDESNET-41703 Text failed to extract in generated presentation Enhancement SLIDESNET-41702 Can&amp;rsquo;t extract all text from slides Enhancement SLIDESNET-41892 Faulty link in web view of PDF file Enhancement SLIDESNET-41509 Conversion to PDF - accessibility standards Feature SLIDESNET-41023 PDF/UA compliance support Feature SLIDESNET-40996 Tagged PDF export Feature SLIDESNET-37215 getAllTextBoxes not getting text from table Enhancement Other Improvements and Changes SLIDESCPP-2460 Improve thumbnails rendering quality (v20.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 20.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 20.5.
Supported platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). New Features and Enhancements Key Summary Category SLIDESNET-38923 Feature to identify read-protected and write-protected presentations Feature  SLIDESNET-41786 Add the ability to validate password to modify Feature SLIDESNET-37280 Support for Mathematical Equations (OMML) Feature SLIDESNET-40011 Align Multiple shapes in one line Feature SLIDESNET-38545 Get real table row height, after the long text is added to cell Enhancement SLIDESNET-41621 Importing Excel EMF image has broken aspect ratio Enhancement Other Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-2209 Use Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 20.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 20.4
Supported platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). Key Summary Category SLIDESNET-37623 Add the possibility to specify PDF/A-1a compliance Feature SLIDESNET-41140 Add OpenDocument Flat XML Presentation (.fodp) file format support Feature SLIDESNET-36525 Support for using formula recalculated cells in charting Feature SLIDESNET-41757 PP2019 - &amp;ldquo;read-only recommended&amp;rdquo; Presentation Feature SLIDESNET-41748 Different line spacing of text Enhancement SLIDESCPP-1716 Implement Tiff pixel format support Enhancement SLIDESCPP-1715 Implement Tiff compression types support Enhancement SLIDESCPP-1714 Implement DPI handling for Tiff format Enhancement SLIDESCPP-2208 Use Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 20.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 20.3
Supported platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-2207 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 20.3 features Enhancement SLIDESNET-41551 Keep the sequence of numbered list that has NumberedBulletStartWith Enhancement SLIDESCPP-2309 Improve thumbnails rendering quality (20.3) Enhancement SLIDESCPP-2207 Use Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 20.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 20.2
Supported platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++). Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang). Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-2206 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 20.2 features Enhancement SLIDESNET-41674 Extremely slow PPT to PDF Conversion Enhancement SLIDESNET-40977 Support for getting size of paragaph and portion inside table cell text frame Feature SLIDESNET-36546 Update custom document properties directly on the source document Feature SLIDESCPP-2232 Fix getting remote images with using WebRequest class Enhancement Public API Changes IPortion::GetRect() method has been added IPortion::GetRect() method has been added.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Slides for CPP 20.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/slides/cpp/release-notes/2020/aspose-slides-for-cpp-20-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Slides for C++ 20.1
Supported Platforms Aspose.Slides for C++ for Windows (Microsoft Visual C++) Aspose.Slides for C++ for Linux (Clang) Key Summary Category SLIDESCPP-2173 Use Aspose.Slides for .NET 20.1 features Feature SLIDESNET-41387 Changing default font when saving presentation Feature SLIDESNET-41601 Support of SHA1/1K checksum type for ODP/OTP presentations Enhancement SLIDESNET-41605 Support of SHA1 key generation algorithm for ODP/OTP presentations Enhancement SLIDESNET-41372 Descriptive exception message when opening password-protected ODP/OTP presentations Enhancement SLIDESCPP-2124 ArgumentException on exporting ODP to PPTX Bug Public API Changes ISaveOptions::set_DefaultRegularFont() and ISaveOptions::get_DefaultRegularFont() methods have been added A new methods set_DefaultRegularFont() and get_DefaultRegularFont() have been added to ISaveOptions interface and SaveOptions abstract class.</description></item></channel></rss>