<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2013 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2013 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.6.0</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.6.0
We are pleased to share a new version of Aspose.PDF for .NET with following improvements.
New Features PDFNEWNET-20927 Save PDF as .eps PDFNEWNET-35889 PDF to EPS Support PDFNEWNET-33410 Convert PDF file to SVG image PDFNEWNET-33541 PDF to Excel worksheet conversion Enhancements PDFNEWNET-34704 BindHTML method should support Stream object PDFNEWNET-35322 PDF to DOC - Blue box should not appear around the text PDFNEWNET-35609 PDF to HTMl: to specify folder for saving PDFNEWNET-35658 Add option to compress the SVG files PDFNEWNET-35890 HorizontalAlignment property should exist in TextState class Exceptions PDFNEWNET-30281 NullReferenceException is occurring when converting XML file into PDF PDFNEWNET-35702 Exception while filling data in form field PDFNEWNET-35745 NullReferenceException when adding watermark to PDF file PDFNEWNET-35743 Text Stamp is throwing NullReferenceException with regional settings other than US Bugs</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.5.0</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.5.0
We are pleased to share a new version of Aspose.PDF for .NET with following improvements.
New Features PDFNEWNET-18920 Convert PDF to ePUB PDFNEWNET-29282 Convert Dynamic XFA to PDF format PDFNEWNET-34813 Convert XFA form to Image format PDFNEWNET-34933 Checking success of a print Job PDFNEWNET-34495 Specify PDF page when viewing the document Enhancements PDFNEWNET-35572 Implement tables import from different sources PDFNEWNET-35657 Optimize SVG file generation PDFNEWNET-35672 PDF to HTML: specify folder for SVG/other image resources(PNG,JPEG etc) PDFNEWNET-35761 Introduce Alignment.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.4.0</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.4.0
We are pleased to share a new version of Aspose.PDF for .NET with following improvements.
New Features PDFNEWNET-13041 WinForms control wrapping PdfViewer PDFNEWNET-13042 Web Control wrapping PdfViewer PDFNEWNET-35287 EPUB to PDF conversion PDFNEWNET-35612 Support Wordwrap in TextStamp Enhancements PDFNEWNET-33812 SetPageSize Method is not well defined PDFNEWNET-35663 Export PDF file pages to JPEGs using MediaBox bounds PDFNEWNET-35521 Image extraction from PDF file takes too much time PDFNEWNET-35723 DOM output is 10 times in size as compate to Generator namespace Exceptions PDFNEWNET-34891 Insufficient data for an image message appears when adding bmp image PDFNEWNET-35649 ArgumentNullException when reading form field PDFNEWNET-34115 Wrong format of PDF String Exception when loading PDF file PDFNEWNET-34162 Exception is occurring when trying to extract text from PDF file PDFNEWNET-35482 NullReferenceException when adding text to PDF file PDFNEWNET-35525 OutofMemoryException while trying to extract text from large PDF PDFNEWNET-34568 Secured PDF (using Certificate Security) gives exception when using PdfFileInfo PDFNEWNET-35605 Incorrect linearization information being returned Bugs</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.3.0</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.3.0
We are pleased to share a new version of Aspose.PDF for .NET with following improvements.
New Features PDFNEWNET-11337 Repair non-standard PDF files and convert to valid PDF files PDFNEWNET-33486 PDF to DOC conversion using Streams PDFNEWNET-33864 Add TOC in existing PDF documents PDFNEWNET-35481 Implement margin support for TextParagraph PDFNEWNET-33544 Allow to pass font as a stream Enhancements PDFNEWNET-34786 Text to PDF is slow or hangs CPU PDFNEWNET-35357 Performance issue when building PDF with HTML tags PDFNEWNET-35520 Slow Performance when creating big Text in PDF file PDFNEWNET-34930 TXT to PDF: Conversion process is taking too much time Exceptions PDFNEWNET-33701 OutOfMemory exception is occurring when creating large PDF PDFNEWNET-35226 HTML to PDF - StackOverFlow is occurring during conversion process PDFNEWNET-35259 PDF to XPS - OutOfMemoryException during conversion PDFNEWNET-35300 NullReferenceException on PageEditor.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.2.0</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-2-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-2-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.2.0
We are pleased to share a new version of Aspose.PDF for .NET with following improvements.
New Features PDFNEWNET-28774 Insert image in a searchable PDF and retain the PDF as searchable PDFNEWNET-32457 Define an outer color of the text when using RenderingMode.FillStrokeText PDFNEWNET-34142 Calculating bbox for a character PDFNEWNET-35107 Extract text from particular page region PDFNEWNET-35413 SAASPDF-70 image resource Support deleting images PDFNEWNET-35277 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.1.0</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.1.0
We are pleased to share a new version of Aspose.PDF for .NET with following improvements.
New Features PDFNEWNET-14497 Support PDF to DOCX Conversion PDFNEWNET-29755 Convert normal PDF to searchable PDF PDFNEWNET-32453 Create Searchable (Indexed) PDF documents PDFNEWNET-35199 SVG to PDF - get source SVG dimensions PDFNEWNET-14493 Implement Tagged PDF to XML conversion Enhancements PDFNEWNET-33729 PDF Text Extraction Not Respecting White-space PDFNEWNET-35210 PdfPageStamp should support the feature to set its dimensions Bugs</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.0.0</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-0-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-8-0-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PDF for .NET 8.0.0
We are pleased to share a new version of Aspose.PDF for .NET with following improvements.
New Features PDFNEWNET-22463 Disable paging in PDF document PDFNEWNET-35204 Update Validate(..) method to take Stream object as an argument PDFNEWNET-35200 Examples dashboard with Aspose.PDF for .NET Exceptions PDFNEWNET-35190 PDF to PDF/A-1b: Exception is occurring during conversion PDFNEWNET-35019 InvalidOperationException raised while updating linkannotation PDFNEWNET-34481 Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 7.9.0</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-7-9-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-7-9-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PDF for .NET 7.9.0
We are pleased to share a new version of Aspose.PDF for .NET with following improvements.
New Features PDFNEWNET-35042 Creation of File annotation without icon PDFNEWNET-35061 Implement FloatingBox class in Aspose.PDF namespace PDFNEWNET-33543 Introduce a setting to define any folder as a fonts storage PDFNEWNET-34380 Support for underline property in TextState (Text Stamp) Enhancements
PDFNEWNET-34666 Poor performance (speed) converting PDF to Image PDFNEWNET-34970 Pdf to doc conversion, resultant file size increases ~6 times PDFNEWNET-35032 Truncate contents of Floating box, as per box size Exceptions PDFNEWNET-33180 Invalid Operation Exception during PDF to TIFF conversion PDFNEWNET-34450 Object Reference Exception thrown on Saving the document PDFNEWNET-34686 System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 7.8.0</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-7-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-7-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.PDF for .NET 7.8.0
We are pleased to share a new version of Aspose.PDF for .NET with following improvements.
New Features PDFNEWNET-29340 PDF to PostScript conversion PDFNEWNET-32458 Support Image collections PDFNEWNET-34523 Set page thumbnail numbering PDFNEWNET-34634 Remove Header and Footer from PDF file PDFNEWNET-34932 How to get document zoom value/factor PDFNEWNET-34379 TextState.ForgroundColor property does not support CMYK colors PDFNEWNET-34381 TextState.BackgroundColor property does not support CMYK colors Enhancements</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 7.7.0</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-7-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2013/aspose-pdf-for-net-7-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for [ Aspose.PDF for .NET 7.7.0|https://releases.aspose.com/pdf/net/new-releases/aspose.pdf-for.net-7.7.0/]
We are pleased to share a new version of Aspose.PDF for .NET with following improvements.
New Features PDFNEWNET-33612 PDF to Word does not treat header and footer as Word Header and Footer PDFNEWNET-34042 Specify Minimum Height for Row PDFNEWNET-34055 Adding Table in Footer of Existing PDF file PDFNEWNET-34304 Render text as a text, but not vector graphics PDFNEWNET-34589 Add Javascript to Page Action Enhancements</description></item></channel></rss>