<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/net/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/net/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.PUB for .NET 19.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-pub-for-net-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-pub-for-net-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PUB for .NET 19.12.
Improvements and Changes This release improves the API functionality by introducing new features, enhancements and bug fixes. Key improvements include:
Conversion into PDF format for raster graphic data has been implemented. Added functionality to edit metadata of PUB files Improvement in Error Handling Key Summary Category PUBNET-113 Implement conversion into PDF format for raster graphic data New Feature PUBNET-112 Add functionality for ability to edit metadata New Feature PUBNET-111 Improve error handling Enhancement PUBNET-67 PUB to PDF - API name is incorrect in Producer field Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes Added APIs Methods Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PUB for .NET 19.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-pub-for-net-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pub/net/release-notes/2019/aspose-pub-for-net-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.PUB for .NET 19.10.
Aspose.PUB for .NET has been launched. It is a set of libraries to read and convert PUB files to PDF file format. It facilitates .NET application developers to work with the electronic publication file format (.pub) without the need of installing it on any server or client application. With Aspose.PUB for .NET, you purely focus on your business logic instead of going into the underlying details of the .</description></item></channel></rss>