<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Page for Java 19.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Page for Java 19.12.
This release is sort of a maintenance release where internal implementation of the API has been improved for better performance.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for Java 19.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-11-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes information of Aspose.Page for Java 19.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PAGEJAVA-61 Output XPS is unable to open after adding image Bug PAGEJAVA-71 Unable to use InsertGlyph() method to add text inside XPS Bug PAGEJAVA-77 Exception during pdf rendering under Linux environment Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for Java 19.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Page for Java 19.10.
Key Summary Category PAGEJAVA-58 Exception java.io.FileNotFoundException: /var/task (Is a directory) converting PS to EPS. Bug PAGEJAVA-62-67 Unable to convert EPS to PDF - An Exception is thrown. Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for Java 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Page for Java 19.9
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PAGEJAVA-57 Port Aspose.Page for .Net 19.9 to Java New Feature Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes No Changes</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for Java 19.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Page for Java 19.8
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PAGEJAVA-52 Port Aspose.Page for .Net 19.8 to Java New Feature PAGEJAVA-49 Lines appears over XPS document after adding image Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for Java 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Page for Java 19.7
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PAGEJAVA-44 Port Aspose.Page for .NET 19.7 to Java Enhancement PAGEJAVA-38 XPS to PDF - NullPointerException exception occurs Bug PAGEJAVA-37 XPS to PDF - API generates a corrupted PDF file Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes See the list of any changes made to the public API such as added, renamed, removed or deprecated members as well as any non-backward compatible change made to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Page for Java 19.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/page/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-page-for-java-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains Release Notes for Aspose.Page for Java 19.6
We at Aspose are honoured to announce first version Aspose.Page for Java 19.6. Aspose.Page is a solution for manipulating PDL formats. The first version of Aspose.Page can:
Create, edit and save XPS document Convert XPS document to PDF and image Convert PostScript (PS) and Encapsulated PostScript (EPS) files to PDF and image XPS Features Create and edit XPS document Add or remove pages of XPS document Work with canvases, paths and glyphs elements Create vector graphics shapes (Path element) using a set of primitives (elliptical arcs, Bezier curve segments and straight line segments) Create text strings (Glyphs element) Group elements (Canvas element) to manipulate a group as a whole Manipulate the appearance of graphics and text strings Use brushes of different types including solid color brush, image brush, visual brush etc Specify colors in different color spaces including sRGB, scRGB and any space based on ICC profile Work with multiple documents inside an XPS document Preserve print tickets in opened XPS document if any Add default print tickets into new XPS document or an opened one if there’re no tickets in it Perform cross-package operations, e.</description></item></channel></rss>