<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2018 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 18.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-note-for-java-18-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-note-for-java-18-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Note for Java 18.11.
Major Features Improved rendering when saving *.one documents to PDF and image formats Features and Improvements Key Summary Category NOTENET-2267 Wrong page size is returned when Page.SizeType is set to SizeByContent New Feature NOTENET-2671 Refactor AppendChildFirst/AppendChildLast/etc exception messages for Document class Bug NOTENET-2674 Investigate bug in InsertChildrenRange Bug NOTENET-2319 Font&amp;rsquo;s size in PDF from Microsoft OneNote and Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 18.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-note-for-java-18-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-note-for-java-18-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Note for Java 18.9.
Major Features Managing font&amp;rsquo;s environment for a document Inserting of pages functionality Features and Improvements Key Summary Category NOTENET-2633 Default font for Note documents New Feature NOTENET-2629 How copy page from one document to another to certain position New Feature NOTENET-2639 Fix the bug with saving as html: style&amp;rsquo;s saving is broken Bug NOTEJAVA-501 OneNote to Html: Content upside down and Data crossing table Bug NOTEJAVA-500 OneNote to HTML: Table turned upside down Bug NOTEJAVA-499 SaveFormat.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 18.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-note-for-java-18-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-note-for-java-18-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Note for Java 18.7.
Major Features Saving hyperlinks from images in PDF Features and Improvements Key Summary Category NOTENET-2253 Add support for hyperlinks in images while converting to PDF New Feature NOTENET-2257 Page tab shows &amp;ldquo;Untitled page&amp;rdquo; for All New Page Insertion greater than one page Bug NOTENET-2263 Images and text notes cannot be moved in OneNote application after saving a document by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 18.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-note-for-java-18-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-note-for-java-18-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information of Aspose.Note for Java 18.5.
Major Features Per page saving in HTML format Support of new license type: license for conholdate.com Features and Improvements
Key Summary Category NOTENET-2450 Add per page saving mode to Aspose.HTML New Feature NOTENET-2546 Implement support of new license type New Feature NOTENET-2396 Exception raised while extracting images without applying license Bug Public API and Backward Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 18.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-note-for-java-18-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-note-for-java-18-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Note for Java 18.3.
Major Features Image&amp;rsquo;s compression in PDF Evaluation&amp;rsquo;s mode restrictions are reworked Features and Improvements Key Summary Category NOTENET-1991 Make evaluation mode limitations more clear New Feature NOTENET-2254 Add option to compress pictures while converting to PDF. New Feature NOTENET-2268 Image.Extension property returns wrong value for gif images Bug NOTENET-2264 Wrong page margin values are returned Bug NOTENET-2241 Large size PDF generated from one note file as compared to MS OneNote Bug NOTENET-2337 Crash while trying to clone Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Note for Java 18.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-note-for-java-18-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/note/java/release-notes/2018/aspose-note-for-java-18-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.Note for Java 18.1 version.
Features and Improvements Saving to stream in HTML format Features and Improvements
Key Summary Category NOTENET-2247 Support saving to stream in html format  New Feature NOTEJAVA-305 Add support of saving to file in html format  New Feature NOTEJAVA-10 Add support for saving to HTML format  New Feature NOTEJAVA-234 ArgumentNullException Parameter name: trueTypeFont Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Public type added Description com.</description></item></channel></rss>