<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2019 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.12.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSJAVA-983 Implement a feature to set &amp;ldquo;Last Saved on&amp;rdquo; of a baseline while creating a file New Feature TASKSNET-2482 Implement a feature to add tasks columns on each exported page New Feature TASKSNET-3579 Enhance task filtering logic for Gantt, Task Usage, and Task Sheet views Enhancement TASKSNET-3517 Enhance XML to MPP copying procedure of view information Enhancement TASKSNET-3289 Enhance reading of linked OLE object properties Enhancement TASKSJAVA-981 Fix exception while reading MPP file Bug TASKSNET-3463 Fix overflow exception on reading MPP file Bug TASKSNET-3460 Fix overflow exception on loading MPP file Bug TASKSNET-3459 Fix generation of TDs for Cost resources Bug TASKSNET-3458 Fix excel unreadable error after mpp conversion Bug TASKSNET-3455 Fix tasks in MSP 2003 file corrupted after resaving Bug TASKSNET-3451 Fix missing resource GUID after resave Bug TASKSNET-3444 Fix crash when saving MPP as XML due to Formula-Column Bug TASKSNET-3441 Fix exception on loading protected MPP file Bug TASKSNET-3426 Fix reading of Tsk.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.10.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-1904 Render comments when saving as image, HTML or PDF New Feature TASKSNET-3142 Implement reading of projects using &amp;ldquo;ReadProjectCoreData&amp;rdquo; internal API of Project Server New Feature TASKSJAVA-983 Set &amp;ldquo;Last Saved on&amp;rdquo; of Baseline while creating a file New Feature TASKSNET-2511 Add check for OutlineCodeId uniqueness Enhancement TASKSNET-1639 Provision of a facility to check if the schedule has a conflict with other Enhancement TASKSNET-3187 Fix ArgumentOutOfRangeException when rendering Gantt chart Bug TASKSNET-3151 Fix incorrect reading of Tsk.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-9-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.9.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSJAVA-890 Milestone tasks that contain resource are not updating %Complete value Bug TASKSNET-3290 Fix rounding error in the actual calculation Bug TASKSJAVA-977 Fix generation of time-phased data Bug</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.7.
Features Implemented resource prefix for nested resources. All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-2992 Implement resource prefix for nested resources New Feature TASKSNET-3075 Add validation of SaveFileFormat.SVG save option Enhancement TASKSNET-2917 Aspose.Tasks saves pages as an image without headers and footers Enhancement TASKSNET-2600 Include header information in the PDF output file Enhancement TASKSNET-3104 Fix NullReferenceException when trying to save project without GanttChart view.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.6.
Features The support of Microsoft Project 2019 has been added. All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-2684 Implement the support of MS Project 2019 New Feature TASKSNET-3032 Fix using of CssStylePrefix for special case Bug TASKSNET-3028 Fix exception ‘The difference between start and finish date cannot be more than 50 years.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.5.
Features The support of Microsoft Project Online has been added. The support of setting CSS prefix for HTML export has been added. The feature to set custom date format while exporting to PDF format has been implemented. Enhanced exceptions which are throwing while access to Primavera DB. All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-2777 Implement the Adding of Page Prefixes in CSS Classes when Saving MS Project into HTML New Feature TASKSNET-2150 Support for Microsoft Office 365 Project Online Service New Feature TASKSNET-2740 Implement an informative exception when trying to open a non-existing project from Primavera DB Enhancement TASKSNET-2623 Implement a feature to set custom date format while exporting to PDF format Enhancement TASKSNET-2964 Fix extra text in the hyperlink note after the MPP file being resaved Bug TASKSNET-2957 Fix missing hyperlinks after the MPP file being resaved Bug TASKSNET-2956 Fix error when project with incorrect formula is saved to XML Bug TASKSNET-2916 Fix reading of resources in MspResourceMapper and MpdResourceMapper Bug TASKSNET-2905 Fix schedule differences after the MPP file being resaved Bug TASKSJAVA-748 The Chinese timestamp of the Project file is displayed in English after being exported to PDF Bug TASKSNET-2519 Fix displaying of lookup values after the MPP file being resaved Bug TASKSJAVA-909 Multipage HTML export saves files into %TEMP% instead of the CWD Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes The following public types were added: Description com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.4.
All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-2915 Exception in Aspose.Tasks is thrown on project saving Bug TASKSNET-2909 Fix writing/reading of BackgroundColor = Automatic in TextStyles Bug TASKSNET-2898 AT throws InvalidCastException while reading project from Project Server 2016 Bug TASKSNET-2653 Remove a set of actual fields while assigning the resource Bug TASKSJAVA-876 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/java/release-notes/2019/aspose-tasks-for-java-19-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.Tasks for Java 19.3.
Major Features The long-awaited feature of style customization for custom task fields has been implemented. This release includes enhancements and a bunch of fixed bugs connected to PDF export. Also in this release, we made some important enhancements in order to implement better support of custom timephased data for MPP/XML files. All Changes Key Summary Issue Type TASKSNET-2816 Implement a feature to customize styles of custom fields New Feature TASKSNET-2860 Fix layout of Gantt table in generated PDF Enhancement TASKSNET-2829 Add calculation of ConstraintDate for all calculation modes Enhancement TASKSNET-2825 Fix the calculation of peak value while adding a custom timephased data in automatic mode.</description></item></channel></rss>