<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.12.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-45358 Obtain CSS separately from HTML markup when exporting to HTML using streams New Feature  CELLSNET-45697 Implement Cell.FormulaLocal similar to Microsoft Interop FormulaLocal New Feature  CELLSNET-45801 Support for Office-Add-Ins in Excel to PDF rendering New Feature  CELLSNET-45796 Smart Markers - How to auto populate data to second worksheet if data is too large and cannot be inserted into a single sheet  New Feature  CELLSNET-45791 Update &amp;ldquo;Keep change history&amp;rdquo; when Sharing Workbook New Feature  CELLSNET-45746 Text in the cells are overlapping with other cells on Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.11.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-45748 XmlMapQuery like functionality needed as available in MS Excel New Feature  CELLSNET-45747 Associated property needed for XMLMaps to get the RootElementName for the map New Feature  CELLSNET-45709 Scale becomes smaller - Fonts issue New Feature  CELLSNET-45743 Protect shared workbook - Set or change password New Feature  CELLSNET-45737 Support PasteType for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.10.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-45695 Set number format for cells in Chart&amp;rsquo;s Data Table New Feature  CELLSNET-45666 Get SheetId field of Excel worksheet New Feature  CELLSNET-45664 Reading and writing External connection of XLSB file  New Feature  CELLSNET-45660 Sheet to Image rendering - Alignment issue for Asian fonts Enhancement  CELLSNET-45408 Value disappears or changes color when convert to PDF  Bug  CELLSNET-45696 Slicer is not moving down in the sheet when inserting rows Bug  CELLSNET-45675 Error calculating the formulas (involving &amp;ldquo;SUMPRODUCT&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;TRANSPOSE&amp;rdquo;) Bug  CELLSNET-45651 TextBox size changes when using Chinese font in the workbook in rendering to PDF Bug  CELLSNET-45678 Partially missing characters when converting to image Bug  CELLSNET-45667 Trendline labels are not updated in MS Excel when we manually change the source value in the cells Bug  CELLSNET-45620 Color and interval between scale is different for 3D chart  Bug  CELLSNET-45397 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.9.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-45614 Determine which Stack Size is needed for a certain Workbook New Feature  CELLSNET-45649 Format the custom Label&amp;rsquo;s font and its cell with Smart Markers  New Feature  CELLSNET-44353 Control loading of external resources in MS Excel workbook New Feature  CELLSNET-40787 Lose Track Changes after conversion (XLS &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; XLSM) New Feature  CELLSNET-45607 Show Cell comment as Excel Tooltip - Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.8.
Key  Summary  Category  CELLSNET-45357  Option to disable downlevel-revealed type of conditional comments during export to HTML  New Feature  CELLSNET-45330  Render comments when saving as image, HTML or PDF  New Feature  CELLSNET-45014  Support style.xml of the chart since office 2013  New Feature  CELLSNET-45501  Set Default Style of GridDesktop similar to Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.7.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-45437 Support errors and Boolean value in Russian locale in Excel to PDF rendering New Feature  CELLSNET-45456 Reading cells&amp;rsquo; data, formula and style from numbers file  New Feature  CELLSNET-45483 Support to change the row index start value to 0 (instead of 1) in Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.6.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-45356 Enquote all attribute values in HTML New Feature  CELLSNET-45394 Support new functions of Office 365 New Feature  CELLSNET-45348 Support Table as the data source of the chart New Feature  CELLSNET-45317 Remove older Web.config settings of Aspose.Cells.GridWeb like force script_path and forcepath  New Feature  CELLSNET-45370 Exception message is wrong - The count of Hyperlinks cannot be larger than 66530 Enhancement  CELLSNET-45391 Excel footer in the output PDF is not italic - it should be Arial 9 and italic Enhancement  CELLSNET-45328 Copy the PageSetup settings from the existing worksheet  Enhancement  CELLSNET-45345 Some part of subscript labels are cut and shifted to a lower line Bug  CELLSNET-45344 Subscript text is displaced to the right a bit - Excel to PDF Rendering Bug  CELLSNET-44595 Output Excel file is not good when converting an HTML file to Excel file format Bug  CELLSNET-44596 Output Excel file is not good when converting an HTML file to Excel file format - I Bug CELLSNET-45409 Exception thrown after multiple loading and saving an XLS file Bug  CELLSNET-45411 Load Filter causes crash while loading an Excel file Bug  CELLSNET-45405 Using IFERROR with NPER is unable to be processed correctly Bug  CELLSNET-45414 Output PDF should have one page instead of two pages Bug  CELLSNET-45399 Image rendered incorrectly when a cell has Arabic currency name Bug  CELLSNET-45389 Shape of parentheses is rendered wrong in output PDF/image Bug  CELLSNET-45376 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.5.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-41365 Support PDF/A-1a compliance in PdfSaveOptions New Feature  CELLSNET-45347 Remove existing PrinterSettings in Excel file New Feature  CELLSNET-45340 Implement Custom Page Size options for the worksheet  New Feature  CELLSNET-45327 Support exporting HTML cells&amp;rsquo; data to DataTable New Feature  CELLSNET-45316 Support the working of GridWeb when ASP.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.4.0.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-45216 Support &amp;ldquo;Lock project for viewing&amp;rdquo; Protection option in VbaProject Properties New Feature  CELLSNET-44219 Password protect the VBA project New Feature  CELLSNET-45246 Implement Sort Warning feature - Sort anything that looks like a number New Feature  CELLSNET-45278 Function SetColumnHeaderToolTip(int colIndex, string toolTip) missing in newer APIs set - Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.3.0.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-45037 Support Custom Total &amp;amp; Grand Total Labels for Pivot Tables New Feature  CELLSNET-45156 Synchronize the paging of the two grids (Aspose.Cells.GridWeb)  New Feature  CELLSNET-45140 Validate updated cells only and ignore validation of other cells (Aspose.Cells.GridWeb)  New Feature  CELLSNET-45158 Change in pivot data source adds additional LinkSource Enhancement  CELLSNET-45168 The shape is skewed/tilted a bit with its text &amp;ldquo;1&amp;rdquo; position changed Bug  CELLSNET-45163 Text in a shape is inverted while rendering worksheet to image Bug  CELLSNET-45161 Angle of the picture in spreadsheet is slightly different Bug  CELLSNET-45159 Auto shape objects have rendered incorrectly Bug  CELLSNET-45138 PrintArea doesn&amp;rsquo;t manage to transform images correctly Bug  CELLSNET-45136 Boxes are rotated when Excel is converted to PDF  Bug  CELLSNET-45182 Resultant spreadsheet cannot be loaded in Excel without repair Bug  CELLSNET-45143 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.02.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-02-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-02-0-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.02.0.
Key Summary Category CELLSNET-45049 Trim blank rows and columns while exporting spreadsheets to CSV format New Feature  CELLSNET-45069 Bind Worksheet to a Customized Collection object (Aspose.Cells.GridWeb) New Feature  CELLSNET-44787 SortRange doesn&amp;rsquo;t have undo/redo feature (Aspose.Cells.GridDesktop)  New Feature  CELLSNET-44746 Aspose.Cells.GridDesktop: Issue with Undo/Redo function when performing Cut/Copy/Paste New Feature  CELLSNET-44230 Split Panes feature for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Cells for .NET 17.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cells/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-cells-for-net-17-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Key Summary Category CELLSNET-44747 MS Excel 2016 XLSX file containing Waterfall chart cannot be opened via Aspose.Cells APIs New Feature  CELLSNET-44940 Bind Worksheet to a Customized Collection object (Aspose.Cells.GridWeb) New Feature  CELLSNET-44939 Bind Worksheet to a DataSet object at Run Time (Aspose.Cells.GridWeb) New Feature  CELLSNET-44597 Output Excel file is not good when converting an HTML file to Excel file format Enhancement  CELLSNET-44994 Issue with Date format in German locale when rendering an Excel file to PDF Enhancement  CELLSNET-44986 Representation of double numbers in Aspose.</description></item></channel></rss>