<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2017 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.12 release.
Improvements Key Summary Category TASKSNET-1566 Add support for setting a default font when a project is rendering into PDF New Feature TASKSNET-2195 Task notes not saved for template file from MSP 2016 Bug TASKSNET-2184 Resource assignment units raise exception when large value is set Bug TASKSNET-2177 Task duration becomes zero if multiple resources are assigned Bug TASKSNET-2176 Project reading exception while loading the MPP file Bug TASKSNET-2171 AT breaks the showing of GanttBarStyle for manual summary tasks Bug TASKSNET-2145 Resource assignment has incorrect baseline start/finish date Bug TASKSNET-2121 FontFamily not set in MPP Bug TASKSNET-1908 Header text is only changed for the default view Bug Public API and Backwards Incompatible Changes Methods and Properties Added Description Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.11.
Major Features This release of Aspose.Tasks for .NET includes following major features.
Option to set output image quality while saving as JPEG New fill pattern for available MSP 2016 file format All Changes Key Summary Category TASKSNET-2140 Add option to set image quality when saving as JPEG New Feature TASKSNET-2147 Enum GanttBarFillPattern should have value 11 corresponding to fill pattern in MSP 2016 Enhancement TASKSNET-2144 Recalculate() is updating manually scheduled tasks Bug TASKSNET-2137 Wrong finish date calculated for ElapsedDay type duration Bug TASKSNET-2136 Prevent recalculation of manually scheduled tasks Bug TASKSNET-2134 Wrong Actual Duration in MPP file Bug TASKSNET-2108 SplitParts collection misses time span Bug TASKSNET-2091 Sub-tasks not rendered while converting MPX to PdfA1b Bug TASKSNET-2077 Wrong Finish date in XML file Bug TASKSNET-2051 Wrong Percent complete in MPP as compared to XML output Bug TASKSNET-1748 Loading project raises ProjectReadingException Bug TASKSNET-1747 TaskReadingException while reading the MPP file Bug TASKSNET-702 MSP 2010 raises error while updating and saving MPP created by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information about Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.9.
All Changes Key Summary Category TASKSNET-2109 Exception raised while loading the mpp file Bug TASKSNET-2105 ArgumentOutOfRangeException exception if 24 Hours Calendar is set Bug TASKSNET-2104 Program hangs while setting Tsk.Start for a Task Bug TASKSNET-2102 Wrong Actual Finish date in MPP as compared to XML output Bug TASKSNET-2095 Summary task fields are empty Bug TASKSNET-2094 Exception raised while saving MPX as PDF Bug TASKSNET-2093 Child tasks are not rendered in PNG without saving the project first Bug TASKSNET-2092 All values of BarStyle&amp;rsquo;s From and To fields are changed Bug TASKSNET-2090 Loading project file raises Exception Bug TASKSNET-2048 Saving into image by page not working properly Bug TASKSNET-2035 Percent complete not set properly in MPP Bug TASKSNET-1788 Setting Project Start date raises ArgumentOutOfRangeException Bug TASKSNET-1749 Assignment Cost is not displayed for Cost resources in Microsoft Project 2013 Bug TASKSNET-1727 Text extended attribute created by the formula is read as a date by Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes of Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.8.
Major Features This release provides the capability of reading/writing RateScale information for Microsoft Project 2013 onward versions.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category TASKSNET-2046 Add support of RateScale reading/writing for MSP 2013+ New Feature TASKSNET-1965 TasksReadingException while using MspDbSettings Enhancement TASKSNET-2055 Error on adding a resource with 0 units to parent task Bug TASKSNET-2054 ActualFinish of a zero-day milestone task not set properly Bug TASKSNET-2053 MPP with Subproject File causes exception while loading into project Bug TASKSNET-2051 Wrong Percent complete in MPP as compared to XML output Bug TASKSNET-2045 Fix difference in Task duration in MSP 2010 and 2013 Bug TASKSNET-2025 MPP to XLSX: Resultant file doesn&amp;rsquo;t contain any data Bug TASKSNET-1786 ExtendedAttribute Lookup values mixed up for the same task Bug TASKSNET-1775 Lookup extended attribute with CustomFieldType.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes of Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.7.
All Changes Key Summary Category TASKSNET-1818 Add support for text style information. Enhancement TASKSNET-2018 Program hangs while loading MPP into Project Bug TASKSNET-2014 MPP file raises TasksReadingException Bug TASKSNET-1993 MPP file saved by MSP 2016 version 1706 raises exception while loading into Project Bug TASKSNET-1990 An entry with the same key already exists - exception Bug TASKSNET-1989 Exception raised while loading attached MPP Bug TASKSNET-1985 TaskReadingException while loading MPP file Bug TASKSNET-1935 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes of Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.6 version.
Improvements Key Summary Category TASKSNET-1971 Add exception which is thrown when there is no installed printer in OS Bug TASKSNET-1963 Finish date is incorrect for zero duration task using Recalculate Bug TASKSNET-1956 Image from footer is recognized as text Bug TASKSNET-1941 Empty project with one task has incorrectly filled ActualStart, ActualFinish dates Bug TASKSNET-1916 HtmlSaveOptions.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes of Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.5 version.
Improvements Key Summary Category TASKSNET-1918 Tasks with custom timephased data has Percent Complete &amp;gt; 100% and MSP in XML format cannot be imported. Bug TASKSNET-1917 Formulas get corrupted after file save Bug TASKSNET-1905 Loading a MPP file using Aspose.Tasks for .NET throw exception An item with the same key has already been added Bug TASKSNET-1899 Recalculation of project sets percent complete to zero on milestone tasks Bug TASKSNET-1867 Saving Project raises TaskWritingException Bug TASKSNET-1814 Erroneous calendar entry added in XML while converting MSP 2016 MPP Bug TASKSNET-1740 Out of Memory error while saving MPP to PNG Bug TASKSNET-1718 Task duration shown wrong in MSP 2016 as compared to MSP 2010 (.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Tasks for .NET API enables application developers to write code for manipulating Microsoft Project documents without it being installed on the systems. It provides support for Microsoft Project (MPP/XML) as well as Primavera File Formats. Project data can be exported to a number of formats including PDF, PNG, BMP and others.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category TASKSNET-1796 Inconsistent behavior of %Complete in MPP Bug TASKSNET-1792 WBS Codes written to MPP file are not same as Microsoft Project Bug TASKSNET-1769 ArgumentOutOfRangeException is raised when setting task Finish date Bug TASKSNET-1692 Empty timephased data added in XML for type AssignmentWork (.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Tasks for .NET 17.1.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-1-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/tasks/net/release-notes/2017/aspose-tasks-for-net-17-1-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Tasks for .NET API enables application developers to write code for manipulating Microsoft Project documents without it being installed on the systems. It provides support for Microsoft Project (MPP/XML) as well as Primavera File Formats. Project data can be exported to a number of formats including PDF, PNG, BMP and others.
Major Features This month&amp;rsquo;s release includes a simplified method for working with custom fields of a project. This improvement implementation makes it easy to create extended attributes of different types for a project.</description></item></channel></rss>