<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2016 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 16.12 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-16-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-16-12-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for .Net has been updated to version 16.12 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-1830 Convert EMF to WMF Feature IMAGINGNET-1824 ThreadSafe API support stage 1 Feature IMAGINGNET-1669 DNG format support Feature IMAGINGNET-2145 Thread safe API for TIFF images Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2134 Could not read layers in PSD file.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 16.10 - Release notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-16-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-16-10-release-notes/</guid><description>has been updated to version 4.0.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-2048 Creating wmf files by calling Graphics methods (drawImage,drawLine, etc.) Feature IMAGINGNET-1858 Support for WMF for possible conversion to SVG Feature IMAGINGNET-2086 Converting GIF to TIFF is generating incorrect TIFF images Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2079 Emf image differs from C# after saving Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2078 Save() operation for psd file does not update changed layers(including text layers) in application, but on disk all is saved.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 4.0.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-4-0-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-4-0-0-release-notes/</guid><description>has been updated to version 4.0.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-2060 Multiple save of Wmf file produce wrong results Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2036 Aspose.Imaging is not returning correct Height &amp;amp; Width of WMF image Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2028 Static method GetFileFormat of Image class is returning incorrect information Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2025 Updating text in text layers of a file is not generating expected output and also throwing exception Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2003 Incorrect layer names returned from a file with multiple layers and nested layers Enhancement IMAGINGNET-1982 Import from Internal format to WMF Enhancement IMAGINGNET-1981 Out of Memory Error Exception when trying to process image of size 500MB Enhancement IMAGINGNET-1618 Some namespaces are missing descriptions Enhancement Usage examples IMAGINGNET-2037 Integrate metering module to promote new sales model for Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 3.9.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-9-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-9-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for .Net has been updated to version 3.9.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-1971 Support for SAI format New Feature IMAGINGNET-1970 Support for GIMP2 format New Feature IMAGINGNET-1847 Implement ability for adding both vector graphics and bitmap components to Metafile New Feature IMAGINGNET-2021 Converting Djvu to Pdf file contains black pages only instead of image in it Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2018 Djvu extracted pages does not contain colors Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2016 Djvu converted to PDF successfully but unable to open the PDF using Adobe PDF reader Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2007 Emf image export error Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2004 Support for TEXT_AS_SHAPES while converting EMF to SVG format Enhancement IMAGINGNET-2001 Updating text in text layers of a PSD file is not generating expected output and also throwing exception Enhancement IMAGINGNET-1991 Investigate emf/emf+ renderer performance Enhancement IMAGINGNET-1980 Implement support of Icc profiles for Jpeg2000 images Enhancement IMAGINGNET-1892 PSD file has 6 layers while Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 3.8.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-8-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-8-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for .Net has been updated to version 3.8.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-1567 Support Wmf file format New Feature IMAGINGNET-1863 Support for Diacom DCM image format New Feature IMAGINGNET-1855 Conversion of SVG to PNG New Feature IMAGINGNET-1832 Conversion of SVG to JPG New Feature IMAGINGNET-1828 Support for WMF for possible conversion to raster images New Feature IMAGINGNET-1827 Support for SVG to Raster Image Conversion New Feature IMAGINGNET-1984 Unable to read file.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 3.7.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-7-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-7-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for .Net has been updated to version 3.7.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category IMAGINGNET-1605 Support FontSettings for CAD and Emf formats New Feature IMAGINGNET-1602 Cropping for emf files New Feature IMAGINGNET-1568 Implement support for Scalable Vector Graphics (SVG) 1.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 3.6.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-6-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-6-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for .Net has been updated to version 3.6.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
Features and Improvements Key Summary Category IMAGING-35315 Support merging PSD layers when converting to a JPG New Feature IMAGING-35301 Support export Emf/Emf+ files to raster formats New Feature IMAGING-35078 Support for Metafile (EMF) New Feature IMAGING-35317 Converting PSD to TIFF is producing incorrect TIFF image Enhancement IMAGING-35302 Improve memory usage while rendering emf/emf+ files Enhancement IMAGING-35198 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 3.5.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-5-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-5-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Features and Improvements Key Summary Category IMAGING-35200 Blur an Image [.Net] New Feature IMAGING-35199 Ability to add / import image to PSD layer [.Net] New Feature IMAGING-35192 Support image correction filters like GaussBlurFilter and RemoveNoiseFilter in Aspose.OCR [.Net] New Feature IMAGING-34756 Helper method to ensure that horizontal &amp;amp; vertical both resolutions are equal New Feature IMAGING-34753 Support DWG 2015 format New Feature IMAGING-34752 Support DWG 2014 format New Feature IMAGING-34614 Support noise removal feature New Feature IMAGING-34491 Support DICOM file format New Feature IMAGING-34336 Support EMF+ file format New Feature IMAGING-35283 Spelling mistake in class constructor : MotionWienerFilterOptions Enhancement IMAGING-35245 The signature of this program is corrupt or invalid Enhancement IMAGING-35235 Loading PSD file throws exception in version 3.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 3.4.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-4-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-4-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for .Net has been updated to version 3.4.0 and we are pleased to announce it. The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
Key Summary Category IMAGING-34882 Ability to detect if a PSD has been flattened; New Features IMAGING-34614 Noise Removal Feature in part of IMAGING-35228 Add support of median and Wiener filtration. New Features IMAGING-35221 Load/Save operation for gif image does not creates watermark on saved image in evaluation mode; Enhancements IMAGING-35212 Spelling Mistake of a property in WebPOptions class.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Imaging for .NET 3.3.0 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-3-0-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/imaging/net/release-notes/2016/aspose-imaging-for-net-3-3-0-release-notes/</guid><description>Aspose.Imaging for .Net has been updated to version 3.3.0 and we are pleased to announce it.
The following is a list of changes in this version of Aspose.Imaging.
New Features IMAGING-34909 Need add support of BITMAPV4 and BITMAPV5 headers for BMP
IMAGING-34482 Support for WebP Image Format
IMAGING-34461 Support tiled tiff images
IMAGING-34052 Read and Write XMP Data for Supported Image formats
IMAGING-33511 Support for JPM image format
IMAGING-33211 Support PSD TextLayer/IMAGING-33121 Ability to manipulate textual layer in PSD</description></item></channel></rss>