<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 21.12 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 21.12
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10452 Dashed line exported wrong as continuous in rotated images Enhancement CADJAVA-10449 Unify API to access layouts and layers Enhancement CADJAVA-10444 FBX failed to export to WEBP, DICOM, EMF and hang on export to BMP Enhancement CADJAVA-10437 Fix output for file Controller-M128-top.dxf in CadTests.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 21.11 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 21.11
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10384 Review test results for MTEXT export and related issues Enhancement CADJAVA-10383 Enrich and unify entities access API for all formats Enhancement CADJAVA-10380 Fix Cad files rendering issues Enhancement CADJAVA-10379 Fix performance issues for text export, review results. Enhancement CADJAVA-10378 Investigate issues with VPORT creation and validate coordinate preservation Enhancement CADJAVA-10376 Update etalons after MTEXT modifications Enhancement CADJAVA-10375 Investigate exceptions and other issues on test run Enhancement CADJAVA-10374 Fix problems with render and placement of composite glyphs, review other problems Enhancement CADJAVA-10373 Fix text rendern for several cad samples Enhancement CADJAVA-10370 Continue investigating test errors and fixing them Enhancement CADJAVA-10369 PCL raster data is not exported.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 21.8 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 21.8
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10307 Support dcm, emf, webp output formats Enhancement CADJAVA-10306 Implement emf export Enhancement CADJAVA-10296 Support ObserverPoint functionality on Iges file format rendering Enhancement CADJAVA-10291 Implement Exporter to fbx (ascii) Enhancement CADJAVA-10290 Export result disappears because of new viewport border change Enhancement CADJAVA-774 Unable to read Dwf content: Error on reading hoops object exception when loading DWF Enhancement CADJAVA-10314 Fix Circle and Arc export for PLT file format Enhancement CADJAVA-10313 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 21.7 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 21.7
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10271 Add PCL5 support for PLT format. Enhancement CADJAVA-10264 Watermark export option Enhancement CADJAVA-10257 Obj file rendering fix Enhancement CADJAVA-10255 Raster data from 1152_1.plt file correctly rendering by foundation library from PDF.Extensions, but foundation library from Aspose.CAD raises exceptions. Enhancement CADJAVA-10251 Implement dcm export Enhancement CADJAVA-10250 Implement webp export Enhancement CADJAVA-10244 Implement FBX format support Enhancement CADJAVA-10242 Rework MTEXT rendering Enhancement CADJAVA-10240 Implement FBX ascii reader Enhancement CADJAVA-10238 DWG file to PDF: How to center the drawing in the DWG into the PDF and display it in proportion Enhancement CADJAVA-10237 Implement export of serialized APS from Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 21.6 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-6-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 21.6
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10205 Implement correct rendering of Rotated dimension from scratch Enhancement CADJAVA-10203 Improve hatch export performance for the file in parent issue Enhancement CADJAVA-10202 Fix issue with MTEXT align Enhancement CADJAVA-10201 Fix coloring of some entities Enhancement CADJAVA-10200 Implement pantone colors support Enhancement CADJAVA-10135 Fix iges parsing infinite loop Enhancement CADJAVA-10131 Implement parsing of missed entities for Iges file format Enhancement CADJAVA-10129 Implement correct iges file rendering Enhancement CADJAVA-10219 Increase the performance of custom hatches export Enhancement CADJAVA-10213 Add functionality to define objectSize Feature CADJAVA-10211 Read the CadLine object from the overwritten AcDbObject Feature CADJAVA-557 [Internal] Implement rendering of united 3D solids from simple objects Feature</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 21.5 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-5-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 21.5
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10171 Improving performance of parsing dwf files Enhancement CADJAVA-10170 Aspose.CAD 20.10: Failed to open PLT Enhancement CADJAVA-10168 Imporve DWF import performance Enhancement CADJAVA-10166 Implement strikeout text support for MText entity Enhancement CADJAVA-10167 DWG is not completely exported to PDF Enhancement CADJAVA-10165 Customer properties are not getting saved in DWG/DXF Enhancement CADJAVA-10164 Specific IFC files failed to open Enhancement CADJAVA-10163 Fix the issue with mixing colors for RGB DWF internal image Enhancement CADJAVA-10162 Converted image from dxf doesn’t include all elements Enhancement CADJAVA-10160 Add a class to create a single AcDbObject Feature</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 21.4 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 21.4
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10147 Reducing memory usage dwg/dxf Enhancement CADJAVA-10138 Optimizing Cad2DPoint, Cad3dPoint and CadSize Enhancement CADJAVA-10137 Parameter is not valid exception on creating Images from DXF Enhancement CADJAVA-10148 Cannot open an image. The image file format may be not supported at the moment exception when loading IFC Enhancement CADJAVA-10145 Saving DXF file result in CadText and CadMText elements getting changed Enhancement CADJAVA-10141 &amp;ldquo;Image export failed.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 21.3 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-3-release-notes/</guid><description>
This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 21.3
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-10118 Implement export to DXF from all supported formats Feature CADJAVA-10116 Unify CAD 2D/3D exporters (remove 2D) Feature CADJAVA-10125 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: The Ifc version isn&amp;rsquo;t valid. Only Ifc: IFC2X3 are currently supported.&amp;rdquo; exception when open document IFC file Feature CADJAVA-10121 How to avoid margin in converting DWF to image Feature CADJAVA-10119 DWG to PDF results in unneccassary lines getting rendered Feature CADJAVA-10117 Exception on saving image as PNG Feature CADJAVA-10115 Missing Block Attribute values in exported PDF Feature CADJAVA-10114 Line Type Not Converting in exported PDF Feature CADJAVA-725 Stackoverflow exception on loading DWG Feature CADJAVA-10124 Entity resizing in a dxf file Feature</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 21.2 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 21.2
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-1004 Implement IFC4 support Feature CADJAVA-1000 Implement functionality allows to extract all text from underlying drawing Enhancement CADJAVA-997 Text objects is not exporting from ifc image. Enhancement CADJAVA-991 Fix Torus export to 3D format Enhancement CADJAVA-1003 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Unknown hoops operation code&amp;rdquo; exception when open document DWF file.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.CAD for Java 21.1 - Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/cad/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-cad-for-java-21-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.CAD for Java 21.1
Key Summary Category CADJAVA-973 Chinesse character are garbled and layers missing in exported PDF Enhancement CADJAVA-964 Implement possibility to add/delete/modify entities for OBJ file format Enhancement CADJAVA-962 Extract DWG different entities and save them in JSON or YML Enhancement CADJAVA-971 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: Unknown hoops operation code&amp;rdquo; exception when open document DWF file Enhancement CADJAVA-970 &amp;ldquo;Image loading failed: The method or operation is not implemented.</description></item></channel></rss>