<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2023 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.12
Major Features As part of our ongoing monthly update process for all APIs offered by Aspose, we are excited to announce the December release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. This release introduces enhancements and new features to our SVG Builder API, along with performance improvements in the CSS parser.
New Features: Enhanced SVG Builder API: We&amp;rsquo;ve expanded the SVG Builder API to include new methods that simplify the creation of SVG elements.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.11
Major Features As part of our ongoing monthly update process for all APIs offered by Aspose, we are excited to announce the November release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. This significant update introduces the new SVG Builder feature, along with important bug fixes:
New Features: Introducing SVG Builder: The highlight of this release is the addition of the SVG Builder, a major enhancement to our API.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.10
Major Features As part of our ongoing monthly update process for all APIs offered by Aspose, we are excited to announce the October release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. This release brings several enhancements and fixes:
Enhancements: Improved Font Caching for Text Element Rendering: In this update, we have enhanced the performance and accuracy of the rendering process by improving our system&amp;rsquo;s ability to cache fonts for text elements.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.9
Major Features As part of our ongoing monthly update process for all APIs offered by Aspose, we are excited to announce the September release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. This release includes a variety of improvements and fixes:
Enhancements: Optimized Memory Management for SkiaSharp Native Objects: In this release, a major focus was placed on the betterment of memory management for SkiaSharp Native Objects.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.8.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-8-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-8-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.8.1
Major Features As part of our ongoing monthly update process for all APIs offered by Aspose, we are excited to announce the August release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. This release includes a variety of improvements and fixes:
Enhancements: Aspose.SVG now supports the conversion of SVG documents to the WEBP format. Users of Aspose.SVG.Drawing.SkiaSharp extension will find: Support for SVG conversions to GIF and BMP formats.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.7
Major Features As part of our ongoing monthly update process for all APIs offered by Aspose, we are excited to announce the July release of Aspose.SVG for .NET. This release includes a variety of improvements and fixes:
Aspose.SVG Updates: Enhancements: Added support for rendering Gradients and Patterns in SVG Text Elements: This enhancement improves the visual quality of text in SVGs, offering a better viewing experience for users.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.6
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are proud to announce the June release of Aspose.SVG for .NET, which includes the following update:
New Features and Enhancements:
Added support for drawing with external extensions:
Introducing the new extension: Aspose.SVG.Drawing.SkiaSharp. The Aspose.SVG.Drawing.SkiaSharp extension enables drawing and rendering SVG images using the SkiaSharp library.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.5
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are proud to announce the May release of Aspose.SVG for .NET, which includes the following update:
Fixed an issue related to detecting UTF16 encoding for documents. The problem has been resolved in compliance with the WHATWG specification, &amp;ldquo;Determining the Character Encoding&amp;rdquo; link.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.4
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are proud to announce the April release of Aspose.SVG for .NET, which includes the following update:
The major additions in this release is support for using 7 lookup tables in TrueType fonts. These lookup tables, enable correct rendering of glyphs in the font.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.3
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are proud to announce the March release of Aspose.SVG for .NET, which includes the following update:
Fixed an issue where certain characters were displayed twice during SVG to PDF conversion (issue SVGNET-182). The root cause of this issue was incorrect processing of ligatures, which are special character combinations used in certain fonts to create more legible and visually appealing text.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.2
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are proud to announce the February release of Aspose.SVG for .NET, which includes the following updates:
Fixed a problem with parsing the SVG transform attribute when commands are linked together without any space.
Improved the algorithm for default naming of image files after converting SVG to raster images.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/svg/net/release-notes/2023/aspose-svg-for-net-23-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.SVG for .NET 23.1
Major Features As per the regular monthly update process of all APIs being offered by Aspose, we are proud to announce the January release of Aspose.SVG for .NET, which includes the following updates:
Support of Cancellation Token has been added to the SVGRenderer class. The Render method now supports a cancellation token, allowing users to request cancellation of the rendering operation while the task is in progress.</description></item></channel></rss>