<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 21.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 21.12.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-1006 Add line export support in U3D format New Feature THREEDNET-1005 Add line import suport in U3D format New Feature THREEDNET-1007 Improve memory efficiency for files with a lot of Node and entities. Improvement THREEDNET-964 USD file with unsupported diffuse definition will crash Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 21.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 21.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-999 Add TimeSamples support in USD Improvement THREEDNET-998 NullReferenceException in some USDZ files Bug fix THREEDNET-997 Some old 6.0 and 6.1 FBX files throws NullReferenceException Bug fix THREEDNET-996 Some malformed GLB file throws &amp;ldquo;Object reference not set to an instance of an object.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 21.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 21.10.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-962 Problems converting from FBX to USDC Bug fix THREEDNET-970 Wrong node names in imported FBX version 7700 Bug fix THREEDNET-965 Cannot import GLTF file packed as zip. Bug fix THREEDNET-967 Illegal property PropertiesView while deserialization CharacterConstraint Bug fix THREEDNET-963 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 21.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 21.9.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-930 Add PCD export support New Feature THREEDNET-926 Add XYZ import support New Feature THREEDNET-927 Add XYZ export support New Feature THREEDNET-938 Triangle-area based point cloud surface generation algorithm. New Feature THREEDNET-932 Add Point Cloud import support in A3DW format New Feature THREEDNET-931 Add Point Cloud export support in A3DW format Feature THREEDNET-946 Fixed PointCloud cannot be exported to PLY format Bug fix THREEDNET-934 Converting from USDZ to OBJ result in Exception Bug fix THREEDNET-936 Lock contention caused by GC in FBX importer Improvement API changes Most changes in 21.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 21.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 21.8.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-922 Add blind watermark support New Feature THREEDNET-920 Save to GLB file with external draco encoder lost many information. Bug fix THREEDNET-918 Significant lock contention in parallelized Scene.Open with fbx files Improvement THREEDNET-924 Vertex deduction was not always work in TriMesh Bug fix THREEDNET-923 Opacity is not handled in FBX importer Bug fix THREEDNET-912 FBX to GLTF2 Conversion issues Bug fix API changes Added com.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 21.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 21.7.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-870 Support for export to USDZ format. New Feature THREEDNET-901 Allow user to specify a factory class for FileSystem to improve security level New feature THREEDNET-902 Add GeomSubset in USDC exporter to support multiple materials Improvement THREEDNET-903 GLTF Save support material names Improvement THREEDNET-905 USD files containing skeleton are not supported.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 21.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 21.6.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-870 Add USDC export support. New Feature THREEDNET-891 Expose zip archive file system New Feature THREEDNET-892 Allow FBX exporter to embed textures during the export. New feature THREEDNET-895 Fixed some characters in node&amp;rsquo;s name will cause generated GLB file failed to pass validation Bug fix THREEDNET-896 Fixed empty scene cannot export to a valid glb file Bug fix THREEDNET-890 Add material/texture export in USDC Improvement THREEDNET-899 Expose the property of RelativeFilename for FBX Texture Improvement API changes Added USD as export type From 21.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 21.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 21.5.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-878 Draw black border around polygons New Feature THREEDNET-879 Convert STL to GLB results in invalid attribute: “/meshes/0/primitives/0/attributes/NORMAL_0” Bug fix THREEDNET-885 Aspose.3D renderer crashed due to large mesh loaded. Bug fix THREEDNET-884 Validation in converted GLB files. Improvement THREEDNET-882 Generated GLB file is not rendering in Babylon.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 21.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 21.4.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-864 Implement FileStream property for Texture Class to load image from a stream Improvement THREEDNET-867 Large obj file take a lot of time to load Improvement THREEDNET-865 Add Autodesk Navisworks compatible material for RVM format Improvement THREEDNET-874 Add support of latest RVM format.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 21.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 21.3.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-847 Add point cloud support in glb New feature THREEDNET-830 Provide low-level mesh API for web renderer. Improvement THREEDNET-838 Export 2.5D Topography with color to a file Improvement THREEDNET-849 Add byte[4] support in glTF export Improvement THREEDNET-832 Implement gizmos for light in web renderer Improvement THREEDNET-833 Implement gizmo for camera in web renderer Improvement THREEDNET-842 Add factor UV parsing support in FBX Improvement THREEDNET-852 Entity renderer architecture refactor for web renderer Task THREEDNET-836 Update the save/load option class names.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 21.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 21.2.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-825 Add USDZ import support. New feature THREEDNET-824 Add texture support in USDZ Task THREEDNET-811 Implement an evaluation version related Exception in the API Improvement THREEDNET-813 Technical details are required on Material and Texture API limitations - API doesn’t provide a way to discover textures on materials Improvement THREEDNET-817 Add support for texture byte[] in case of glb, gltf, obj Improvement THREEDAPP-80 Improve the page loading speed of web renderer Improvement THREEDNET-814 Triangle indices are not correct Bug fix THREEDNET-809 FBX Save Exception: Unsupported attribute type Bug fix THREEDNET-810 Filesize is getting bigger while reusing the same texture Bug fix THREEDNET-816 Incorrect mesh while loading OBJ Bug fix THREEDNET-807 There is no texture in the exported FBX Bug fix THREEDNET-815 Materials with shader model = Unknown will failed to render.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.3D for Java 21.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/3d/java/release-notes/2021/aspose-3d-for-java-21-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.3D for Java 21.1.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category THREEDNET-784 Add support of USDC format New feature THREEDNET-773 Add material support for DXF file Improvement THREEDNET-797 Add support for .net 5.0 Improvement THREEDNET-803 Improve ComboBox in web renderer. Improvement THREEDNET-795 Obj to u3d conversion - missing texture Bug fix THREEDNET-801 The implementation of camera&amp;rsquo;s orthographic projection is incorrect Bug fix THREEDNET-783 Map bitmap to triangles from GLB.</description></item></channel></rss>