<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2021 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.12</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.12.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-50991 Create example fixup Feature PDFNET-46044 Increase performance while adding text Enhancement PDFNET-40008 TIFF to PDF - Exception during conversion Bug PDFNET-45059 PDF to JPG - Cross reference table or cross reference stream not found Bug PDFNET-50458 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.11</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.11.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-49031 Allow non-latin characters in password Feature PDFNET-49705 PDF to Docx: Preserve Images in EnchantedFlow mode Enhancement PDFNET-50633 Add support for license in .NET 6.0 Enhancement PDFNET-35472 Operations with linearized document after Save() method call causes errors Bug PDFNET-50202 Property AllowExceptions in PdfFileSecurity class doesn&amp;rsquo;t work correctly Bug PDFNET-48729 System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.10</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.10.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-49992 Detect hidden text Feature PDFNET-29786 Get information regarding number of layers in PDF document Feature PDFNET-50621 Sign with OcspSettings throws Exception (ArgumentOutOfRangeException) Enhancement PDFNET-49582 Page.Background Property is not working when page is landscape Bug PDFNET-50215 HTML to PDF - Program hitting infinite loop and failing to generate PDF Bug PDFNET-42894 Text is overlapping in output after replacing fonts Bug PDFNET-48528 Parameter is not valid error occurs while converting PDF to PPTX Bug PDFNET-49367 PDF to PDF/A - Signature field have been disabled Bug PDFNET-49472 Invalid signature object error while removing the signatures Bug PDFNET-47938 Unable to get certificate chain when signing PDF from Certificate Store Bug PDFNET-49937 File size is getting increased while converting to grayscale Bug PDFNET-49392 PDF to Excel - table data is not correctly formatted in the output Bug PDFNET-45259 NullReferenceException is thrown by PdfFileEditor Bug PDFNET-43343 Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.9</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.9.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-48976 Support extended customization of Digital Signatures Appearance Feature PDFNET-50158 Collect data from the WidgetAnnotation Feature PDFNET-48659 Speed up while checking signatures Enhancement PDFNET-46513 Speed up while verifying signatures from PDF document Enhancement PDFNET-48471 Speed up convertion PDF to images Enhancement PDFNET-49707 PDF to DOCX: Recognize indents of paragraphs in EnhancedFlow mode Enhancement PDFNET-47669 Adding watermark causing second signature invalid in PDF Bug PDFNET-47666 Merge and sign PDF files making signature invalid Bug PDFNET-46336 System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.8</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.8.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-47235 Text color in Digital Signature Feature PDFNET-50167 Hyphenation characters for TextFragment Feature PDFNET-50226 Dynamic header and footer content is overlapping with body content Enhancement PDFNET-49798 A part of XMP-metadata elements is missing Enhancement PDFNET-50137 Line wrapping is not honored Enhancement PDFNET-48152 Exception on converting PDF to TIFF Bug PDFNET-47648 Exception on converting PDF to PDF/UA Bug PDFNET-47952 PdfFileEditor.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.7</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.7.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-49595 Advanced streams support to handle huge documents Feature PDFNET-50068 PDF creation based on XML and XLS with parameters Feature PDFNET-44278 High Resources Usage and Application Crash Enhancement PDFNET-49740 PDF/A became invalid after multiple digital signature Enhancement PDFNET-50059 Problem adding right aligned HtmlFragment in PDF Bug PDFNET-48206 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.6</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.6.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-49961 Hiding image using ImagePlacementAbsorber from the document Feature PDFNET-39127 Improve process to determine Page color information Enhancement PDFNET-45299 Improve getting page color type Enhancement PDFNET-49938 PDF to XLSX - Extra column is being added Bug PDFNET-48955 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.5</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.5.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-49418 Add .NET5 support for Aspose.PDF Feature PDFNET-49679 XFA: Add 3of9 barcode support for XFA to standard forms conversion Feature PDFNET-49791 How to extract font full name from it description/resource at PDF? Feature PDFNET-45405 Long time consumption during conversion of PDF to HTML Enhancement PDFNET-49437 Saving pdf document to docx format throws Index out of range exception Bug PDFNET-48916 Unable to retrieve JavaScript from the PDF - System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.4</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.4.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-49616 Add API for merging images Feature PDFNET-49596 HTML to PDF - Content is being repeated Bug PDFNET-49438 Aspose.PDF 21.2 Aspose.Pdf.GroupProcessor.IPdfTypeExtractor - errors while extracting a text from PDF if venture license is applied Bug PDFNET-49678 API is throwing exception on adding HtmlFragment in header/footer with customer text state Bug PDFNET-49317 TextBuilder instance corrupts text elements Bug PDFNET-39602 HTML to PDF - Exception during conversion Bug PDFNET-39762 HTML to PDF - Table with many columns is being truncated Bug PDFNET-42440 PDF to HTML - icon link is missing Bug PDFNET-48723 Inconsistent behavior with files over 2GB Bug PDFNET-49244 PDF to XLSX - result is different than our online demo Bug PDFNET-40921 Redaction annotation not working as expected Bug PDFNET-48627 Exception thrown when rendering from PDF with images in Linux Bug PDFNET-41983 Exception when optimizing the PDF file Bug PDFNET-49394 System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.3</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.3.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-47256 Public expose of property to detect Azure Information Protection Feature PDFNET-38013 Implement Getter for FontStyle property Enhancement PDFNET-48805 A generic error occurred in GDI+ when opening PCL Bug PDFNET-49434 XImage.Grayscaled property throws Null Reference exception Bug PDFNET-49249 PDF to HTML conversion does not honor italic text Bug PDFNET-49387 Object reference issue while merging PDF files Bug PDFNET-48902 Issue with adding attachment Bug PDFNET-48950 Cell splits into multiple cells Bug PDFNET-49157 Exception thrown: &amp;lsquo;System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.2</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.2.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-49194 PDF to Excel conversion takes to much time Enhancement PDFNET-48928 HTML to PDF using MemoryStream - Program keeps running and consumes all memory Enhancement PDFNET-49363 Enable updating of producer field Enhancement PDFNET-49258 Signa PDF with UseLTV as true - Object Reference not set to an instance Bug PDFNET-49314 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.1</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/pdf/net/release-notes/2021/aspose-pdf-for-net-21-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes information for Aspose.PDF for .NET 21.1.
Improvements and Changes Key Summary Category PDFNET-48470 After conversion to HTML the font is not fully embedded in the output. New Feature PDFNET-43227 Add support of retrieving the background color of TextFragment New Feature PDFNET-47217 Aspose.PDF 19.10: Converting a particular PDF to PDF 1.3 is very slow Enhancement PDFNET-49028 System.</description></item></channel></rss>