<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/</link><description>Recent content in Release Notes - 2020 on Releases - aspose.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 20.12 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-12-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 20.12.
Major Features There are 107 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Verified Aspose.Words for .NET Standard works with .NET 5.0. Added an ability to embed PostScript Fonts upon saving documents. Implemented condition evaluation extension point. Provided an option to import styles from a dynamically inserted document for LINQ Reporting Engine. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-16895 Add feature to insert style separator using DOM New Feature WORDSNET-20552 LINQ Reporting Engine - Provide a way to import styles from a dynamically inserted document New Feature WORDSNET-18827 Add option to perform memory optimization while loading document New Feature WORDSNET-21432 Check Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 20.11 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-11-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-11-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 20.11.
Major Features There are 80 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Document.SpellingChecked and Document.GrammarChecked properties were exposed publicly. Charts data points API was extended. Implemented basic support for rendering fonts with legacy Arabic encodings. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10130 Implement table row wrapping around floaters as MS Word 2013 does New Feature WORDSNET-16527 Incorrect RTL table row wrapping around a floater in 2013 mode New Feature WORDSNET-18416 DOCX to PDF conversion issue with table position Enhancement WORDSNET-20148 Table row does not break across pages Enhancement WORDSNET-20626 Converting DOC/DOCX to PDF - Page break issue Enhancement WORDSNET-21179 Saving requires a seekable stream Enhancement WORDSNET-14311 Font type is changed after converting Word to PDF Enhancement WORDSNET-21147 Expected a value between 0 and 22024 error occurs during Rendering a DOC Bug WORDSNET-21198 Creating instance of LayoutEnumerator throws System.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 20.10 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-10-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-10-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 20.10.
Major Features There are 89 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added support for loading CHM documents. Document.ExtractPages() feature was introduced. Implemented new API for exporting specific pages to fixed page formats. Released the first version of SmartArt Cold Rendering. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-3110 Allow export of non-sequential pages to rendered formats New Feature WORDSNET-17788 Consider supporting the CHM format New Feature WORDSNET-11143 DOCX to HTML issue with smartArt rendering New Feature WORDSNET-19983 Improve text effects rendering in .</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 20.9 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-9-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-9-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 20.9.
Major Features There are 82 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
VbaReferenceCollection and related types are exposed publicly. Implemented support of footnotes upon loading PDF documents. Implemented rendering of metafiles with EMF+ containers. The FormField font formatting API was extended. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-20589 PDF to DOCX - footnotes New Feature WORDSNET-522 Allow applying font formatting to FormField as a whole New Feature WORDSNET-20289 Passing correct border parameters through Words-HTML-Words roundtrip New Feature WORDSNET-13678 Provide a way to remove template reference from a Word document New Feature WORDSNET-20986 &amp;lsquo;Keep with next&amp;rsquo; property is changed after RTF to DOCX conversion Enhancement WORDSNET-19977 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 20.8 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-8-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-8-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 20.8.
Major Features There are 81 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Implemented Markdown Inline Images feature. Added new font substitution rule for font name processing. Added flag indicating whether images must be skipped while loading PDF document. Implemented support for SVG images embedded using data URLs upon HTML import. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-19654 Add support for SVG images embedded using data URLs New Feature WORDSNET-18471 ResolveFontNames option for HtmlFixedSaveOptions and SvgSaveOptions New Feature WORDSNET-20467 Implement Markdown Inline Images feature New Feature WORDSNET-7201 Problem with Copy Macros from one document to another Bug WORDSNET-20693 Elements of the SVG shape are disappeared when building the effect Bug WORDSNET-20473 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 20.7 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-7-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-7-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 20.7.
Major Features There are 91 improvements and fixes in this regular monthly release. The most notable are:
Added new nodes to handle multi-section structured document tags. Added a new public property MailMerge.RetainFirstSectionStart. RevisionOptions class is extended with new properties. Improved performance of SmartArt cold rendering. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-9500 International characters (Tamil) are not converted correctly from MHTML to PDF New Feature WORDSNET-7150 SDT controls are getting lost during open/save New Feature WORDSNET-9501 International characters (Telugu) are not converted correctly from MHTML to PDF New Feature WORDSNET-5713 StructuredDocumentTag containing Section Breaks is lost upon loading New Feature WORDSNET-20589 PDF to DOCX - footnotes New Feature WORDSNET-20480 Provide property to enable &amp;ldquo;strict MS Word behavioral compliance&amp;rdquo; during mail merge New Feature WORDSNET-9908 Preserve RichText Content Control with Section Break New Feature WORDSNET-6773 Row contents larger than page size truncate while setting AllowBreakAcrossPages=False Enhancement WORDSNET-20415 Maintaining rev bars when converting a DOCX to PDF with track changes Enhancement WORDSNET-18609 A line moves to the previous Page in PDF Enhancement WORDSNET-6721 DOC to PDF conversion issue with a Persian font Bug WORDSNET-13519 Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 20.6 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-6-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-6-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 20.6.
Major Features Font.EmphasisMark is exposed to the public. Added a new public property ImportFormatOptions.IgnoreHeaderFooter. MarkdownSaveOptions class is introduced. Provided options to control JSON simple values’ recognition for LINQ Reporting Engine. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-13983 Add feature to support &amp;lsquo;Emphasis on Mark&amp;rsquo; font setting New Feature WORDSNET-19976 Font embedding works fine but the symbol is saved to PDF incorrectly New Feature WORDSNET-20513 Check how Aspose.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 20.5 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-5-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-5-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 20.5.
Major Features Provided ability to show/hide Grammatical and Spelling errors. New helper class to work with watermark inside document was introduced. Added feature to set compression level for OOXML documents. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-10403 Add feature to &amp;lsquo;Hide spelling errors in this document only&amp;rsquo; New Feature WORDSNET-4879 Add a helper method to insert a watermark into the header New Feature WORDSNET-10404 Add feature to &amp;lsquo;Hide grammar errors in this document only&amp;rsquo; New Feature WORDSNET-20094 Add and option to remove duplicate styles to Document.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 20.4 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-4-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-4-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 20.4.
Major Features Starting from 20.4 version Aspose.Words also provides DLL for .NET 4.6.1. Like .NET Standard 2.0 it supports reading PDF documents. Provided ability to change Asian paragraph spacing and indents. Added image interpolation option for PDF rendering (new public property PdfSaveOptions.InterpolateImages). Added a new mode 3D shapes rendering. Extended API of chart data labels and series. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-15697 Providing ability to change password secured VBA code (change string) New Feature WORDSNET-20043 Expose public ComparisonLevel (Granularity) option New Feature WORDSNET-20001 Provide API to get set Word for Chinese specific Paragraph formattings New Feature WORDSNET-19913 Range.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 20.3 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-3-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-3-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 20.3.
Major Features No separate DLLs for Xamarin anymore. FindReplaceOptions class is extended with new properties. Implemented the correct rendering of the &amp;ldquo;Letterlike&amp;rdquo; symbols. Supported dynamic stretching of an image within textbox bounds preserving the ratio of the image for the LINQ Reporting Engine. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-18362 LINQ Reporting Engine - Provide option to fit the image within textbox bounds while maintaining ratio New Feature WORDSNET-19568 Provide ability to set different attributes of Shape inside IFieldMergingCallback.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 20.2 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-2-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-2-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 20.2.
Major Features Loading PDF documents is now supported by Aspose.Words for .NET Standard. Background shape texture image is now rendered the same way as in print layout of MS Word with a 100% scale. Supported dynamic insertion of documents and images from Base64-encoded bytes and dynamic checkbox value setting for the LINQ Reporting Engine. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-19561 Support dynamic checkbox value setting using LINQ Reporting Engine New Feature WORDSNET-19750 Add features to support field formats when FieldMergingArgs.</description></item><item><title>Aspose.Words for .NET 20.1 Release Notes</title><link>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-1-release-notes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://releases-qa.aspose.com/words/net/release-notes/2020/aspose-words-for-net-20-1-release-notes/</guid><description>This page contains release notes for Aspose.Words for .NET 20.1.
Major Features Implemented support of paragraph rules in footnotes. API to get/set the position of the floating table are exposed. Implemented an ability to check if VbaProject is signed. Added feature to insert IconCaption while using InsertOleObject. Supported dynamic bookmark insertion for LINQ Reporting Engine. Full List of Issues Covering all Changes in this Release Key Summary Category WORDSNET-12444 Support an API to check if VBAcode is signed New Feature WORDSNET-12204 Add feature to set/get positioning of floating table New Feature WORDSNET-19648 Create bookmarks using LINQ Reporting Engine New Feature WORDSNET-11833 Add feature to insert IconCaption while using InsertOleObject New Feature WORDSNET-19366 insertOleObject IconCaption filename New Feature WORDSNET-18818 Make DML image rendering resilient to images with corrupted SVG extensions Enhancement WORDSNET-19498 Content pushed to previous pages in PDF Enhancement WORDSNET-11110 DOC to PDF conversion issue with table&amp;rsquo;s layout Enhancement WORDSNET-19479 NullReferenceException occurs upon saving to HtmlFixed Bug WORDSNET-18603 Nested shapes overlaps cell borders Bug WORDSNET-19667 Paragraph marker changes from not hidden to hidden after document insert Bug WORDSNET-19671 DOCX to PDF conversion issue with content position Bug WORDSNET-19681 IgnoreFields options causes incorrect comparison Bug WORDSNET-19683 Document layout is not preserved after conversion from ODT to a DOCX Bug WORDSNET-19549 Word Document to PDF &amp;ldquo;Attempted to divide by zero&amp;rdquo; Bug WORDSNET-19674 Lucida Console text metrics do not match MS Word Bug WORDSNET-19601 DocumentProperty isLinkToContent fails for Numbers-type using bookmark in DOCX file Bug WORDSNET-18928 Add feature to insert IconCaption and correct icon while using InsertOleObject Bug WORDSNET-14272 DOCX to PDF conversion issue with Khmer font Bug WORDSNET-19625 After conversion to PDF a part of a table content is wrapping Bug WORDSNET-19659 System.</description></item></channel></rss>